[Music] you turned me on like a light switch
[音樂]你像電燈開關一樣打開了我
[Music]
[音樂]
foreign
外國的
[Music]
[音樂]
like a light switch [Music]
像電燈開關[音樂]
[Music] foreign
[音樂]外國的
baby [Music]
嬰兒[音樂]
[Music]
[音樂]
me [Music]
我[音樂]
[Applause]
[掌聲]
[Music]
[音樂]
you [Music]
你[音樂]
um [Music]
嗯[音樂]
[Music]
[音樂]
[Music] crying crying
[音樂]哭著哭
[Music]
[音樂]
i'm i loser [Music]
我是失敗者[音樂]
foreign
外國的
[Music] [Applause]
[音樂][掌聲]
[Music]
[音樂]
i love is
我愛的是
guys
伙計們
[Music] [Applause]
[音樂][掌聲]
[Music] is
[音樂]是
[Music]
[音樂]
foreign [Music]
外國的[音樂]
[Applause] [Music]
[掌聲][音樂]
is [Music]
是[音樂]
[Music]
[音樂]
um hello hi guys good morning
你好大家好，早上好
everybody yo yo yo what's up
大家喲喲喲怎麼了
hey bros hope you're having a great day so far dude it's already [ __ ]
嘿兄弟希望你有一個美好的一天到目前為止，伙計，它已經他媽的
thursday and my brain cannot comprehend
週四我的大腦無法理解
like the fact that it's already what that the week is already almost over
就像它已經是什麼這一周已經快結束了
that's like really it's like really crazy to me that
這就像真的，這對我來說真的很瘋狂
um i don't know it's already thursday like
嗯，我不知道已經是星期四了喜歡
i guess time has been passing by real fast the past couple of months but
我想時間已經過去了過去幾個月快但是
hey you know what they say about people that um you know
嘿，你知道他們怎麼說人那你知道
about people that uh or like if you know you feel like time is going by super
關於你或喜歡的人，如果你知道的話你覺得時間過得真快
super duper duper quick when you're just you know
超級騙子騙子快當你剛剛你知道
doing your thing it means that you're having fun right because like time
做你的事，這意味著你玩得開心，因為喜歡時間
passes by fast when you're having fun and to be honest i feel like i've been
當你玩得開心時快速通過老實說，我覺得我一直
having a lot of fun so i guess that's why like the months or like the weeks
玩得很開心所以我猜是這樣為什麼喜歡幾個月或幾週
have been going by so damn quickly recently yeah it's like dude i remember
過得真快最近是的，這就像我記得的伙計
it was march not sorry like mid-may so
這是三月，不像五月中旬那樣抱歉所以
man i don't know it's it just like blows my brain it like
伙計，我不知道這是它就像打擊我的大腦一樣
blows my brain out blows my blows my brain is that is that the right word
吹我的腦袋吹我的吹我的大腦是正確的詞
whenever whenever i use the word like blow it's like for the
每當我使用喜歡這個詞時吹它就像
you know but you know you know you know what i'm
你知道但是你知道你知道你知道我是什麼
trying to say right not the not the other thing but
試圖說對不是 不是 不是 其他 而是
the the the the thing the it's it's a saying i swear to sing i think it's a
那個東西它是一個說我發誓要唱歌 我認為這是一個
sing right some people say that
唱對有些人說
blow your brains out yeah
吹爆你的大腦是的
yeah it is a thing okay okay okay i'm not something cool
是的，這是一件事，好吧好吧好吧，我是不是很酷
sorry about that uh yummy thank you for the uh gift subs
對於那個很抱歉嗯，很好吃，謝謝你的禮物
and hikaru cindy thank you for the four months dude uh midnight thank you for
和 hikaru cindy 謝謝你的四個幾個月老兄呃午夜謝謝你
the gift subs as well dude um good morning all you guys welcome and
禮物也不錯，伙計，很好早上，你們歡迎和
uh jess thank you for the 2000 bits and
呃傑斯謝謝你的2000位和
gale thank you for the gift subs and yummy thank you for more give subs by
大風謝謝你的禮物潛艇和好吃，謝謝你更多的給潛艇
the way if you guys got a gift sub from anybody be sure to give them a big thank
如果你們從那裡得到一個禮物子的方式任何人都一定要非常感謝他們
you okay just uh send some send a little bit of
你沒事吧只是呃發送一些發送一點點
kindness back if you can because uh i'm sure they'd appreciate it as well
如果可以的話，善待我，因為我是當然他們也會很感激
okay but
好的但
today i
今天一世
wanted to finish up or like play through the rest of stanley parable because the
想要完成或喜歡玩斯坦利寓言的其餘部分，因為
last time we played it for the people that were there and watched the vod we
上次我們為人民演奏在那裡觀看了我們的視頻
couldn't finish it because my internet was just like oh haha let's do let's do
無法完成它，因為我的互聯網就像哦哈哈讓我們做吧
something funny and mode and it shut down
有趣的事情和模式並關閉
like during a very convenient part which was kind of spooky but um yeah
就像在一個非常方便的部分有點嚇人，但嗯是的
i just couldn't keep playing the game because my internet kept going on and
我只是無法繼續玩遊戲因為我的互聯網一直在繼續
off that day so i decided to just reschedule
離開那天所以我決定重新安排
it for this weekend hopefully we don't have any more internet problems come on
這個週末希望我們不要還有更多的互聯網問題嗎
guys guys i need you i need everybody here to like manifest good [ __ ]
伙計們，我需要你，我需要每個人在這裡喜歡表現得很好他媽的
internet so that we can finish this game i don't know if it'll happen again i
上網，這樣我們就可以完成這個遊戲我不知道它是否會再次發生
really doubt it will because i feel like the only times i have like sussy
真的懷疑它會因為我覺得我唯一喜歡蘇西的時候
internet is when it's like later into the night
互聯網就像後來一樣夜晚
so i don't understand like uh if it were to happen again like the only
所以我不明白如果它像唯一一樣再次發生
other time that it kind of happened before was like when i was uh finishing
其他時候它發生了之前就像我完成的時候一樣
it takes to a vox um a month ago so i don't think it will
它需要一個vox um一個月前，所以我認為不會
happen again in the morning that is
再次發生在早上
yeah yeah no no bad internet manifest only good internet so we can finish this
是的，是的，不，沒有糟糕的互聯網清單只有良好的互聯網，所以我們可以完成這個
game oh yeah by the way i hope everyone's
遊戲哦，是的，順便說一句，我希望每個人都
been enjoying the new video that i uploaded to my youtube so uh i
一直在欣賞我的新視頻上傳到我的 youtube 所以呃我
have been i talked with a new editor and they uh decided like i've been working
我和一位新編輯談過嗎？他們決定就像我一直在工作
with them and they want to uh you know edit down the overcooked collab that i
和他們在一起，他們想你知道編輯我的過度烹飪的合作
had with vox and into like one good video and i think it
與vox和喜歡一個好視頻，我認為
came out really really well so you guys should definitely check it out it's on
結果真的很好，所以你們絕對應該檢查一下它是否開啟
my youtube channel and um just let me know in the future if
我的 youtube 頻道和嗯以後告訴我
there's like any other games that you would want to see us play because we've
就像你喜歡的任何其他遊戲一樣會想看我們比賽，因為我們已經
been talking about different games that we want to try together but
一直在談論不同的遊戲我們想一起嘗試但是
and i think vox suggested chess like the old dog he is but like dude
我認為vox建議像這樣的國際象棋他是老狗，但像老兄
i don't know i feel like chess is something i would want to do
我不知道我的感覺國際象棋是我想做的事
like off stream more than like on stream i don't know who would want to watch us
喜歡直播比喜歡直播我不知道誰想看我們
like play chess for like five hours dude like
喜歡下象棋五個小時，伙計，就像
okay maybe maybe i'm like doubting myself too much but maybe a lot of you
好吧，也許我想懷疑我自己太多了，但也許很多人
actually but it's it's like i don't know i feel like i'd be so focused on the
實際上，但這就像我不知道我覺得我會如此專注於
game and so focused on trying to like you know mind game him so i don't know
遊戲，所以專注於嘗試喜歡你知道他的心理遊戲所以我不知道
if like playing chess for like that long will be would be uh feasible but yeah um
如果喜歡下棋那麼久將是可行的，但是是的
yeah if there's any cool collab games out there that you know about that you
是的，如果有任何很酷的合作遊戲在那裡你知道你
think we would enjoy that'll like you know hit the same kind of vibe as like
認為我們會喜歡你知道和喜歡一樣的氛圍
overclocked and it takes two other fun multiplayer co-ops then uh let me know
超頻，它需要另外兩個樂趣多人合作然後呃讓我知道
okay yeah yeah yeah yeah i suck at chess
好的是的，是的，是的，我的國際象棋很爛
though i haven't played chess like really seriously since like high school
雖然我沒有像這樣下過國際象棋真的很認真，因為喜歡高中
and i kind of forgot like what i for i remember stuff was just
我有點忘記了我記得的東西只是
like i forgot a few things you know
就像我忘記了一些你知道的事情
okay ah i'm super hyped to finish this game
好的啊，我很高興能完成這場比賽
though last time we played it it really like put us through a uh mind break trip
雖然上次我們真的玩過就像讓我們經歷一次心靈休息之旅
like it felt so crazy like imagine you're on like
就像想像的那樣瘋狂你喜歡
like a like you're on weed right is that the right one no no no it's like
就像你在雜草上一樣是那個正確的不不不它就像
you're on a trip you're like on this like like you're on a high right and and
你正在旅行 你喜歡這個就像你在右邊
also you're like um
還你就像嗯
how do i put it where's that one word i'm looking for
怎麼說呢 那個詞在哪裡我在找
it's like if you were to eat pop rocks right drink
就像是如果你要吃流行搖滾，就喝吧
soda masturbate and like do a i don't know triple like axle flip on like on
蘇打水手淫和喜歡做我不知道三重像軸翻轉一樣
this ice skating rink
這個溜冰場
thank you forward to more collabs with vox
謝謝你轉發更多的合作聲音
anything we'll do and how come you look so sus on twitter
我們會做的任何事情你怎麼在推特上看起來那麼難看
as well hey what do you mean how come i look so sus
還有，嘿，你是什麼意思，我怎麼來看起來很蘇
isn't that like all the time oh yeah speaking of um there's like i posted
是不是一直都這樣哦耶說到嗯，就像我發布的一樣
like a really cute um thingy from last night matami one of my friends like
就像一個非常可愛的東西晚上matami 我的一個朋友喜歡
helps me with the uh edit for that so thank you matami i love you
幫助我進行編輯，所以謝謝matami我愛你
um i'm gonna show like the other version
嗯我會像其他版本一樣展示
that i didn't get to show because i thought it was really uh adorable but
我沒有展示，因為我認為它真的很可愛但是
no that's not it again that's not it this is what it is my top five favorite
不，那不是它，那不是它這是我最喜歡的前五名
games
遊戲
i don't think i showed this one um on twitter but it's
我不認為我在上面展示過這個推特，但它是
like it was i was like it looks a little too
喜歡我也覺得它看起來有點像
embarrassed i'm a little too embarrassed there
尷尬 我有點太尷尬了那裡
i like it a lot though it's cute but you know two dude like
我很喜歡它雖然很可愛但是你知道兩個傢伙喜歡
vibes for me for uh that type of uh sweater i guess a lot more cozy than
對我的感覺，呃，那種類型的呃我想毛衣比毛衣舒服多了
embarrassed if anything
如果有什麼尷尬
uh zorden thank you for the zono glad you're streaming again this is one of my
呃 zorden 謝謝你的 zono 很高興你又在流媒體了，這是我的一個
top five favorite games of all time so i hope you'll be enjoying it i okay
有史以來最喜歡的五款遊戲，所以我希望你會喜歡它我還好
for the first like what hour and a half that i got to play it dude it was
第一個像什麼一個半小時我必須玩它，伙計
[ __ ] awesome like i did not expect to enjoy it that much and like i don't know
他媽的真棒，就像我沒想到一樣非常享受它，就像我不知道
like the the banter from the from the narrator is so funny too like
就像來自的玩笑旁白太有趣了
i know there's a multiple endings for the game like 40 something right 42 is
我知道有多個結局像40這樣的遊戲正確的42是
it 42 or is it more and we got like only like a handful right like a few of it
它是 42 還是更多，我們得到的只是像少數一樣
i'd say like less than 10. so we got like quite a few more to go i don't know
我會說不到 10 個。所以我們得到了想再去幾個我不知道
maybe i'll replay through some of the endings again because like
也許我會重播一些再次結束，因為喜歡
i don't know i really like the one where it just like propelled us into fire
我不知道我真的喜歡那個它就像把我們推向了火
watch for some reason in rocket league that was odd
在火箭聯賽中出於某種原因觀看這很奇怪
i'm gonna come why what did i do huh what did i do to
我要來為什麼我做了什麼啊我做了什麼
make you coom uh
讓你爽呃
it started with the and on an unrelated notes or hint
它以 and 開頭，不相關註釋或提示
it started with the until dawn stream i don't know what that means but ah thank
它始於直到黎明的溪流不知道那是什麼意思但是啊謝謝
you for the dono and i hope you're having a great day if that sounds kind
你是捐贈者，我希望你是如果這聽起來不錯的話，今天過得愉快
of ominous not gonna lie maybe thank you for the don't know you've been so tired
不祥之兆不會說謊也許謝謝你因為不知道你已經這麼累了
today but just hearing your voice makes me feel better
今天，但只是聽到你的聲音我感覺好多了
oh dude come here come here you guys cannot you know lay your head on my lap
哦，伙計來這裡，你們來這裡難道你不知道把頭靠在我的腿上
if you want while i play video games isn't that like is that what people do i
如果你想在我玩電子遊戲的時候這不就是人們所做的嗎？
feel like that's the dream right you just want to like land someone's lap
感覺這就是你的夢想只是想搭上某人的腿
while they're doing their work or like while you're playing something and just
當他們在做他們的工作或喜歡當你在玩東西的時候
like pass out and definitely not bite their thighs
像昏倒一樣絕對不咬他們的大腿
right definitely not nope no sir ah
對，絕對不是，不，先生啊
so yeah i'm thank you for the uh sincerely and give subs as well thank
所以是的，我很感謝你真誠地給潛艇以及感謝
you so much and himmers thank you for the 5 000 bits hope you had a great
你非常感謝他5 000 位希望你有一個偉大的
birthday by the way okay
順便說一句生日好的
it's time i'm ready i'm so [ __ ] ready for this
是時候了我準備好了 我他媽的準備好了
game let me uh switch on over to the screen
遊戲讓我呃切換到屏幕
i think here it is
我想在這裡
there's uh gonna be no heart rate monitor for this one today because i
不會有心率今天監視這個，因為我
thought like um it's not spooky this is not a horror game right
想，嗯，這並不可怕，這是不是恐怖遊戲吧
oh yeah [ __ ] hold on i forgot to turn on like um that's it
哦，是的，他媽的等一下，我忘了打開就像嗯就是這樣
let's turn on my vts stuff okay i think we're good now
讓我們打開我的 vts 東西，好吧，我想我們現在很好
yeah okay we're fine
是的，我們很好
with my music and we are pagan nice 69 a.m oh no 6 009 am no it saw was it
用我的音樂，我們是異教徒的好人69 a.m oh no 6 009 am no 它看到了
on my clock it's 9 00 22 a.m right now where i live
我的時鐘現在是上午 9 點 00 分 22 點我生活的地方
dude i just want to say i've never had like
老兄我只想說我從來沒有喜歡過
such powerful motivation to wake up like i wake up at like eight o'clock
如此強大的醒來動力就像我八點起床
usually um before or like even seven to get ready for stream like and i get
通常是在七點之前或者甚至七點之前準備好流，我得到了
right out of bed like really excited to say hi to you guys and hang out right
就像真的很興奮地下床一樣和你們打個招呼，然後出去玩
before i never like really enjoyed getting up that early like i always
在我從來沒有真正喜歡過之前像往常一樣早起
dreaded it for anything whether it was like for school for like to go out to
害怕它，無論它是喜歡上學 喜歡出去
get groceries or like you know to what to uh go do my job like it just i never
買雜貨或像你知道的那樣呃去做我的工作只是我從來沒有
had that motivation before like as powerful as this so i don't know you
之前有這種動機如此強大所以我不認識你
guys are amazing this is really amazing because like i never would have thought
伙計們太棒了，這真的太棒了因為我從來沒有想過
like i would be somewhat of a morning person now or like
就像我會現在有點像早起的人
uh you know more enjoy the mornings more and so like this
呃你知道更多像這樣多享受早晨
so yeah thank you no you changed me in a way
所以，是的，謝謝不，你在某種程度上改變了我
in a good way i think yeah so i'm just being a little sappy sorry
以一種好的方式，我認為是的，所以我只是有點悶騷抱歉
okay also i don't know we already hit the zono
還可以我不知道我們已經打了zono
goal for today that was really quick thank you guys um
今天的目標那真的很快謝謝你們
i might hide that later we'll see okay it's 9 24 am
我可能會隱藏，稍後我們會看到好的，現在是上午 9 點 24 分
hang on hang on before i get started can i just say
等等等等在我開始之前我可以說
something thank you for actually setting the clock
某物謝謝你實際設置時鐘
both times you boot up the game ah
兩次啟動遊戲啊
a lot of people don't take that step seriously they just leave the clock set
很多人沒有邁出這一步說真的，他們只是離開了時鐘
at 12 and calls a day but you're actually taking the time to
12 點，每天打電話但你實際上是在花時間
set the clock and i appreciate that wait who's saying that is that the
設置時鐘，我很感激等等，誰說那是
narrator that's how i know that you care about
敘述者我就是這樣知道你在乎的
this experience you're paying attention i don't even have any way of knowing if
你關注的這個經歷我什至不知道是否
the times you're sending are correct i tell you what i'll make you a deal
您發送的時間是正確的我告訴你我會讓你做個交易
since you've been so cooperative next time you boot up the game and see the
既然你下次這麼配合當你啟動遊戲並看到
screen just set the clock to your favorite time what what's my favorite
屏幕只是將時鐘設置為您的最喜歡的時間什麼是我最喜歡的
time go ahead pick whichever time you want
時間繼續選擇你想要的任何時間
even if it's not the correct time you've earned it i feel like i'm being trolled
即使現在不是正確的時間賺到了，我覺得我被拖了
like it's like they're they're like edging me
喜歡就好像他們在逼我
you know all right i'll let you get back to the
你知道好吧，我會讓你回到
video game now
現在的電子遊戲
that's cute okay that's kind of cute i i can't lie
這很可愛，好吧，這有點可愛，我我不能說謊
all right charlton goes back to his office job [ __ ] yeah
好吧，查爾頓回到他的辦公室工作他媽的是的
oh yeah accounting hr uh
哦是啊會計hr呃
yeah files tax
是的檔案稅
[Music] isn't that what people do
[音樂]人們不就是這樣嗎
i know a man named stanley stanley stanley stanley worked for a company in
我認識一個叫斯坦利·斯坦利的人stanley stanley 在一家公司工作
a big building where he was employee number four employee number employee
他是僱員的一座大建築四號員工號員工
number 427's job was simple he sat at his desk in room 427 and he pushed
427 號的工作很簡單，他坐在他在 427 房間的桌子，他推
buttons on the keyboard orders came to him through a monitor on his desk
鍵盤上的按鈕命令來了他通過辦公桌上的顯示器
oh i i didn't mean to click through that
哦我不是故意點擊那個
oops sorry achievement unlocked welcome back sassy
哎呀，對不起成就解鎖歡迎回來野蠻
narrator is back yeah he's he's very sassy his narrator has a lot of attitude
敘述者回來了，是的，他是他非常sassy 他的敘述者有很多態度
a lot of [ __ ] attitude
很多他媽的態度
you love him he's he's funny he's a funny guy he's a pretty funny british
你愛他 他很有趣 他是一個有趣的傢伙 他是個很有趣的英國人
lad a british lad i've had too much shaw you know
小伙子一個英國小伙子我受夠了你知道的
i've had more than enough like overload what could it mean
我已經受夠了，比如超載這意味著什麼
stanley decided to go to the meeting room perhaps he had simply missed a memo
斯坦利決定去開會房間也許他只是錯過了一個備忘錄
i've had more than enough british people no matter how hard stanley looked he
我有足夠多的英國人不管斯坦利看起來多麼努力，他
couldn't find a trace okay fine i'll just go i'll just go because he won't
找不到踪跡，好吧，我會的走吧，我就走，因為他不會
shut the [ __ ] up
閉嘴
you only talking okay fine for the rest of the stream i'll i'll talk
你只說好就剩下的我會說的
oh offend every person from the uk
哦，冒犯每個來自英國的人
i'll start now all right bruv
我現在就開始好吧布魯夫
oh my god that's a potted plant it's a window
哦，天哪，那是盆栽植物窗戶
that's a door that's a chair
那是一扇門那是一把椅子
i'm sorry is that is this getting to you i don't know lights
對不起，這是給你的嗎我不知道燈
what's the naming ob objects i got left or right i remember last time
ob對象的命名是什麼我向左或向右 我記得上次
i got i went right uh it's uh it like the game broke
我知道我走對了就像遊戲壞了
broke i can't i'll go left for a bit yeah i'll
壞了我不能我會向左走一點是的，我會的
actually pay attention to where he wants me to go
其實注意他想要的地方我去
okay
好的
god i'm such a dick i'm not a single person here either feeling a wave of
天哪，我真是個混蛋，我不是單身這裡的人要么感覺一波
disbelief stanley decided to go up to his boss's office hoping he might find
難以置信的斯坦利決定上去他老闆的辦公室希望他能找到
an answer there go to my boss's office oh no i don't want i don't want to do
去我老闆的辦公室找答案哦，不，我不想我不想做
the actual ending hold on i had to go
實際的結局堅持我不得不去
chris he's supposed to be in the broom closet
克里斯，他應該在掃帚裡壁櫥
oh my god dude if i feel like i am i am like tilting so many so many people i am
哦，天哪，伙計，如果我覺得我是我我喜歡傾斜這麼多這麼多人
i apologize i'm i i'm it's just like i can't i don't
我道歉我是我我是這就像我不能我不
know don't i'm doing my best all right this is what
知道不我正在盡力而為，這就是
um hanging out onto a staircase stanley walked upstairs oh oh my god bloody hell
嗯，在樓梯上閒逛 stanley走到樓上哦，我的天，該死的地獄
holy [ __ ] dude like there's actually like a bottom floor now
天哪，這傢伙喜歡現在實際上就像是底層
before there was like it was fenced off and they wanted me to go upstairs
在它被圍起來之前他們要我上樓
by the way for people that are new to the stream i don't actually talk like
順便說一句，對於不熟悉的人我實際上不喜歡說話的流
this okay i i feel i think it feels very
這個好吧，我覺得我覺得這感覺很
awkward if um somebody just came in here and they're like oh damn he's he's one
如果有人剛進來就尷尬了他們就像哦，該死的，他是他的一個
of us like and i know no i'm not i don't talk like this i'm actually very
我們喜歡，我知道不，我不是，我不這樣說話我其實很
american all right
美國人好的
i don't know if i'm even doing a good job or not
我什至不知道我是否做得很好工作與否
oh oh no
哦不好了
oh no no it's okay it's it's all right it's all right i think okay maybe oh
哦，不，不，沒關係，沒關係沒關係，我覺得還可以，也許哦
shite dude dude i think okay okay we're fine we're fine okay
狗屎伙計，我想好吧好吧，我們是很好，我們很好
guys i thought okay okay okay back to very good dude i thought we i thought
伙計們，我想好吧好吧好吧回到很好，我以為我們認為
i i think we jinxed it did we jinx it like the bat the internet like lags out
我想我們把它搞砸了，我們把它搞砸了像蝙蝠一樣，互聯網就像落後一樣
for a second because of like uh what's it
一秒鐘因為像呃什麼它
because we jinxed it oh no bro
因為我們把它搞砸了哦，不，兄弟
did i die [ __ ] up that did i like uh you know accidentally
我死了嗎我喜歡那個你不小心知道的
manifest bad internet or maybe all of you guys are manifesting yeah you gotta
表現出糟糕的互聯網或所有你們正在表現，是的，你必須
bring back the good internet i can't believe it's happening again all right i
帶回好的互聯網，我做不到相信它會再次發生，好吧我
can't believe it's happening again
不敢相信它再次發生
oh yeah we shouldn't be down here but here we are but stanley just couldn't do
哦，是的，我們不應該在這裡，但是我們在這裡，但斯坦利做不到
it he considered the possibility of facing his boss admitting he had left
他認為有可能面對他的老闆承認他已經離開
his post during work hours he might be fired for that and in such a competitive
他在工作時間的職位他可能是為此而被解僱，在這樣一個競爭激烈的
economy why had he taken that risk all because he believed everyone had
經濟 他為什麼要冒這個險因為他相信每個人都有
vanished his boss would think he was crazy yeah i'm pretty crazy something
消失了他的老闆會認為他是瘋了，是的，我很瘋狂的東西
occurred to stanley maybe maybe to himself maybe i am crazy i am crazy all
斯坦利突然想到也許也許他自己也許我瘋了我都瘋了
of my co-workers blinking mysteriously out of existence in a single moment for
我的同事神秘地眨眼在一瞬間不存在
no reason at all none of it made any logical sense
完全沒有理由沒有任何邏輯意義
for example why couldn't he see his feet when he looked down huh why did doors
例如為什麼他看不到他的腳當他低頭時，為什麼門
close automatically behind him wherever he went oh man you're creeping
在他身後自動關閉他走了哦，伙計，你在爬行
rooms were starting to look pretty familiar were they simply repeating
房間開始看起來很漂亮熟悉的是他們只是重複
no stanley said to himself this is all too strange this can't be real and at
沒有斯坦利對自己說這就是全部太奇怪了，這不可能是真實的
last he came to the conclusion that had been on the tip of his tongue he just
最後他得出的結論是他只是在舌尖上
hadn't found the words for it i'm dreaming
還沒有找到它的詞我在做夢
he yelled this is all a dream oh what a relief stanley felt to have
他大喊這一切都是夢哦，斯坦利感到多麼寬慰
finally found an answer an explanation his co-workers weren't actually gone he
終於找到答案解釋他的同事實際上並沒有離開他
wasn't going to lose his job he wasn't crazy after all
他不會失去工作畢竟瘋了
and he thought to himself i suppose i'll wake up soon i'll have to go back to my
他心想我想我會的快醒來我得回到我的
boring real-life job pushing buttons i may as well enjoy this while i'm still
無聊的現實工作按按鈕我趁我還在的時候好好享受吧
lucid so he imagined himself flying and began
清醒的所以他想像自己在飛翔並開始
to gently float above the ground then he imagined himself soaring through
輕輕地漂浮在地面之上然後他想像自己飛過
space on a magical starfield and it too appeared it was so much fun and stanley
神奇星空上的空間，它也是看起來很有趣，斯坦利
mother the [ __ ] has happened still not woken up
媽的，還沒有發生醒了
how was he remaining so lucid and then perhaps the strangest question
他怎麼還這麼清醒然後也許是最奇怪的問題
of them all entered stanley's head one he was amazed he hadn't asked himself
他們都進入了斯坦利的腦袋之一他很驚訝他沒有問自己
sooner why is there a voice in my head
早點為什麼我的腦海裡有聲音
dictating everything that i'm doing and thinking
口授我正在做的一切思維
now the voice was describing itself being considered by stanley who found it
現在聲音在描述自己被找到它的斯坦利考慮
particularly strange i'm dreaming about a voice describing me thinking about how
我夢到的特別奇怪一個聲音描述我在思考如何
it's describing my thoughts he thought and while he thought it all very odd and
它在描述我的想法，他認為雖然他覺得這一切都很奇怪
wondered if this voice spoke to all people in their dreams the truth was
想知道這個聲音是否對所有人說人們在夢中的真相是
that of course this was not a dream how could it be
那當然這不是夢怎麼可能
was stanley simply deceiving himself believing that if he's asleep he doesn't
斯坦利只是在欺騙自己相信如果他睡著了他不會
have to take responsibility for himself stanley is as awake right now as he's
必須對自己負責斯坦利現在和他一樣清醒
ever been in his life what's happening dude now hearing the voice speak these
曾經在他的生活中發生過什麼老兄現在聽到聲音說這些
words was quite a shock to stanley after all he knew for certain beyond a doubt
之後的話讓斯坦利感到非常震驚毫無疑問，他所知道的一切
that this was in fact a dream did the voice not see him float and make the
這實際上是一個夢想聲音沒有看到他漂浮，使
magical stars just a moment ago how else would the voice explain all that this
神奇的星星剛才怎麼了聲音能解釋這一切嗎
voice was a part of himself too surely surely if he could just
聲音肯定是他自己的一部分當然，如果他能
he would prove it he would prove that he was in control
他會證明的他會證明他在掌控之中
that this was a dream so he closed his eyes gently and he invited himself to
這是一個夢，所以他關閉了他的眼神溫柔，他邀請自己
wake up he felt the cool weight of the blanket
醒來他感覺到毯子冰涼的重量
on his skin the press of the mattress on his back
在他的皮膚上床墊壓在他背上
the fresh air of a world outside this one
外面世界的新鮮空氣一
let me wake up he thought to himself i'm through with this dream
讓我醒來 他心想我完成了這個夢想
i wish it to be over i let me go back to my job
我希望它結束我讓我回到我的工作
let me continue pushing the buttons please
讓我繼續按下按鈕請
it's all i want i'm like i want my apartment and my wife my wife and my job
這就是我想要的我就像我想要我的公寓和我的妻子 我的妻子和我的工作
all i want is my life exactly the way it's always been i have a wife what my
我想要的只是我的生活完全一樣一直以來，我有一個妻子，我的
life is normal i am normal
生活很正常我很正常
everything will be fine there is no war embossing say
一切都會好起來的沒有戰爭壓花說
okay copium copium copium copium copium
好的copium copium copium copium copium
copium he's on copium
副本他在復印
stanley began screaming oh please someone wake me up my name is stanley i
斯坦利開始尖叫哦拜託有人叫醒我我的名字是斯坦利我
have a boss i have an office i am real please just someone tell me i am real i
有老闆我有辦公室我是真實的請有人告訴我我是真實的我
must be real i must be can anyone hear my voice who am i who am i
一定是真的 我一定是真的 任何人都可以聽到我的聲音我是誰我是誰
and everything went black what the [ __ ] dude
一切都變黑了什麼他媽的伙計
actually this is the story of a woman named mariella huh
其實這是一個女人的故事叫瑪麗拉哈
wait why ella woke up on a day like any other
等等，為什麼埃拉會像任何一天一樣醒來其他
she arose got dressed gathered her belongings and walked to her place of
她站起來穿好衣服聚集了她收拾東西，走到她的住處
work but on this particular day her walk was interrupted by the body of a man
工作，但在這一天她走路被一個男人的身體打斷
he stumbled through town talking and screaming to himself and then collapsed
他在城鎮談話中跌跌撞撞，對自己尖叫然後倒下
dead on the sidewalk and although she would soon turn to go call for an
死在人行道上，雖然她很快就會轉身去打電話
ambulance i died for just a few brief moments she considered the strange man i
救護車我死了只是短暫的當她考慮我這個陌生男人的時候
died obviously crazy this much she knew everyone knows what crazy people look
死得很明顯，她知道這麼多每個人都知道瘋子的樣子
like and in that moment she thought to herself how lucky she was to be normal
喜歡，在那一刻她想她自己是多麼幸運，她是正常的
i am saying i am in control of my mind i know what is real and what isn't
我是說我可以控制我的思想我知道什麼是真的什麼不是
it was comforting to think this and in a certain way seeing this man made her
想到這一點很令人欣慰以某種方式看到這個男人讓她
feel better but then she remembered the meeting she
感覺好多了但後來她想起了她的會面
had scheduled for that day the very important people whose impressions of
原定那天印象深刻的重要人物
her would affect her career and by extension the rest of her life
她會影響她的職業生涯延長她的餘生
she had no time for this so it was only a moment that she stood there staring
她沒有時間做這件事，所以只有她站在那裡凝視的那一刻
down at the body and then she turned and ran
身體向下然後她轉身就跑
[Music] wow
[音樂]哇
man
男人
weed is a very very powerful tool damn
雜草是一個非常非常強大的工具該死
that's all i have to say okay
這就是我要說的好的
well like yeah that happened
出色地就像是的那樣發生了
um
嗯
that like happened so fast like the escalation from oh sorry the escalation
事情發生得如此之快，就像升級從哦對不起升級
from what happened once i went downstairs was like bloody
從我去的時候發生的事情樓下就像血腥
creepy in insane old man i'm mixing my accents now
瘋狂的令人毛骨悚然老頭，我現在正在混合我的口音
anyways that was one ending i think uh we can go on to a different ending right
不管怎樣，那是一個結局，我想呃我們可以繼續不同的結局
yeah yeah yeah all of his co-workers were
是的是的，是的，他所有的同事都是
gone what could it mean i decided to go to the meeting you know
走了是什麼意思我決定去參加你知道的會議
i sounded like uh forrest gump there for a
我聽起來像呃阿甘正傳一個
i think i think i was like it's like i second
我想我覺得我就像我第二
creep gennady gennady
蠕變 根納迪 根納迪
new content what
新內容什麼
tempting door what a [ __ ] tempting door you are
誘人的門你是多麼他媽的誘人的門
new content ah
新內容啊
you know this feels this feels like a honey
你知道這感覺就像蜂蜜
uh a honey pot like they they're baiting me like who just puts this on a door
呃一個蜜罐，就像他們在誘餌一樣我喜歡誰只是把這個放在門上
this is like the ultimate bait for any streamer or like any content creator new
這就像任何人的終極誘餌流媒體或像任何內容創建者一樣新
content are you gonna walk on in of course
內容你會走進去嗎課程
new content what does that mean new content
新內容 新內容是什麼意思內容
what if i just walk away no no
如果我走開怎麼辦 不不
nope okay
沒關係
they're baiting me they're masturbating me yes
他們在引誘我 他們在[ __ ]我可以
well i'm locked in now [ __ ] night
好吧，我現在被鎖了他媽的晚上
this better not be a horror game it feels it better not be a horrible
這最好不是恐怖遊戲感覺最好不要太可怕
hello and thank you for playing the stanley parable ultra deluxe
你好，謝謝你玩斯坦利寓言超豪華
as you may know the stanley parable was a video game released in 2013 on home
你可能知道斯坦利的比喻是2013 年在家發布的視頻遊戲
computers after receiving critical and commercial
電腦在收到關鍵和商業信息後
success it was expanded upon in 2022 with the stanley parable ultra deluxe a
它在 2022 年得到了擴展與斯坦利寓言超豪華
reimagining of the game for consoles and home computers
重新構想遊戲機和家用電腦
i feel like i'm on the stanley parable ultra deluxe features exciting new
我覺得我在斯坦利的寓言上超豪華功能令人興奮的新功能
content that broadens and expands the world of the stanley parable delighting
擴大和擴展的內容斯坦利寓言的世界令人愉快
audiences the world over more more
世界各地的觀眾更多更多的
more please step inside and see what thrilling new adventures await in the
更多請走進去看看驚心動魄的新冒險等待著
stanley parable ultra deluxe wait did i just finish like this sounds delightful
斯坦利寓言超豪華等待我嗎像這樣結束聽起來很愉快
i'm very excited to see the thrilling new ultra deluxe content
我很高興看到驚心動魄的新的超豪華內容
oh hold on wait does that mean hey guys does that mean that
哦，等等，這是否意味著嘿，伙計們這是否意味著
i i beat the like original stanley parable
我打敗了原來的斯坦利比喻
like is that what it means this is like more
喜歡這是什麼意思 這更像
like the additional stuff that they added to the game
喜歡他們額外的東西添加到遊戲中
like i've already gone through everything from the first stuff okay i
就像我已經經歷過從第一件事開始的一切都好，我
guess that's why the door opened right because i've seen everything there is to
猜猜這就是為什麼門正確打開的原因因為我已經看到了一切
see in the original
看在原來的
supposedly all right cool if i just go back no i don't want to go back
如果我去就好了不，我不想回去
special yet but i'm sure it's just the beginning of a mesmerizing adventure
特別的，但我敢肯定這只是迷人冒險的開始
a mesmerizing adventure hello
一場迷人的冒險你好
um why is it broken what's going on here am i stuck are we stop bro should we be
嗯，為什麼它壞了這裡發生了什麼我被困住了嗎，兄弟，我們應該停下來嗎？
moving somewhere oh there we go all right finally i got
搬到某個地方哦，我們一切都好，最後我得到了
scared it's one of my fears getting stuck in an elevator like that never
害怕這是我的恐懼之一從來沒有像這樣被困在電梯裡
been more ready let's do it it's really not horror yeah it's not
準備好了，讓我們開始吧這真的不是恐怖，是的，不是
horror today not no horror i just want a vibe
今天的恐怖不是沒有恐怖我只是想要一個氛圍
i have to say initial impressions of stanley parable ultra deluxe mythius
我不得不說最初的印象斯坦利寓言超豪華神話
it's as if them oh okay let's see the content give me
就好像他們哦，好吧，讓我們看看內容給我
the content stanley
內容斯坦利
you know it's like he's a parasite the narrator is like a parasite in my brain
你知道這就像他是一個寄生蟲敘述者就像我腦子裡的寄生蟲
it's like pushing me to do more bad things
這就像在逼我做更多的壞事事物
oh the jump circle what is this okay i'm done talking british accent i
哦，跳圈這是什麼好吧，我說完英國口音了
can't take it seriously anymore the jump circle
不能再認真了跳躍圈
i can jump now
我現在可以跳了
like it looks like i'm down i'm bouncing i'm bouncing i can jump now before i
好像我倒下了，我在彈跳我正在彈跳 我現在可以在我之前跳
couldn't jump hold on wait i can't jump outside of the circle
等不及了我不能跳出圈子
i can jump like
我可以跳
[ __ ] it like delays me
他媽的喜歡耽誤了我
before i can get anywhere else
在我去別的地方之前
that's all i have ah what how do i get more jumps
那是我的全部了啊，我怎樣才能獲得更多的跳躍
oh is is that it
哦是是這樣嗎
surely that's not all the new content there has to be something else right
當然這不是所有的新內容必須有其他正確的事情
i don't know i want to jump more i want some more made out i feel like a
我不知道我想跳更多我想要更多的東西，我覺得自己像一個
bunny when i'm jumping like that yeah you want to see me i mean there's a lot
兔子當我那樣跳的時候是的你想見我我的意思是有很多
of shoto made out oh my god there's so many people that drew me in the maid
哦，我的上帝，我的天啊！許多人把我吸引到了女僕
outfit uh a couple days ago thank you for that it's super cute i remember uh
前幾天的衣服謝謝因為它超級可愛我記得呃
i think another an artistry like miuki and uh shoe together and made off and i
我認為另一個像 miuki 這樣的藝術和 uh 鞋子在一起，然後我就走了
thought that was so adorable it made me made me gush
覺得那太可愛了，這讓我讓我滔滔不絕
you know that was hella cute
你知道那太可愛了
was that it just more jumping just some jumps
是它只是更多地跳躍而已跳躍
goodness another elevator stanley i have to say
善良另一個電梯斯坦利我不得不說
initial impressions of this game are not positive it's just elevators and jumping
對這款遊戲的初步印像不是積極的，這只是電梯和跳躍
is this what passes for exciting new content if this is new content then i
這就是令人興奮的新事物嗎內容 如果這是新內容，那麼我
could just read you the whole dictionary there's 20 hours of new content right
可以給你讀整本字典有 20 小時的新內容吧
there hell i could counter 30 trillion you could put that on the box the
地獄我可以對抗30萬億你可以把它放在盒子上
stanley parable ultra deluxe now with over a thousand hours of new content and
斯坦利寓言超豪華現在與超過一千小時的新內容和
if oh wait there's more
如果哦等等還有更多
very good yes i knew there had to be something else let's see it i'm ready
很好，是的，我知道必須有別的東西讓我們看看我準備好了
for whatever it is somebody uh typed in chat i don't understand you but i love
不管是什麼人輸入的聊天我不懂你但我愛
you thank you for watching dude i don't know how many people here are
謝謝你收看老兄我不知道這裡有多少人
watching but can't understand what i'm saying but hey i'm glad you're here
看但不明白我是什麼說但是嘿我很高興你在這裡
thank you for coming by and watching even though you can't really understand
謝謝你的光臨觀看即使你無法真正理解
what i'm saying that's uh that's sweet you know it's really
我在說那是呃那很甜蜜你知道這真的
sweet uh thank you for enjoying the new content wait
親愛的，謝謝你享受新的內容等待
no way bro did i just get debated is that it don't lock me in [ __ ]
沒辦法，兄弟我只是被辯論了是它不會把我鎖在他媽的
oh you've got to be kidding me you see stanley this is what happens when greedy
哦，你一定是在開玩笑吧，你看斯坦利這就是貪婪時發生的事情
video game developers with no respect for their fan base rush a cheap
不受尊重的視頻遊戲開發者為他們的粉絲群搶便宜
expansion to market for no reason other than to make an easy dollar and don't
無緣無故地拓展市場 其他而不是賺到容易的美元而不是
get me started on the level of craftsmanship that's gone into it in
讓我開始融入其中的工藝
fact i'm looking right now at the game's achievements and it's hard to believe
事實上我現在正在看比賽成就令人難以置信
one of them actually says test achievement please ignore what quality
其中一個實際上說測試成就請忽略什麼品質
assurance department signed off on this i'm infuriated and i'm offended and i i
保證部門在此簽字我很生氣，我很生氣，我我
intend to find these people on twitter and help them personally accountable
打算在推特上找到這些人並幫助他們承擔個人責任
what's the male equivalent of a character too much anticipation around
什麼是男性的等價物性格太期待周圍
the new content i'm afraid he could never have lived up to such expectations
新內容恐怕他可以從來沒有辜負過這樣的期望
if you're still with me why don't we just reset the game and we'll try to get
如果你還在我身邊 為什麼我們不只需重置遊戲，我們將嘗試獲取
back to what he's gonna write it's quit longer really about
回到他要寫的內容真的更長
no frills narrator really said i'm gonna write it to it longer right now having a
沒有多餘的敘述者真的說我會現在寫更長的時間
great time together like always what do you say friend
像往常一樣在一起的美好時光你說什麼朋友
an atom oh wait we just gotta we just gotta
一個原子哦，等等，我們只需要我們只需要
reset again wait new area oh hold up yeah it's actually new
再次重置等待新區域哦，等等是的，它實際上是新的
kinda new
有點新
[Music] you can't believe he's gonna cancel the
[音樂]你無法相信他會取消
game's developers for making a money grab game
遊戲開發者製作搶錢遊戲
when he's part of the game himself that's crazy dude
當他自己參與比賽時那是瘋狂的傢伙
that's crazy dial
這是瘋狂的撥號
is this what the old off yeah that's the old office
這是什麼舊關閉是的舊辦公室
i used to be there that was my that's my home well
我曾經在那裡那是我的那是我的家
not really my home stanley
不是我的家斯坦利
come over here in the vent i want to show you something
到通風口過來我給你看個東西
who the [ __ ] would listen to that what coming to the vents it's not sauce
誰他媽的會聽那個什麼來到通風口它不是醬汁
among us among us among us among us i don't want to go in the vent do i really
在我們之中 在我們之中 在我們之中 在我們之中我真的不想進入通風口嗎
want to go on the vent but there's so many there's so many cool things over
想去通風口，但有這樣的有很多很酷的事情
here
這裡
wait this kind of looks like the original office
等待這種看起來像原辦公室
hmm
唔
uh all right i mean i guess you win since i
呃好吧，我的意思是我猜你贏了，因為我
don't want to go back to the regular office just yet
不想回到常規辦公室剛剛
don't eat me please more coffee nut and screwdrivers what's
請不要吃我更多咖啡堅果和螺絲刀什麼是
with the what's with the nuts and the screwdrivers
堅果是怎麼回事螺絲刀
what is coffee nut
什麼是咖啡果
aren't you guys friends no he's just the voice in my head you remember how cheap
你們不是朋友嗎，不，他只是我腦海裡的聲音你記得有多便宜
and unsatisfying the new ultra deluxe content turned out to be but it got me
並且不滿意新的超豪華內容原來是，但它讓我
thinking about the past and how much better the stanley parable used to be so
想著過去和多少更好的斯坦利寓言曾經如此
i made something special and tucked it away here where the games developers
我做了一些特別的東西並把它藏起來遠離遊戲開發者的地方
won't find it just our little secret
不會找到它只是我們的小秘密
take a look what the [ __ ] is this
看看這是什麼鬼
like the entire vibes just changed in an instant
就像整個氛圍剛剛改變立即的
huh where are we
呵呵我們在哪裡
ah i call it the memory zone it's where
啊我稱它為記憶區
i've been storing all my favorite memories so i can relive the peak
我一直在存儲我所有的最愛回憶讓我重溫高峰
experiences of my life whenever i want experiences like the launch of the
隨時隨地體驗我的生活體驗，例如推出
stanley parable on pc
電腦上的斯坦利寓言
how do we how do we get in there all the memories out you oh
我們如何進入那裡回憶出來你哦
you definitely don't look dangerous
你看起來絕對不危險
i mean it doesn't really look that dangerous
我的意思是看起來不像危險的
it's pretty peaceful i would go here and and vibe
很平靜我會去這里和氛圍
you see stanley doesn't the memory zone remind you of how wonderful stanley
你看斯坦利沒有記憶區讓你想起斯坦利是多麼美妙
parable was before it was solid with a cheap re-release
寓言是在它堅固之前廉價重新發布
remember back in october of 2013 when the game originally launched no back
記得在 2013 年 10 月遊戲一開始就沒有退路
then video games had integrity why back then it all meant he's like back in my
那麼電子遊戲有完整性 為什麼要回來那麼這一切都意味著他就像回到了我的
day back in my day
天想當年
we had good video games in 2013 zone sweet zone
2013 年我們有很好的電子遊戲甜蜜地帶
yeah he's like oh he's like the boomer that can't like uh you know he even has
是的，他就像哦，他就像嬰兒潮一代那不能喜歡你知道他甚至有
the steam page he has the [ __ ] steam page right on the in the frame oh my god
他有他媽的蒸汽的蒸汽頁面頁面右側在框架中哦，我的上帝
get over yourself like
克服自己喜歡
it's like those boomers that uh you know like and things used to be so much
就像那些你知道的嬰兒潮一代喜歡和過去的事情太多了
better back then nowadays like video games and music and what they used
比現在更好電子遊戲和音樂以及他們使用的東西
to be my my first kiss my first car released a
成為我的初吻 我的第一輛車發布了
stanley parable in 2013. ill oh my god this looks like such a
2013 年的斯坦利寓言。哦，天哪，這看起來像這樣
pinterest picture
興趣圖片
who's this guy
這個人是誰
yeah who's this dude again another steam
是的，這傢伙是誰再次蒸汽
yeah another steam page i've never played the original game so
是的另一個蒸汽頁面我從來沒有玩過原版遊戲所以
this is like this is weird for me it's like do i
這就像這對我來說很奇怪，就像我一樣
remember no i don't i never played the original game
記得不，我不，我從來沒有玩過原創遊戲
trip down memory lane smile because it happened
沿著記憶小路微笑，因為它發生了
why is this such like you know such a this is like the
為什麼會像你知道的那樣這就像
live laugh love equivalence
活笑愛等價
type of image
圖像類型
go outside it's on play for five years is this actually an achievement
出去玩五年這真的是一項成就嗎
wait is this is this an achievement for real go outside
等等，這是一個成就嗎真正走出去
wow
哇
unachievable is impossible to get this achievement [ __ ] you okay okay
unachievable 是不可能得到這個成就他媽的你好吧好吧
british academy award of course the british academy award
英國學院獎當然是英國學院獎
all right now he's dead so um is that it
好吧，現在他死了嗯，就是這樣
god i feel so out of place right now the wrong person is where i keep reviews
天啊，我現在感覺很格格不入錯誤的人是我保留評論的地方
of the stanley parable like this stunning triumph of games journalism 10
像這樣的斯坦利寓言遊戲新聞的驚人勝利 10
out of 10 from destructoid.com james stephanie sterling
滿分 10 從destructoid.com 詹姆斯·斯蒂芬妮·斯特林
writes and i quote we're so many games that aspire to be
寫，我引用我們有很多渴望成為的遊戲
more than games end up less than any form of art stanley parable strives and
多於遊戲最終少於任何斯坦利寓言的藝術形式努力和
then succeeds to be every game ever created did you hear that stanley every
然後成功地成為每場比賽創建你聽到斯坦利每
game ever created that's how grand and all-encompassing the original stanley
遊戲曾經創造過如此盛大和包羅萬象的原始斯坦利
parable was it was literally every game ever created it was skyrim it was
比喻真的是每場比賽曾經創造過它是天際
persona 3. it was all of them and now it's nothing i played persona 3 and
角色 3. 是所有人，現在這沒什麼我玩的角色 3 和
stanley parable why isn't even the stanley parable anymore it's just a husk
斯坦利寓言為什麼甚至不是斯坦利的寓言不再只是一個外殼
now a lifeless husk with an hour of new
現在一小時新的死氣沉沉的外殼
elevator content damn i didn't realize i played skyrim
電梯內容該死的，我沒有意識到我玩了天際
and persona 3 in the span of one hour last time
和角色 3 在一小時內上次
minecraft wait why is there minecraft wait what's
我的世界等等為什麼有我的世界等等是什麼
that door why does that look so eerie it's like a creepypasta
那扇門為什麼看起來如此詭異就像令人毛骨悚然的意大利面
what's with the minecraft picture huh
我的世界圖片是怎麼回事呵呵
and this how the tasteful nostalgic it was good
和這個多麼有品味的懷舊它是好的
okay now yo downstairs or they go up here
好的，現在你在樓下或者他們上去這裡
oh
哦
and memory zone maintenance hold on hold on we have two options here
和記憶區維護暫停在我們這裡有兩個選擇
the original remake do i give a [ __ ] about this or should i
原版翻拍我是在乎這個還是應該
go
去
hmm hold on
唔堅持，稍等
oh no i want to go in the door [ __ ] he doesn't let me go in the door why
哦，不，我想進門去他媽的不讓我進門 為什麼
doesn't let me go inside let me go inside you
不讓我進去 讓我走在你的內心
here's another moving passage this time from gamespot.com
這次是另一個動人的段落來自gamespot.com
the stanley parable is both a richly stimulating commentary on the nature of
斯坦利的寓言既富有對性質的刺激性評論
choice in games and one that offers some of the most enjoyable surprising and
遊戲中的選擇和提供一些最令人愉快的驚喜和
rewarding choices i've ever been confronted with in a game nine out of
我曾經做過的有益的選擇在一場比賽中面臨九場
ten don't you get it stanley the game was perfect it didn't need anything else
十 你不明白嗎 stanley 遊戲很完美，不需要其他任何東西
it didn't need new content it just needed to be left alone to spend
它不需要新內容它只需要一個人呆著花
the rest of time collecting dust in the hallowed hall of beloved video game
其餘時間收集灰塵心愛的電子遊戲的神聖大廳
members get me out get me out
成員讓我出去讓我出去
oh
哦
these were simpler times stanley but i wouldn't give to go back to have
這些是更簡單的時代斯坦利但我不會放棄回去擁有
it all over again wait
一切重新來過等待
hang on i don't recall this part of the memory
不掛斷我不記得這部分記憶
zone before what's this what's down here
前區這是什麼
oh where was this oh no oh god no stanley it's a
哦，這是在哪裡哦不哦上帝不斯坦利這是一個
collection of reviews from steam the online video game distributor i haven't
收集來自 Steam 的評論我沒有在線視頻遊戲經銷商
looked at these in years i can't even team reviews collecting
這些年來我什至不能團隊評論收集
oh boy oh boy we get so we get to read some we have to read some hater comments
哦，天哪，天哪，我們明白了，所以我們開始閱讀有些我們必須閱讀一些仇恨評論
here we go you bothered to play this game to full completion the narrator is
我們來了，你費心玩這個遊戲完全完成敘述者是
obnoxious and unfunny with his humor and dialogue proving to
令人討厭和無趣用他的幽默和對話證明
be more irritating than entertaining i'm funny i'm not trying to be funny i'm
我比娛樂更煩人搞笑我不是想搞笑我是
trying to make a serious work of art i suppose i could write up a handful of
試圖做一件嚴肅的藝術品我假設我可以寫一些
gags to insert into the stanley parable but the game is already such a densely
塞進斯坦利寓言的噱頭但是遊戲已經是這麼密集了
layered web wow unfunny
分層網頁哇無趣
that i can't even imagine where i'd have the room to stick them he couldn't
我什至無法想像我會在哪裡貼他們的房間他不能
handle one bad criticism damn i'm lucky bro
處理一個糟糕的批評該死的我很幸運兄弟
call him unfunny poor narrator you know dude i think you're funny
稱他為無趣的可憐的敘述者，你知道的伙計，我覺得你很有趣
you're a pretty funny guy a pretty funny face
你是個很有趣的人 很有趣臉
yeah maybe this was a bad idea maybe we
是的也許這是個壞主意也許我們
shouldn't have gone here it feels like uh
不應該去這裡感覺就像呃
a left or dead map for some for some reason
一些人的左地圖或死地圖原因
this is not opening hello oh hey another bad review see what
這不是開放的你好哦嘿另一個差評看看什麼
this one says while the idea for the game is good
這個說雖然遊戲的想法很好
for someone who prefers non-linear games this preachiness gets annoying fast
對於喜歡非線性遊戲的人這種說教很快就很煩人
preachy stanley i'm not preachy am i you wouldn't tell me if i'm preachy
說教的斯坦利，我不是說教的，我是不是你不會告訴我我是不是說教的
honestly you can oh goodness this is actually quite shocking for me but i
老實說，你可以哦，天哪，這是實際上對我來說很震驚，但我
always will to be honest i had always thought of the game's dialogue as being
老實說，我總是認為遊戲的對話是
rather tears to begin with you can't know how much fluff i cut from
一開始就流淚你不知道我剪了多少絨毛
the game to get it to feel as light and airy as it well i always thought it did
遊戲讓它感覺很輕，通風很好，我一直認為它確實如此
but maybe it wasn't uh i i yeah what an awful memory to have to hold on
但也許不是呃，我是的多麼可怕的記憶必須堅持
to i think he's pretty uh my otherwise unimpeachable track record
我認為他很漂亮，否則我的無可挑剔的記錄
i feel like a failure
我覺得像失敗一樣
like i let these people down perhaps the stanley parable isn't quite
就像我讓這些人失望也許斯坦利的寓言並不完全
as sterling as i always remembered he he saw two bad reviews and he was
像我一直記得的那樣純正他看到兩個差評，他是
like i'm a failure what no
就像我失敗了什麼不
bro why you can't just just like take that
兄弟為什麼你不能只是喜歡拿那個
as like oh my god it's such a you know it's like
就像哦，我的上帝，這就是你知道的
the small amount of people are like oh you're terrible i hate this person right
少數人喜歡哦你太可怕了 我討厭這個人 對
there's always gonna be the small percent of people that don't like you
總會有小的不喜歡你的人的百分比
right or like like the game or like whoever
對或喜歡 喜歡游戲或喜歡誰
focus on all the good all the people that support you
專注於所有的好所有的人支持你的
support the game i wish i could jump right now my god i miss the jumping
支持我希望我能跳的遊戲現在我的上帝我想念跳躍
circle
圓圈
yeah poor narrator no there's another one
是的可憐的敘述者，不，還有另一個
what's this one got to say 2014. you constantly have to stop doing
2014 年這個人要說什麼。你必須經常停止做
anything so the narrator can catch up with his long-winded explanations of
任何讓敘述者能夠趕上的東西用他冗長的解釋
what's happening i wish there was a skip button
發生了什麼我希望有一個跳過按鈕
a skip button well well yes yes i think we can do that
跳過按鈕好吧，是的，是的，我認為我們可以做到
if i'm truly too preachy then then maybe letting you skip ahead for just a moment
如果我真的太說教那麼也許讓你跳過片刻
surely it couldn't hurt not if it means we can strike these negative reviews
如果這意味著它肯定不會受到傷害我們可以打擊這些負面評論
from the record only positive reviews of the stanley barrel that's my memory
從記錄來看，只有正面評價那是我記憶中的斯坦利桶
today and it's always been my model what is that i can do anything for the
今天，它一直是我的榜樣是我可以為
customers yes a skip button we shall have
顧客是的，我們將有一個跳過按鈕
wait we have a skip button now you have a second here it is go ahead
等等，我們現在有一個跳過按鈕你有一秒鐘，繼續
and give it a shot i'll pop you forward in time so that the second my incessant
試一試，我會帶你向前及時讓我的第二個不停
droning starts to bore you with just the push of a button you'll have zip right
嗡嗡聲開始讓你感到厭煩按下按鈕，您將擁有正確的拉鍊
past it it's what the players have been asking for i'm very proud to have
過去，這就是球員們一直以來的樣子要求我很自豪有
delivered no more listening to me rambling on and on and on no no no no
不再聽我說話不不不不不不不不不不不不不
the stanley parable is a game for the people and if the people want silence
斯坦利寓言是一個遊戲人們，如果人們想要沉默
then by goodness that's what they're going to get well then sit around
天哪，他們就是這樣會好起來然後坐
waiting for me to shut up go ahead and make me shut up here we'll pretend that
等我閉嘴繼續讓我閉嘴，我們會假裝
i've just begun an intern listen to it and it goes something like this
我剛開始實習 聽聽它是這樣的
the story and the choices or what have you can i just listen to it by becoming
故事和選擇或有什麼你能不能讓我聽聽
it is so on and so forth until inevitably we all until the end of time
如此等等，直到不可避免地我們都直到時間的盡頭
at which time everything rolled once so now you see blah blah blah
那時一切都滾動了一次現在你看到了等等等等
we've eaten too much and it can't be just yet no no until
我們吃得太多了，不可能只是還沒有，直到
245 that the logic of elimination working backwards the deduction
245那淘汰的邏輯倒推扣除
therefore becomes impossible to manufacture it went on for nearly 10 000
因此變得不可能製造它持續了近 10 000
years until just yesterday oh my god you are this is like a filibuster what the
直到昨天，天哪，你這像阻撓議事嗎？
heck ah it's the only thing there is okay
哎呀這是唯一可以的
okay okay i get it but i don't want to skip
好吧好吧我明白了，但我不想跳過
i
一世
once so now you see he just skipped back he just he just went back i have to skip
曾經所以現在你看到他只是跳過他只是他剛回去我必須跳過
him too much and he comes he's saying everything again
他太多了，他來了，他說一切又來了
until 245 that the logic
直到 245那個邏輯
i kind of had to back you see you were only frozen in time for a few minutes
我不得不支持你看你是只凍結了幾分鐘
but it was plenty of time for me to deliver a long rambling monologue full
但我有足夠的時間發表冗長的漫無邊際的獨白
of unnecessary verbal flourishes and lengthy ruminations on the nature of
不必要的口頭花言巧語和對性質的冗長反省
choice in video games of course i happen to believe it was perhaps one of my more
我當然會選擇電子遊戲相信這也許是我的更多
profound such ruminations not that of course you need a description of it but
深刻的這樣的沉思不是當然，您需要對其進行描述，但是
if i had to
如果我不得不
oh well there's sport you really did catch me rambling on it didn't you but
哦，你真的做了什麼運動抓到我在胡說八道，不是嗎？
that's the power of the button the minute i start to go off on a
這就是按鈕的力量分鐘我開始去
thoughtless display of self-absorption it's
輕率地展示自我它是
okay welcome back stanley i should say that the amount of time the button has
好吧，歡迎回來斯坦利，我應該說按鈕的時間量
been skipping through is becoming longer and longer that last one was well i want
跳過的時間越來越長我想要的最後一個很好
to say maybe 30 45 minutes it's not unendurable by any means but it's
說也許 30 45 分鐘不是無論如何都無法忍受，但它是
stanley stanley stanley please don't push the button again it's been 12
斯坦利 斯坦利 斯坦利 請不要再次按下按鈕 已經 12 點了
hours you've just been frozen there i don't know why the skips are getting
幾個小時你剛剛被凍結在那裡我不知道為什麼跳過
longer but they're really truly getting again my god
更長，但他們真的得到了又是我的上帝
oh stanley you're back what you're back oh my goodness i have someone to talk to
哦，斯坦利，你回來了，你回來了哦，我的天哪，我有人要說話
again stanley i i think it's been a week for two weeks
再次斯坦利，我想已經一周了兩週
i've been sitting here all that time just sitting here not a single person to
我一直坐在這裡只是坐在這裡沒有一個人
speak with and you'd think that's sad just how it's always oh that's so sad me
和你說話，你會覺得這很可悲怎麼總是這樣啊，我太難過了
talking and you saying nothing um i'm good i'll see you in like a month
說話，你什麼也沒說，嗯，我是很好，一個月後見
oh hello oh
哦你好哦
hello it's you you're here again welcome i have had time to think about you and
你好，是你，你又來了，歡迎我有時間想你和
about us and about everything we've been through i've had so much time i stopped
關於我們和我們曾經的一切由於我有這麼多時間我停下來
keeping track after a year a year down in one place and not move for one entire
一年後跟踪在一個地方而不是一整個移動
year let me describe it for you no i don't want to hear it
年份讓我為你描述一下不，我不想听
oh okay now how long has it been is he dead
哦，好吧，現在他有多久了死的
oh my god i think he's dead i killed him oh my god i killed him
哦，我的上帝，我想他已經死了，我殺了他哦，我的上帝，我殺了他
he's gone how long has it been a year it's been
他走了一年有多久了
more than years maybe has it been like 10 years
多年來，也許一直是這樣10年
hello narrator you there did i kill you by
你好旁白你在那裡我殺了你
accident
事故
oh [ __ ] he's dead
哦，他媽的他死了
the clock isn't even moving the batteries are gone the plan is dead
時鐘甚至沒有移動電池沒電了 計劃沒了
um [Music]
嗯[音樂]
well this is kind of an awkward situation
好吧，這有點尷尬情況
if i wait a bit he'll still be around right
如果我等一下，他還會在附近正確的
now
現在
uh-huh what what what's happening
嗯嗯什麼發生了什麼事
is that the fire alarm
那是火警
i think that's a fire alarm but they didn't understand the game was never
我認為那是火警，但他們不明白遊戲從來沒有
meant to be funny it was meant to have a point it was meant to speak to the human
本來是有趣的點它是為了和人類說話
condition but where are they where are the jokes they bemoan they screamed they
條件，但他們在哪裡？他們哀嘆的笑話他們尖叫他們
gnashed their teeth and said entertain us it wasn't in hello they had to leave
咬牙切齒說請自便我們不在你好，他們不得不離開
i'm back little thumbs down review and make all of their pitiful demands but
我回來了小拇指向下評論和提出他們所有可憐的要求，但
then he's talking too much they said first he did oh my god okay i'm not
然後他說的太多了，他們說首先他做了哦，我的上帝，好吧，我不是
gonna read all that good for you or sorry that happened i guess i don't know
會讀到對你有好處的一切，或者對不起，我想我不知道
oh man the clock fell
哦，天哪，時鐘掉了
you guys ever have that you guys ever get those kinds of texts they're like
你們曾經有過你們曾經有過得到他們喜歡的那種文本
super long you're just like damn i'm really not in the mood to read all that
超長你就像該死的我一樣真的沒有心情閱讀所有這些
sorry it happens sometimes
對不起它有時會發生
sometimes i feel bad for him i do that for him too
有時我為他感到難過我也為他這樣做
it's making me feel guilty all right because we have a skip button he just he
這讓我感到內疚因為我們有一個跳過按鈕他只是他
took one one review it was like oh wow fine let me just blow it out proportion
拿了一篇評論就像哦哇好吧，讓我把它吹出來
the end is never the end is never the end is never the end is never the end is
結束永遠不是結束終點永遠是終點永遠是終點
never the end is never the end is never the end is never the end is never the
永無止境 永無止境 永無止境結束永遠不是結束
end is never the end is never the end is never the end is never the end it's
終點永遠是終點永遠是終點永遠不會結束
never the end it's never the end it's never the end it's never the end it's
永遠不會結束 它永遠不會結束 它是永遠不會結束 它永遠不會結束 它是
never the end it's never the end oh my god how do you breathe how does this guy
永遠不會結束 它永遠不會結束 oh my上帝，你怎麼呼吸這傢伙怎麼樣？
breathe never the end is never the end is never the end is never the end is
呼吸 永遠不會結束 永遠不會結束永遠不會結束 永遠不會結束
never the end
永遠不會結束
dude when can i leave is there like a door that'll magically open for me when
伙計，我什麼時候可以離開？門會神奇地為我打開
can i go
我可以去嗎
it's leaking the building's leaking
它在洩漏建築物漏水
i want out man i want out of this place there's a big mistake there's a big
我想出去，我想離開這個地方有一個很大的錯誤有一個很大的
mistake man get me out i feel like there's a monster
錯誤的人讓我出去，我覺得有一個怪物
that's gonna show up behind the walls please
那會出現在牆後請
oh that's bad
哦，那很糟糕
that's pretty bad dude how long have we been here like
這很糟糕伙計，我們在這裡待了多久了
canonic like everything's gone like
典型的喜歡一切都過去了
disheveled and broke down and decomposed ass have been at least like 10 000 years
蓬頭垢面 分解 腐爛屁股至少已經有 10 000 年了
right maybe maybe a little 10 000 years
正確的也許可能有一點 10 000 年
i can see the outside oh my god sunlight oh my god sunlight
我可以看到外面哦我的上帝陽光哦，我的上帝陽光
no there's nothing
不，什麼都沒有
ah narrator you're around
啊敘述者你在身邊
he's been he's been real quiet i think he is well he's gone insane i don't know
我想他一直很安靜他很好 他瘋了 我不知道
where he went he's probably still here but just forgot
他去了哪裡他可能還在這裡，只是忘記了
oh man oh man this isn't good
天啊哦，伙計，這不好
guys this isn't good what the [ __ ] huh oh oh nature got inside somehow
伙計們，這不好，他媽的呵呵，哦，自然不知怎的進入了裡面
that's that's really pretty okay this is really pretty
這真的很好 這是真的很漂亮
i'm not gonna lie i like that a lot you know i like it when the nature overtakes
我不會說謊我很喜歡你知道我喜歡大自然超越
i kind of want it is it gonna is it gonna keep growing inside what's what's
我有點想要它是它會是它會在裡面不斷成長
next what comes after this huh
接下來是什麼
what but huh
什麼但是啊
oh
哦
what but how how did that happen
什麼，但這是怎麼發生的
is that the sky up there no i can't see the sky
是那裡的天空 不 我看不見天空
or is it like covered up by like debris i don't know
還是像被碎片一樣覆蓋我不知道
no the grass i can't touch grass anymore
沒有草，我不能再碰草了
i'm gonna go to the next part
我要去下一部分
what is going on what's happening here
到底是怎麼回事這裡發生了什麼事
this is not supposed to be a horror game guys guys we're not supposed to have a
這不應該是一個恐怖遊戲伙計們，我們不應該有
horror experience right now
恐怖經歷馬上
this was meant to be a chill game huh
這本來是一個寒冷的遊戲呵呵
what's going on can i get out
這是怎麼回事我能出去嗎
i feel like i'm stuck man i think yeah i'd probably the
我覺得我被困住了伙計，我想是的，我可能會
sunlight got blocked from whatever is out there
陽光被擋住了在那裡
whatever that was i think something collapsed on the building
不管我怎麼想倒在大樓上
skip get me out
跳過讓我出去
oh
哦
i can't press the button anymore am i free
我不能再按按鈕了，是嗎？自由的
freedom
自由
narrator
敘述者
am i am i playing like monster hunter now
我是不是像怪物獵人一樣玩現在
what's happening [Music]
發生了什麼[音樂]
bro this is so trip this is so trippy like
兄弟，這真是太棒了，太棒了喜歡
okay the end is never the end it's never the
好的終點永遠不是終點
end it's not everything ha
結束這不是一切哈
what but no no there had to be more to that why did
什麼但沒有不，必須有更多，為什麼
you [Music]
你[音樂]
bro why well i i wanted to
兄弟為什麼我想
i wanted to you know let's see more
我想讓你知道讓我們看看更多
i guess there was not much to see though it was just all flat sand right
我想雖然沒什麼可看的只是所有平坦的沙子
i don't know if he died i think narrator died he's probably back now right are
我不知道他是否死了，我想敘述者死了，他現在可能回來了
you back narrator all of his co-workers were gone what could it mean oh my god
你回來講述他所有的同事走了這意味著什麼我的上帝
he's back danny decided to go to the meeting room perhaps he had simply
他回來了，丹尼決定去會議室也許他只是
missed a memo dude he's back holy [ __ ]
錯過了一個備忘錄，伙計，他回來了天哪
new content new new content
新內容新的新內容
should i go inside i kind of have to right
我應該進去嗎我不得不糾正
it feels like i kind of have to i mean it's a very compelling sign i think
感覺好像我不得不說我認為這是一個非常引人注目的跡象
anybody would be uh convinced
任何人都會是深信不疑
and they used uh some my favorite colors blue and pink so oh good you notice my
他們用了一些我最喜歡的顏色藍色和粉色，太好了，你注意到了我的
sign yes i have something very exciting to see
簽名是的，我有一些非常令人興奮的事情查看
okay was it this time where is he kidnapping me now till
好吧這次是他現在在哪裡綁架我直到
two now
現在兩個
more elevators huh you see stanley i've been reflecting
更多電梯嗯，你看斯坦利，我一直在反思
on the stanley parable oh my gosh shut up about the stanley parable just let me
在斯坦利的寓言中哦，我的天哪，閉嘴關於斯坦利的寓言讓我
i say we take it one step even further which is why i'm very proud to announce
我說我們更進一步這就是為什麼我很自豪地宣布
for the first time ever the stanley parable
有史以來第一次史丹利的寓言
huh [Music]
呵呵[音樂]
yes you see isn't this far superior to a measly re-release with a few minor
是的，你看這不是遠遠優於微不足道地重新發布了一些未成年人
additions think of all the new territory we'll cover with a fully fledged sequel
補充想到所有的新領域我們將介紹一個成熟的續集
an entirely new experience built from the ground up why there is so many
一種全新的體驗徹底解決為什麼有這麼多
possibilities he could go in so many different directions
他可以進入這麼多的可能性不同的方向
this is what fans have truly been asking for
這就是粉絲們一直在問的為了
what does it say
它說什麼
do
做
oh that's just two right yeah taste the sequel
哦，那隻是兩個，是的嚐嚐續集
new and tasty
新的和好吃的
how tasty is it calling it the stanley parable 2 is just so much catchier than
叫它斯坦利有多好吃寓言 2 比第二個更吸引人
ultra deluxe don't you think ultra ducks what does it even mean it's like when
超豪華你不覺得超鴨嗎它甚至意味著什麼時候
you get an ultra deluxe hamburger cheeseburger it's an artistic statement
你會得到一個超豪華的漢堡包芝士漢堡這是一種藝術宣言
that's why i thought it's like a future better cheeseburger it screams progress
這就是為什麼我認為這就像一個未來更好的芝士漢堡它尖叫著進步
and innovation and long-term franchising potential
和創新和長期特許經營潛在的
it's like uh it's like the same cheeseburger right but now it has like
就像呃一樣芝士漢堡，但現在它有
another uh burger patty you probably put like more cheese on it maybe uh maybe a
另一個你可能放的漢堡肉餅喜歡更多的奶酪也許呃也許是
fried egg and uh maybe like some bacon on it too
煎雞蛋呃，也許也喜歡一些培根
and uh maybe the buns aren't like regular buns now they're like sesame
呃，也許小圓麵包不像普通包子現在它們就像芝麻一樣
seed buns and you also have like you know uh curly fries will fit too and you
種子包子，你也有喜歡的知道呃卷薯條也適合你
have like um you know truffle aioli to dip it in and then you have a chocolate
就像你知道松露蒜泥蛋黃醬一樣把它浸進去，然後你就有一塊巧克力了
milkshake to drink with it so that's like yeah right
奶昔和它一起喝是的，對
right something like that ultra deluxe
對的就是那種超豪華的東西
they're back two doors oh no pt
他們回到了兩扇門哦不pt
oh no that's just part two whenever i see pt it gets me excited i just
哦，不，那隻是第二部分，每當我看到pt讓我興奮我只是
reminded remember [ __ ] um silent hill pt
提醒記住他媽的嗯寂靜嶺pt
e let's say e4 e
e 比方說 e4e
e what does that mean
e這意味著什麼
e
click to add speaker nuts this presentation is terrible
單擊以添加揚聲器螺母這個演示文稿很糟糕
i don't even see the projector where's the projector unless it's one of those
我什至看不到投影儀在哪裡投影機，除非它是其中之一
screens that doesn't have a projector it's just like oh yeah it isn't okay
沒有投影儀的屏幕就像哦，是的，這不好
[Music] i just shows up on it
[音樂]我只是出現在上面
e now to be clear i haven't quite nailed down what exactly the stanley parable 2
現在要明確一點，我還沒有完全確定到底斯坦利寓言2
is going to be but let's take a look at some of the features i've been
將是，但讓我們來看看我的一些功能
developing for it i think that if i can loosely organize a
為它開發我想如果我能鬆散地組織一個
handful of interesting concepts that surely the game will sort of naturally
一些有趣的概念遊戲肯定會很自然
spring up around them it'll all work it took the red marker with me
在他們周圍湧現，一切都會好起來的帶著我的紅色記號筆
[Laughter] magic than anything scientific or
[笑聲]魔法勝過任何科學或
logical really oh i didn't even pay attention to what
真的合乎邏輯哦，我什至沒有註意什麼
you were saying what the [ __ ] why is this
你在說這他媽是什麼原因這個
you know the way they draw the two is like the way i feel like i drew
你知道他們畫這兩個的方式是就像我畫的那樣
[ __ ] random letters and numbers when i was in like elementary school
他媽的隨機字母和數字我就像小學一樣
damn what a baller move who took the red marker me
該死的拿紅球的球員動作標記我
it was me
那是我
that's like albon knox energy what's this the roman numeral 2 every
這就像阿爾本諾克斯能量這是什麼羅馬數字 2 每
pause button is a roman numeral too i i i i guess right kind of this way to
暫停按鈕也是羅馬數字我我我想這種方式是正確的
a show floor
展示廳
this looks so ominous though i want to go down the ominous hallway
這看起來很不祥，雖然我想沿著不祥的走廊走下去
like which way would you want to go down this creepy ass hallway or over
比如你想走哪條路沿著這個令人毛骨悚然的走廊或以上
here into the expo hall this looks like more of my kind of vibes
這裡進入博覽館這看起來更像是我的那種感覺
can i crouch in there no no it really doesn't let me it just
我可以蹲在那裡嗎不，它真的不允許我這樣做
blocks me off
阻止我
but i want to see what's down the creepy hallway
但我想看看這令人毛骨悚然門廳
it's my horror instincts kicking in
這是我的恐怖本能
the bus is here
公共汽車到了
man i haven't been to an expo or con in a while
伙計，我沒去過博覽會或騙局一會兒
maybe someday
也許有一天
here we are go on try out some of the new features
在這裡我們繼續嘗試一些新的功能
the button that says the name of the player that is playing the game
顯示名稱的按鈕正在玩遊戲的玩家
hear your name in the game
在遊戲中聽到你的名字
for the stanley parable 2 i asked myself what do players really want and of
對於斯坦利寓言 2 我問自己玩家真正想要什麼？
course the first too big too small just right individually recognized and
當然第一個太大太小只是權利單獨承認和
validated as people so with that in mind my first addition
驗證為人所以考慮到這一點，我的第一個補充
to the game is this button which speaks the name of the person playing the game
對遊戲來說，這個按鈕會說話玩遊戲的人的名字
isn't that wonderful
是不是很美妙
what i should have clarified right now the button only says the name jim but of
我現在應該澄清的按鈕只說名字吉姆，但
course in the final game this button will say your name whatever name that is
當然在最後的遊戲這個按鈕會說出你的名字
here let's have you role players gym to really simulate the full experience i'm
在這裡，讓我們讓你的角色球員健身房真正模擬我的完整體驗
not a gem just play along okay sorry it's all the gems out there
不是寶石只是一起玩好吧，對不起，那裡都是寶石
my bad but okay here we go let's take a deep breath jim in your mind forget
我的不好，但好吧，我們走吧，讓我們來深呼吸吉姆在你的腦海中忘記
whoever you are and simply become a person named jim
無論你是誰，只要成為一個叫吉姆的人
i want you to imagine yourself living as jim sleeping and wakings oh hell no i'm
我想讓你想像自己的生活吉姆睡覺和醒來哦，天哪，我不是
not i'm not being i'm not waking up as a gym
不是我不是我不是醒來健身房
seizing all of the world's [ __ ] that's it
抓住世界上所有的他媽的而已
and as jim watching your dreams crumble into dust
吉姆看著你的夢想破滅化為塵埃
do you feel it deeply are you really truly gym right now if so then please
你是否深深地感覺到你真的是真正的健身房現在如果是的話那麼請
step forward and press the button and just have my have my dreams crumble like
向前走並按下按鈕讓我的夢想像崩潰一樣
jim oh i'm sorry it's all the gyms out there your dreams are crumbling right
吉姆，哦，對不起，所有的體育館都出去了那裡你的夢想正在搖搖欲墜
now yes you'll see what a thrill what a rush
現在是的，你會看到多麼激動多麼匆忙
that was you the button that was me
那是你那個是我的按鈕
oh it's you no it's not i'm not jim i want to hear
哦，是你不，我不是吉姆，我想听
to say gym it again even harder the second time if
說健身房如果第二次更難
this were the only new feature in the stanley parable 2 it would still be
這是唯一的新功能斯坦利寓言 2 它仍然是
worth the money let's take a break from the gym button i'm too emotionally
物有所值，讓我們休息一下健身房按鈕 我太情緒化了
drained from all of this personal validation
從所有這些個人的驗證
he's acting like it's uh i'm hitting his g spot you know it's like when i press
他表現得好像是我在打他g 發現你知道就像我按下
the button he's like oh ah it's time for f oh there cowboy
他喜歡的按鈕哦啊，該是牛仔的時候了
sometimes the person can be too much jim i'm putting the gym button away
有時這個人可能太過分了吉姆我把健身按鈕放在一邊
otherwise soon i'll start to make all sense of who you actually are no
否則很快我就會開始做所有的感覺你實際上不是誰
he took away my button he really said he really confiscated
他拿走了我的鈕扣他真的說他真的沒收了
from me he said no more it's gone now you don't have any more
他不再對我說現在你沒有了
gym button rights okay i really like the button though maybe i
健身房按鈕權利好我真的很喜歡這個按鈕雖然也許我
am jim i am now jim jimmy neutron i'm jimmy neutron
我是吉姆 我現在是吉姆吉米中子 我是吉米中子
i just got to get a big brain and a friend named carl weiser
我只是得有一個大腦袋和一個叫卡爾韋瑟的朋友
he was attracted to my mom right that's how that's how the show
他被我媽媽吸引了對 就是這樣 節目就是這樣
went i think you
我想去了你
named jim to play the stanley parable too that would actually save me the work
命名吉姆扮演斯坦利寓言這實際上也可以節省我的工作
of finishing this feature
完成這個功能
infinite holes oh infinite holes oh my god that sounds like an amazing
無限洞哦無限洞哦，我的上帝，這聽起來很神奇
merchandise idea i want infinite holes
商品理念我想要無限的洞
for life epilogue oh wait hold on before i go in
終生結語哦，等我進去之前等一下
there i'm gonna look around here merch oh they even have a merch stand
我要去看看這裡的商品哦，他們甚至有一個商品攤位
there's a qr code up there what the heck okay
上面有一個二維碼 什麼鬼好的
free merch the reassurance bucket please no screenshots
免費商品的安心桶請不要截圖
uh hold on i want to take a look what's the reassurance bucket hello
呃等等我想看看是什麼安心桶你好
a common complaint of the stanley parable was that it was confusing and
斯坦利的共同抱怨比喻令人困惑，
paradoxical that it engendered a chaotic sense of reckless despair in those who
矛盾的是，它造成了混亂那些人的魯莽絕望感
bought it well i'm happy to say that after much
買的不錯我很高興地這麼說
consideration i've engineered a clever solution to this fundamental problem
考慮到我設計了一個聰明的解決這個基本問題
with the game it's the stanley parable reassurance
隨著遊戲這是斯坦利寓言的保證
bucket is it my [ __ ] bucket anytime you're holding the bucket a sense of
桶是我的精液桶嗎你拿著桶的感覺
calm and ease will fill your mind and your heart it's true
平靜和輕鬆會充滿你的思想和你的心是真的
as long as you hold on to the bucket the many disorienting contradictions of the
只要你抓住水桶許多令人迷惑的矛盾
stanley parable will feel perfectly normal and perhaps even comforting
斯坦利寓言會感覺完美正常，甚至可能令人欣慰
you may even come to long for the gentle embracing
你甚至會渴望溫柔擁抱
cognitive dissonance while the bucket is in your arms and to be honest it's a
桶時認知失調在你的懷裡，老實說，這是一個
much more convenient i can't grab the bucket me than actually redesigning the
方便多了我抓不到比實際重新設計
game to be less uncomfortable can you imagine what a pain in the ass that
遊戲能少點不舒服嗎想像一下那是多麼痛苦
would be yes the bucket is the perfect solution come on and give it a try the
是的，水桶是完美的解決方案來試試看
chum bucket you got the chum bucket in the [ __ ] bucket
密友桶 你有密友桶暨桶
i just [Laughter]
我只是[笑聲]
can you feel it the glow of comfort even in the face of
你能感覺到嗎即使在面對
crushing despair must already be sweeping through your body anymore
壓倒性的絕望一定已經再掃過你的身體
can i say that i do believe the bucket lends you an air of charisma as well
我能說我相信水桶嗎也給你一種魅力
it's just a bucket just holding it has made you the slightest bit more
它只是一個拿著它的桶讓你多一點
attractive as a person ah the benefits of the bucket seem to go
有吸引力的人啊桶的好處似乎去了
on and on don't they what all this and more awaits you in the stanley parable
他們不就是這一切嗎？斯坦利寓言中還有更多等著你
too he laughed at me he was like
也他笑我他就像
you fell for my trap jim
你愛上了我的陷阱吉姆
damn okay now i have a bucket i can't get rid of the bucket now can i can i
該死的好吧，現在我有一個桶，我不能現在擺脫水桶我可以嗎
put the bucket back is this stuck with me
把桶放回去這是我的問題嗎
no oh my god the bucket is stuck with me
不哦，天哪，水桶卡在我身上
damn it okay well
該死的還好
what's wrong what do i name the bucket
怎麼了，我給桶起什麼名字
uh you know i think um
呃你知道我想嗯
[Music] i'm gonna name you
[音樂]我要給你起名字
i'm gonna go i'm gonna name you uh
我要去吧，我要給你取名
um um
嗯嗯
um uh
嗯呃
uh uh on onion yeah i'm gonna name you onion your
呃呃洋蔥是的，我要叫你洋蔥
name's onion does anyone give out awards for most enjoyable bucket in a video
名字的洋蔥有人發獎嗎視頻中最有趣的水桶
game that really should be an award if it
遊戲如果它真的應該是一個獎項
isn't already
還沒有
free new and easy achievement i love onions onions are great
我喜歡免費的新的和容易的成就洋蔥 洋蔥很棒
don't you guys like onions i love onion soup i love onion zip i love ah fried
你們不喜歡洋蔥嗎？我喜歡洋蔥湯我愛洋蔥拉鍊我愛啊油炸
onion i love onion rings i love caramelized onions i love
洋蔥 我愛洋蔥圈我喜歡我喜歡的焦糖洋蔥
grilled onions
烤洋蔥
well we'll figure that out later
好吧，我們稍後會解決的
uh okay maybe i shouldn't go here yeah and
呃好吧也許我不應該去這裡是的
look at everything else right dude onions are pog onions are
看看其他的對了，洋蔥是洋蔥
[ __ ] great
他媽的太棒了
the jump circle the infinite holes i want to see this infinite hole you're
跳躍圈無限洞我想看看你是這個無限的洞
talking about more holes
談論更多孔
yeah i'm really dude i'm really i'm just stuck with this bucket by the way
是的，我真的是伙計，我真的，我只是順便卡在這個桶上
okay i'll be honest i haven't yet decided on this one i think that in the
好吧，老實說我還沒有決定了這個，我認為在
new version the office could use a bit of decoration like balloons but i
新版本辦公室可以用一點像氣球一樣的裝飾，但我
undecided on get well someday and happy 12th birthday which would you go with
遲遲未定，總有一天會好起來，開心起來12歲生日你會和哪個一起去
get well someday or happy 12th birthday stephanie's
總有一天會好起來，或者 12 歲生日快樂斯蒂芬妮的
wait what is this for huh get well sunday heart
等等這是什麼啊週日心臟好起來
wait i like this one
等等我喜歡這個
i kind of like this one
我有點喜歡這個
happy 12th birthday stephanie what the [ __ ] who's my stephanie's
斯蒂芬妮 12 歲生日快樂他媽的誰是我斯蒂芬妮的
step bro yeah well someday
步兄弟是的，總有一天
i like i like the passive aggressiveness about this one right because you can
我喜歡我喜歡被動的攻擊性關於這一點，因為你可以
take it you can take it as a bad contact so you also like taking a good way so
接受它，您可以將其視為不良接觸所以你也喜歡走好路so
i'll do that sometimes when you solicit another person's opinion it makes you
我有時會在你招攬的時候這樣做另一個人的意見它讓你
realize that you knew which one you actually really wanted all along happy
意識到你知道你是誰其實真的很想一直開心
12th birthday step nice it is what
12歲生日步驟很好，這是什麼
oh okay or actually maybe i should have gone with no no i've
哦，好吧或者實際上也許我應該離開，不，不，我已經
made my decision we're moving on come now you've already made your choice it's
做出了我的決定，我們繼續前進現在你已經做出了選擇
true that you chose badly that we all have to move on from our mistakes
真的，你選錯了，我們都必須從我們的錯誤中繼續前進
he he gave me the the choice to pick one
他他讓我選擇一個
and then he said no you're wrong
然後他說不，你錯了
he said i was wrong wow okay
他說我錯了哇好的
the illusion of choice
選擇的錯覺
time and depth oh no this is too big brain for me sorry
時間和深度哦，不，這對我來說太大了，對不起
i don't understand infinity whole entrance
我不明白無窮大整個入口
more holes more holes it just keeps going more
更多孔更多的洞它只會繼續更多
there's more there's a lot of holes are there also plot holes
還有很多洞是否也有情節漏洞
as well stanley here's an idea that i'm truly fond of it's never been done
斯坦利還有一個想法，我是真正喜歡它從未做過
before in a video game this is in fact a hole that you can fall down forever
在電子遊戲之前，這實際上是你可以永遠掉下去的洞
that's right infinite falling you can fall until the end of time if you like a
沒錯，你可以無限下落如果你喜歡，直到時間的盡頭
stunning leap forward for video games is a medium
視頻遊戲的驚人飛躍是一種媒介
infinite hole oh that's a deep hole
無限洞哦，那是個深洞
that's a really deep hole there
那是一個非常深的洞
do we do you guys want to go inside the hole
你們想進去嗎洞
do we want to go inside the hole
我們想進入洞內嗎
it's really something to jump inside the hole
這真的是跳進去的東西洞
what if it's just a drawing of a hole it's not really a hole
如果它只是一個洞的圖紙怎麼辦這不是一個真正的洞
oh it's a hole
哦，這是一個洞
you see isn't it wonderful one of my more ingenious concoctions if i do say
你看這不是我的精彩之一嗎如果我說更巧妙的混合物
oh my god now then since you've gotten to see the infinite hole you can press
哦，我的上帝，既然你得到了看到你可以按下的無限洞
the teleport button to pop back up to the top what's that button
要彈回的傳送按鈕頂部那個按鈕是什麼
i'll press g to return to the surface what if i just wanna now i don't mean to
我會按g返回水面如果我只想現在我不想
be a bummer but i do recommend you use the teleport button to go back to the
是一個無賴，但我建議你使用傳送按鈕返回
top why maybe do it on the sooner rather than later spectrum of things you said
頂部 為什麼可能越早越好比你說的後來的事情譜
it was an endless hole right so i should be fine right
這是一個無盡的洞，所以我應該沒事吧
right okay stanley i don't know quite how to
正確的好吧，斯坦利，我不知道該怎麼做
say this tactfully but it's possible that i slightly exaggerated the infinite
委婉地說，但這是可能的我稍微誇大了無限
nature of the hole is it a very very deep hole to be
洞的性質這是一個非常非常深的洞嗎
certain it is it's an extremely deep
肯定是這是一個非常深的
i don't want anyone to say that it isn't an astonishingly deep hole it is is it
我不想讓任何人說它不是這是一個驚人的深洞
infinite well that sort of depends on your
無窮那取決於你的
definition of infinity from one perspective the infinite is merely
從一定義無窮大透視無限只是
philosophical in nature it's more of a oh okay well good for you you found the
本質上是哲學的，它更像是哦，好吧，對你有好處，你找到了
bottom where i didn't die you found me out stanley i'm a liar and cheat and
在我沒有死的底部你找到了我出 stanley 我是個騙子
you're so clever look i think the issue here is just that you're unusually
你太聰明了，我覺得這個問題這只是你不尋常
fascinated by falling what normal person actually wants to
沉迷於墜落正常人實際上想要什麼
fall infinitely i figured the hurl was as deep as anyone would actually need
無限墜落我想投擲是任何人實際需要的深度
don't you put this on me maybe you're the problem
你不把這個放在我身上也許你是問題
i didn't even do anything there he he got so upset at me for nothing i just
我什至什麼都沒做他他無緣無故生我的氣，我只是
want to fall in the hole why didn't we just put all this i have a
想掉進洞裡為什麼我們不把這一切都放在我有一個
need to fill holes sometimes you just want to go down the
需要補洞有時你只是想往下走
hole explore the hole see what's down the hole find out what's at the end of
洞 探索洞 看看有什麼洞找出盡頭是什麼
the hole button to warp up to the top of the hole
洞按鈕翹曲到孔的頂部
and we can move on i'll just be up here when you're ready
我們可以繼續前進 我會在這裡當你準備好
no i'm sitting down here i'm sitting at the bottom of the well with my bucket in
不，我坐在這裡，我坐在井底有我的桶
this hole now you can't tell me what to do
這個洞現在你不能告訴我要做什麼做
[Music] yup just me and my bucket
[音樂]是的，只有我和我的水桶
me and my bucket onion his name's onion by the way my bucket's name onion
我和我的桶洋蔥 他的名字叫洋蔥順便說一下我的桶的名字洋蔥
in this hole by myself like what
在這個洞裡自己喜歡什麼
300 000 feet down below surviving here my name's my name is jim apparently
300 000 英尺以下的地方倖存下來我的名字是我的名字顯然是吉姆
and i have a bucket and i'm stuck in a hole
我有一個桶我被困在一個洞裡
hell what do you mean bratty
地獄你是什​​麼意思
damn i'm at the i'm at the far bottom of this [ __ ] dude
該死的我在我在最底層這個混蛋
that's kind of ironic don't you think
這有點諷刺你不覺得嗎
look at the bottom of the hole
看孔底
huh huh
呵呵呵呵
you know i don't like that
你知道我不喜歡那樣
i don't like that at all we're gonna we're gonna get the [ __ ] out
我一點也不喜歡我們要我們要他媽的出去
of here i i great now i'm very excited to show you even more of my ideas for
在這裡，我很棒，現在我很興奮向您展示我的更多想法
the sequel oh for heaven
續集哦，為了天堂
i was right the problem is you it's not me the
我是對的問題是你不是我
problem is that you like holes too much not normal
問題是你太喜歡洞了不正常
would have said yep that's an infinite hole right there goes on forever till
會說是的，那是無限的洞就在那里永遠持續到
the end of time don't need to see it all but not you oh no no no no you have a
時間的盡頭不需要看到這一切但不是你哦不不不不你有
weird sort of oh
奇怪的那種哦
did the hole seem even shorter to you this time no help it feel like you spent
你覺得這個洞更短了嗎這次沒有幫助，感覺就像你花了
a little less time in there than you did before he knows man he [ __ ] knows i
在那裡的時間比你少一點在他知道男人之前他他媽的就知道我
like holes too much
太喜歡洞了
that's okay down he got me i mean admittedly i didn't make an infinite
沒關係，他抓住了我，我的意思是誠然，我沒有製造無限
hole but i didn't think it was that not infinite well i suppose once again
洞，但我不認為那不是我想再一次無限好
there's nothing to do here if you decide you've had enough of the hole you can
如果你決定，這裡無事可做你已經受夠了你可以的洞
hit the teleport button and come join me up i want more hole give me more hole
按下傳送按鈕來加入我我想要更多的洞給我更多的洞
had enough i'm positively thrilled gosh how could i have guessed you're back in
受夠了，我非常激動，天哪我怎麼會猜到你回來了
the hole if this starts to become a thing where
洞如果這開始成為一件事情
it's so small okay yeah wait why is this whole so small now
它是如此之小，好吧是的，等等，為什麼這整個現在這麼小
extremely certain that the whole is not only not infinite but that it's growing
非常確定整體不是不僅不是無限的，而且還在增長
steadily less and less infinite why are you suspecting what i'm starting to hit
越來越少 無限 為什麼你懷疑我開始打什麼
the point where it's no longer feasible to call the hole infinitely deep even by
不再可行的地步甚至將洞稱為無限深
the lacks overall standards for accountability and marketing what's
缺乏整體標準問責制和營銷是什麼
going on here stanley i have no explanation for the i
在這裡進行stanley 我對我沒有任何解釋
want to keep falling here let's try something let's pop back
想繼續跌倒在這裡讓我們嘗試一些讓我們彈回來
up to the top and we'll see if it gets any shorter
到頂部，我們會看看它是否得到任何更短的
well there's sure game of my life how is this still
肯定有我生命中的遊戲怎麼還是這樣
appealing to you i know you're obsessed with holes but at
吸引你我知道你對洞很著迷，但在
this depth i just can't see this scratching the itch
這個深度我只是看不到這個抓癢
oh who am i to judge
哦我是誰來評判
you just do whatever it is you're here to do and hit the teleport button when
你只是做任何事情你在這裡做並按下傳送按鈕時
you're ready to move on press g to return to a surface why can't
你準備好繼續前進了按 g 返回表面 為什麼不能
i just jump up
我只是跳起來
hmm is the um
唔是嗯
teleport button not working you better
傳送按鈕不起作用你更好
well i mean i really don't have an explanation it
我的意思是我真的沒有解釋
was working just a moment ago
剛才還在工作
i'm stuck i'm actually stuck
我被困住了我實際上被困住了
no there is one thing i can do to fix this
不，我可以做一件事來解決這個
i'm out goodbye stanley you couldn't bear to be away from the hole and now
我出去了再見斯坦利你不能忍受著遠離這個洞，現在
you'll get more time with it than you could ever have asked for it's a win for
你會得到比你更多的時間本來可以要求這是一場胜利
everyone you get to be with the whole i get to do literally anything else
你能和整個我在一起的每個人開始做任何其他事情
take care stanley i hope you in the hole have a wonderful rest of eternity
保重斯坦利，我希望你在洞裡享受美好的永恆
together he left oh my god he [ __ ] left
他一起離開哦，我的上帝，他他媽的離開了
he's like since you like that hole so much how long do you just stay with it
他就像因為你喜歡那個洞所以你能堅持多久
goodbye i'm gonna go do something else wow
再見，我要去干點別的事哇
that's kind of sad
這有點難過
it feels kind of like a you know like a metaphor
感覺有點像你知道的隱喻
right it's kind of like a metaphor in a way
正確的這在某種程度上有點像一個隱喻
also the creepy music i'm not liking it somebody come inside
還有令人毛骨悚然的音樂我不喜歡有人進來
can you close the door can you close the door
你能關上門嗎你能關上門嗎
maybe oh the hole
也許哦洞
oh my god the hole it's growing
哦，我的上帝，它正在增長的洞
oh my god it's getting deeper oh yeah oh yeah
天啊，越來越深了哦對哦對
let's go let's go
我們走吧我們走吧
wait where am i going though where the [ __ ] am i going
等等我要去哪裡雖然在哪裡他媽的我要去嗎
press f to change my perspective [Music]
按 f 改變我的觀點[音樂]
what [Music]
什麼[音樂]
why is this so dramatic why the [ __ ] is this so dramatic for
為什麼這麼戲劇化為什麼這他媽的如此戲劇化
huh
呵呵
press g to change my perception
按 g 改變我的看法
[Music] so
[音樂]所以
[Music]
[音樂]
[Music] my head stronger now you're no longer
[音樂]我的頭更強壯了，現在你不再
using out this space [Music]
利用這個空間[音樂]
i press h to change my reality
我按 h 改變我的現實
[Music] [Laughter]
[音樂][笑聲]
[Music]
[音樂]
wait i kind of like this one
等等，我有點喜歡這個
what is happening what this sounds so [ __ ] creepy
發生了什麼這聽起來如此他媽的令人毛骨悚然
[Music]
[音樂]
[Music] i i'm oh that's kind of cute
[音樂]我是哦，這有點可愛
i i'm really i'm really lost y'all i'm really [ __ ] lost i don't know what's
我真的我真的迷路了你們都是我真他媽的迷路了，我不知道是什麼
happening i don't know how to get out can i get out please can you let me out
發生了我不知道怎麼出去我能出去嗎？你能不能讓我出去
of the hole please let me let me out of the [ __ ]
洞的請讓我讓我離開他媽的
hole i want out of the hole now
我現在想出洞
let me out let me
讓我出去讓我來
out stanley oh oh good you're awake it seems you had sort of dozed off there
出來 stanley 哦 哦 好 你醒了看來你在那裡打瞌睡了
drifting away into dreamland but we can't have that stanley because this
飄進夢鄉，但我們不能有那個斯坦利，因為這個
hole is just so darn fascinating that i want you to be wide awake for every
洞太迷人了，我希望你每時每刻都保持清醒
second of it you don't want to miss a single moment oh my god how about if i
第二個你不想錯過單片刻哦，我的上帝，如果我怎麼樣
just pop in from time to time and wake you up to keep you really truly focused
只是不時彈出並醒來你起來讓你真正真正專注
on the whole from the looks of things you and i will
總體上從你我會的事情來看
have many many years here in this hole and i'm looking forward to all of them
在這個洞裡有很多年我很期待他們所有人
stay alert stanley i'll be back
保持警惕，斯坦利，我會回來的
no come back i don't want to be in the hole anymore i don't wanna be in the
不回來我不想在洞了，我不想在
hole oh no oh no it's gonna happen again guys
洞哦不哦不這會再次發生伙計們
guys it's happening again oh unless
伙計們，這又發生了哦，除非
unless
除非
oh oh
哦哦
brought me back here we are oh go on [ __ ] me
帶我回來我們在這裡哦，繼續操我
i have my bucket back this is this bucket just stuck with me
我有我的桶回來了這是這個桶剛剛卡在我身上
from now on like i can't i can't escape from them the bucket's just like it's
從現在開始就像我不能我不能逃脫從他們那裡桶就像它一樣
you guys you know what i feel like the bucket can be you guys i'm holding you
你們知道我的感受水桶可以是你們，我抱著你們
all in my arms right now you are the bucket
現在都在我的懷裡你是桶
you are my bucket this empty little bucket that's waiting
你是我的水桶這個等待的空小桶
to get like i don't know i'm gonna put you on my head that toss
變得像我不知道我要把你放在我的頭上那折騰
you across the room
你穿過房間
that's new what else is new
那是新的還有什麼是新的
collectibles free new easy achievement can't believe
收藏品免費 新 輕鬆 成就 不敢相信
that's i can't believe it's that simple i can't believe it's that simple
那是我不敢相信它這麼簡單我不敢相信就這麼簡單
free achievement get yours right now pull the lever receive your new
免費成就 立即獲得拉動槓桿接收你的新
achievement no more steps it just works get yours right now free achievement
成就沒有更多的步驟它只是工作立即獲得您的免費成就
okay sure what's with you now here's something special you remember that
好吧，確定你現在怎麼樣了一些特別的東西你記得
broken test achievement that got left in the game on accident well i'm developing
留下的殘破的測試成績我正在開發的意外遊戲
a technology to simply give you the achievement yes you see you'll come to
一種技術，簡單地為您提供成就是的，你看你會來的
this lever and when you can't okay perhaps i should have clarified
這個槓桿，當你不能好吧，也許我應該澄清一下
this is technology that will exist right now the achievement is still fully
這是正確存在的技術現在成就還完全
broken is it broken oh it's better i guarantee it will be
壞了是不是壞了哦，我保證會更好
fixed in the sequel to at least satisfy the hordes of ravenous fans all over the
固定在續集中至少滿足成群結隊的狂熱粉絲遍布各地
world who have been uproariously demanding this feature gamers we hear
曾經鬧得沸沸揚揚的世界我們聽到的要求這個功能的遊戲玩家
you and i promise it will happen
你和我保證它會發生
what if i just press it enough times right
如果我按足夠多次怎麼辦正確的
you think i'll you think you'll come by
你認為我會 你認為你會過來
gamers
遊戲玩家
[ __ ] damn it
他媽的該死的
you said it was gonna be a free achievement you lied it's not free
你說這將是免費的你撒謊的成就不是免費的
achievement i mean maybe it is i just have to do it
成就我的意思是也許是我必須這樣做
properly um
適當地嗯
there has to be something here come on come on show me the goods show me the
這裡一定有什麼東西來吧來給我看看貨物給我看看
show me the goodies show me the goodies there has to be something around here i
給我看好吃的 給我看看好吃的這裡一定有什麼東西我
want me inside i'm hungry i'm hungry for it
想要我進去 我餓了 我很餓它
damn it [ __ ] okay
該死的好的
i'm gonna get out now screw it man i'll need you and your stinky little
我要出去了需要你和你的臭小子
achievement anyways what else what other exhibits haven't we
反正成就還有什麼其他展品我們沒有
seen yet stinky little achievements new content
還沒見過臭小成就新內容
the jump circle what this is the same thing let's bring the jump circle back
跳圈這是一樣的事情讓我們把跳躍圈帶回來
for stanley parable 2 as well it's oh wait
對於斯坦利寓言 2 也是哦等待
you already spent all your jumps the first time we saw the jump sir give me
你已經用盡了所有的跳躍我們第一次看到跳躍先生給我
more jumps hmm oh well i suppose it can just be a nice
更多的跳躍嗯嗯嗯我想它可能只是一個不錯的
decorative piece then or yeah you could be a nice person and give me more jumps
裝飾件然後或者是的，你可以做個好人，給我更多的跳躍
right the jump circle
正確的跳躍圈
no it doesn't want to give me more jumps away
不，它不想給我更多的跳躍離開
[Music] no jumping yeah
[音樂]不跳是的
okay is this is there anything else
好的這是還有別的嗎
of all collectibles there's collectibles up
其中收藏品有收藏品了
here
這裡
can you find them can you find them can you find them can you find them collect
你能找到他們嗎 你能找到他們嗎你找到他們你能找到他們收集嗎
them all why does this sound so ominous ah
商場為什麼聽起來那麼不祥啊
collectibles now it's a real video game in the
收藏品現在它是一個真正的視頻遊戲
stanley parable 2 you'll run around gathering up these miniature stanley
斯坦利寓言2你會跑來跑去收集這些微型斯坦利
figurines so thank you thank you for that is that there will be no reward for
小雕像所以謝謝你謝謝你也就是說，不會有任何獎勵
collecting all of them i don't want to stifle the intrinsic joy of watching a
收集所有我不想扼殺觀看的內在樂趣
number go up you simply collect all of them and then you move the hell on with
數字上升你只需收集所有他們然後你繼續前進
your unremarkable life ah
你平凡的一生啊
zero out of six that's one out of six wait
六分之一是六分之一等待
there's five more collect them all
還有五個把它們都收集起來
it's not like pokemon this doesn't feel like pokemon the worst when you collect
這不像口袋妖怪，這沒有感覺收集時最喜歡口袋妖怪
everything in a video game and then they give you a big fancy reward for it
電子遊戲中的一切，然後他們給你一個花哨的大獎勵
absolutely tragic
絕對悲劇
settings world champion what
設置世界冠軍什麼
ah ah
啊啊
until i go down here over here wait there's something right there let me
直到我下到這裡等那裡有東西讓我
check that out
檢查出
no doesn't let me go through that area what the [ __ ] was it blocked off for
不，不讓我穿過那個區域他媽的是為了什麼而被封鎖的
hold on then this goes somewhere else
堅持，稍等然後這個去別的地方
oh that that drops off or does it
哦，那掉下來了或者做
kind of looks cool though i like this i need a little area have you seen
雖然我喜歡這個，但看起來很酷我需要一個小地方你看到了嗎
everything you wanted to ready to move on now
你想要的一切都準備好了現在開始
no no wait what about the epilogue
不等一下結尾呢
is there did i see everything i wanted to is this like the way to the next area
我有沒有看到我想要的一切to 是這樣去下一個區域的路嗎
i don't know hold on let me go back
我不知道等我回去
by the way can you guys hear this can you guys hear this from my side
順便說一句，你們能聽到這個嗎你們從我身邊聽到這個
uh okay hold on hold on okay i'm gonna talk and then like
呃，好吧，等等，好吧，我會的說話然後喜歡
do this like a little bit yeah my chair is
做這個有點像，是的，我的椅子是
squeaky now i don't know what happened do you guys know how to like
吱吱，現在我不知道發生了什麼你們知道怎麼喜歡嗎
um what's it do you know how to like not make it squeaky anymore because this is
嗯，你知道怎麼不喜歡嗎？讓它不再吱吱作響，因為這是
kind of a new chair like i got like a few months ago but now it's already like
一種像我一樣的新椅子幾個月前，但現在已經像
you know squeak squeak squeaking a bit i don't know how to fix it well
你知道吱吱吱吱有點不知道怎麼修好
not like a few months it's been like half a year
不像幾個月它就像半年
that's he's oil really that's really i had to actually have to use oil for it
那是他的油真的那真的是我實際上不得不為此使用石油
does it help lube that's used lube
有幫助嗎用過的潤滑油
okay i mean
好的我的意思是
does any kind of oil work or do i have to like get a
有什麼油可以用嗎？或者我有嗎喜歡得到一個
get a specific type of oil
獲得特定類型的油
okay all right gotcha settings world champion i can't go
好的，好的，明白了設置世界冠軍我不能去
inside here i got baited what
在這裡我被誘餌了什麼
that's new
那是新的
okay just oil got it got it i'll find some kind of
好吧，只是油明白了，我會找到一些
chair oil i guess
我猜椅子油
right
正確的
if i just get um if i just get like canola oil or
如果我得到嗯如果我喜歡菜籽油或
sunflower oil and put it in there but that work too is
葵花籽油並把它放在那裡，但這項工作也是
that fine is that safe i don't know
那很好是不是很安全我不知道
also leave the screws loose oh no i don't want to fall out my chair please
也讓螺絲鬆動哦不我不想從椅子上掉下來
what no no no what do you mean no oh wow i know
什麼 不 不 不 你是什麼意思 不哦，哇，我知道了
wd40 what is that is that the oil that i have to use
wd40 那是什麼那是我必須使用的油嗎
okay okay okay okay got it got it got it sorry sorry sorry naruto i understand
好的 好的 好的 好的 明白了 明白了對不起對不起對不起火影忍者我明白了
though my bad
儘管我的錯
no screenshots why is this saying no screenshots for
沒有截圖為什麼這說不截圖
stanley oh what do you think do you like all of the new features this is okay i
斯坦利哦，你覺得你喜歡什麼所有的新功能這沒關係我
like the whole clear yet how exactly these features will come together as one
喜歡整體清晰但究竟如何這些功能將合二為一
the whole is the best part of video game but i can feel it in my soul it's going
整體是電子遊戲中最好的部分但我能在我的靈魂中感覺到它正在發生
to work there's definitely a good game in there somewhere say let's do an
上班肯定有好遊戲在那裡某處說讓我們做一個
experiment i'll arrange these new features together and we'll see whether
實驗我會安排這些新的功能在一起，我們將看看是否
or not it coheres into a meaningful gameplay experience
或不凝聚成一個有意義的遊戲體驗
[Music] okay
[音樂]好的
are you ready here it is i give you
你準備好了嗎我給你
the stanley parable two [Music]
斯坦利寓言二[音樂]
what that's it
什麼而已
um well um i mean there's potential here
嗯嗯，我的意思是這裡有潛力
right it's sort of okay never mind hold on let me do a different
對，沒關係，沒關係等等，讓我做一個不同的
arrangement okay yes yes this is much better i feel
安排好的，是的，我覺得這好多了
good here we go i want i want a new hole
好的我們走吧，我想要一個新洞
oh
哦
wait the skip button oh no that's a gym button this isn't a coherent video game
等待跳過按鈕哦不，那是健身房按鈕，這不是一個連貫的視頻遊戲
at all it's a lot of gags and i do very much enjoy creating gags
根本就是很多噱頭我非常喜歡製作噱頭
but they don't add up to anything i wanted more than anything to create a
但它們不加起來我最想創造一個
sequel that would capture all the magic of the first game i wanted fans to love
續集將捕捉所有魔力我希望粉絲喜歡的第一場比賽
it no matter how good these gags are they wouldn't stand on their own they
不管這些噱頭有多好他們不會獨自站立
would need the structure in the gameplay of the original
需要遊戲中的結構原來的
wait maybe that's it
等待也許就是這樣
i can take the original stanley parable uh-huh
我可以接受最初的斯坦利寓言嗯
insert a few of my new features into it peacefully of course
將我的一些新功能插入其中當然是和平的
with care for the vision and integrity of the original game
關注遠見和誠信原始遊戲的
would it possibly work i suppose it could but it would need a
它可能有用嗎我想它可以，但它需要一個
really really tremendous title screen a title screen that says with bold and
真的真的很棒的標題畫面標題屏幕以粗體顯示
uncompromising conviction this is the stanley parable too
堅定不移的信念這也是斯坦利的寓言
let me see if i can whip something up [Music]
讓我看看我能不能做點什麼[音樂]
perfect go ahead
完美的前進
take a look
看一看
wow he actually did it
哇，他真的做到了
the settings even look better too
設置甚至看起來也更好
that's crazy okay
太瘋狂了好的
i click anything anything else everything's red
我點擊任何東西其他的一切都是紅色的
are we sure this isn't gonna be a horror game
我們確定這不會是一個恐怖遊戲
this is the story of a man named stanley no
這是一個叫斯坦利的人的故事不
stanley work oh no
斯坦利工作哦不
[Music]
[音樂]
it looks the exact same i don't want the i don't want the
看起來一模一樣我不想要我不想要
stephanie's [ __ ] uh balloons were gone what could it mean
斯蒂芬妮他媽的呃氣球消失了是什麼意思
so don't wanted to go to the meeting room perhaps he had simply missed a memo
所以不想去開會房間也許他只是錯過了一個備忘錄
i'm stuck i'm stuck in an endless loop i'm gonna go crazy man you felt the
我被困住了，我陷入了無限循環我要瘋了，你感覺到了
bucket calling to him begging him to pick it up why why was he not doing it
水桶呼喚他求他拿起它為什麼他不這樣做
stanley felt the bucket calling to him do i pick it up
斯坦利感覺到水桶在呼喚他我去拿嗎
why do i why do i why does it want me to pick up the bucket so bad
為什麼我為什麼我為什麼它要我拿起水桶太糟糕了
what if i just ignore the bucket huh what if i just ignore the bucket
如果我只是忽略水桶呢？如果我只是忽略桶怎麼辦
did i take it with me
我把它帶走了嗎
you know i'm pick you guys up fine i'll take you by god
你知道我會接你們的，我會的帶你上天
you're so needy you guys are so needy stanley picked up
你太需要了你們太需要了，斯坦利撿到了
the bucket yeah i did i did pick up the bucket damn
桶是的，我確實撿了桶該死的
bro that's that's noteworthy the bucket is back
兄弟，這是值得注意的水桶回來了
stanley clutched the bucket tightly to his chest and entered the door on his
斯坦利緊緊抓住水桶他的胸膛，踏著他的門進了門
left he's making me seem so crazy like what's
剩下他讓我看起來很瘋狂
the deal with the bucket what's the bucket for
處理桶是什麼桶為
is there like something game changing about this [ __ ] bucket
有沒有什麼東西改變這個他媽的桶的遊戲規則
let's go to the right this was not the correct way to the meeting room but
讓我們向右走 這不是去會議室的正確方式，但是
stanley had felt the bucket calling to him telling him that the employee lounge
斯坦利感覺到水桶在呼喚他告訴他員工休息室
was simply the place to be why is the bucket telling me what it
只是一個地方，為什麼是桶告訴我它是什麼
and here it was had the bucket turned out to be correct well no never mind the
水桶轉過來了是正確的，沒關係
bucket was wrong stanley took the door on his left to go
桶錯了斯坦利拿著左邊的門走了
back to the meeting no
回到會議沒有
no said the bucket don't go to the meeting
不說水桶不去開會
room go somewhere else the cargo lift yes go there go to the cargo lift
房間 去別的地方 貨梯是的 去那裡 去貨梯
it sounds like mister the bucket
聽起來像先生桶
[Laughter] why did i think of him i don't know
[笑聲]為什麼我會想起他我不知道
oh god oh my god what good said the bucket now ride the lift all the way to
哦上帝哦我的上帝說了什麼好話桶現在一直乘坐電梯到
the top there's something up there i need you to do
上面有東西我需要你做
stanley did not question why or how this bucket was speaking to you this isn't
斯坦利沒有質疑為什麼或如何桶在和你說話這不是
between you of course because don't tell him this
你們之間當然因​​為不要告訴他這個
between me and you guys stanley chose not to think about this obvious fact he
在我和你們之間，斯坦利選擇了不去想這個顯而易見的事實，他
was firmly convinced that the bucket had to go down here and he unthinkingly did
堅信水桶有下到這裡，他不假思索地做了
whatever the bucket asked no i'm not obeying the bucket i'm going
不管桶問什麼不，我不服從我要去的桶
to go down here go down here with the bucket
下到這裡拿著桶下去
oh this is new
哦，這是新的
no stop look there on the wall you see there's a sign right there it says no
不停地看你看到的牆上那裡有個牌子，上面寫著不
buckets past this point stanley how could you think it was okay to bring the
桶過了這一點斯坦利如何你覺得可以帶嗎
bucket here unless what if the problem is that you actually
在這裡桶，除非如果問題是你實際上
don't know what is a bucket and what isn't a bucket i suppose that would
不知道什麼是桶和什麼不是一個桶，我想那會
explain a lot about your behavior up to this point which if that's true well my
解釋很多關於你的行為直到這一點，如果那是真的，我的
goodness what is this bucket
善良這個桶是什麼
like this misunderstanding could have dire consequences entire rest of the
像這種誤解可能有可怕的後果整個其餘的
game if not addressed quickly and properly
如果不迅速解決遊戲適當地
so much of the impact of the story is dependent on your understanding of what
這個故事的影響很大取決於你對什麼的理解
is and isn't a bucket i know what about you step in here for a moment
是不是一個桶我知道什麼你進來一會兒
oh man you want me to walk in there you want to walk inside there why can't you
哦，伙計，你想讓我走進去想進去那裡你為什麼不能
just go in here what's wrong with the bucket doesn't let me bring onion inside
進去看看有什麼問題桶不讓我把洋蔥帶進去
is this a bucket he really thinks i'm stupid doesn't he
這是一個桶嗎他真的認為我很愚蠢，不是嗎？
now then i really think i don't know what a bucket is some test scenarios and
現在我真的覺得我不知道什麼是桶是一些測試場景和
you'll tell me whether or not the thing i'm showing you is a bucket okay surely
你會告訴我這件事是否我在向你展示你是一個水桶，當然可以
enough right they should tell us everything easy ever need to know you
他們應該告訴我們足夠的權利一切都容易了解你
can do this or is not a bucket
可以這樣做或者不是桶
okay let's begin
好吧，讓我們開始吧
item one is this a bucket yeah
第一項是這是一個桶是的
[Music] incorrect it is a hologram of a bucket
[音樂]不正確，它是桶的全息圖
not an actual bucket
不是一個真正的桶
item two is this a bucket
第二項這是一個桶嗎
oh it's against one of these games huh yeah
哦，這是針對這些遊戲之一的吧是的
it is a bucket incorrect it is a 3d printed recreation of a bucket not an
它是一個桶，不正確它是一個 3d一個桶的印刷娛樂不是一個
actual bucket okay
實際桶好的
yeah
是的
i feel like i'm being i'm being gaslit three
我覺得我正在我正在加油三
is this a bucket you know how about cuz because because you're such a smart
這是一個你知道的桶嗎因為你太聰明了
dude i'm gonna say no that's not a bucket
伙計，我會說不，那不是桶
what this is a bucket
什麼這是一個桶
item four is this a bucket
第四項這是一個桶嗎
i don't know what to think anymore man i i really don't know what to think
我不知道該怎麼想了，伙計我真的不知道該怎麼想
anymore is this a [ __ ] bucket
這不再是一個他媽的桶
uh
呃
it's an enormous machine that kills the earth i thought this was a gimmick how
這是一台巨大的機器，可以殺死地球，我認為這是一個噱頭
on earth did you manage to screw it up absolutely
你到底有沒有搞砸絕對地
incredible let's just move on to the next one i thought he was trying to
不可思議，讓我們繼續下一個我以為他在嘗試
debate me i thought he was just trying to debate me this time that's not a
辯論我我以為他只是在嘗試這次和我辯論那不是
bucket is this a bucket
桶這是一個桶嗎
oh should i say yes what the [ __ ] is this oh no you're
哦，我應該說是嗎這他媽的是什麼哦不，你是
you're not a [ __ ]
你不是他媽的
incorrect this is a bucket
不正確，這是一個桶
i hate i i am actually molding right now i
我恨我現在實際上正在成型
can't believe this i'm molding over this [ __ ] video game
不敢相信這是我正在塑造的他媽的視頻遊戲
what
什麼
how's that a bucket come on please tell me
桶怎麼來的請告訴我
you're wrong item six
你錯了第六項
is this a bucket yeah
這是一個桶嗎是的
trick question both gotcha how's that your question
技巧問題都知道你的問題怎麼樣
how how's that both
如何這兩個怎麼樣
huh hold up hold up how's that how's that
呵呵舉起 舉起 怎麼樣 那 怎麼樣 那
bone it should be around here i'm so confused i'm so confused
骨頭它應該在這附近，我是如此困惑我很困惑
trick question
技巧問題
trick question what do you mean trick question
詭計問題 你是什麼意思 詭計問題
yes thank you there's nothing here i gotta
是的謝謝你這裡什麼都沒有我要
got something right in the bucket we both know full world nothing isn't a
我們在桶裡找到了正確的東西都知道完整的世界沒有什麼不是
bucket wait when i say nothing isn't a bucket that makes it sound like i'm
等我說什麼都不是讓它聽起來像我的桶
saying everything is a bucket which of course is not true unless is that what
說一切都是水桶當然不是真的，除非那是什麼
you think answer me straight stanley are you
您認為直接回答我，斯坦利，你是嗎
trying to tell me that you believe everything is a bucket
試圖告訴我你相信一切都是一個桶
i i don't know
一世我不知道
i don't know i don't know anymore
我不知道我不知道了
what do you do to me
你對我做什麼
no it's not a no everything's a bucket
不這不是沒有，一切都是水桶
you know what i'm too confused to even sort it out
你知道我太糊塗了梳理出來
i've lost all sense of perspective what is a bucket what isn't the bucket i
我已經失去了所有的透視感是一個桶什麼不是桶我
think you're crazy i could answer these questions with confidence and yet now
覺得你瘋了我可以回答這些充滿信心地提出問題，但現在
i'm somewhat adrift i want to get out of here any of us know what a bucket is
我有點漂泊我想擺脫在這裡，我們中的任何人都知道桶是什麼
am i a bucket no you're not a bucket stanley i can't keep doing this i'm
我是水桶嗎不你不是水桶斯坦利，我不能繼續這樣做，我是
losing myself and myself was all i ever had to begin with
失去自己和我自己是我的全部必須從
i'm afraid the bucket is threatening to tear our relationship apart i can't have
恐怕水桶威脅到撕裂我們的關係，我無法擁有
that i'm sorry but i'm going to erase all no aim entirely okay no
我很抱歉，但我要抹去所有 沒有目標 完全可以 沒有
it's a he took a whole bucket what happened is everything gone why
他拿了一整桶發生的一切都過去了 為什麼
didn't everything disappear wait was everything a bucket
不是一切都消失了等等一切都是水桶
every single thing in the game was a bucket
遊戲中的每一件事都是桶
oh my god i had no idea wow you're a funny guy except me
哦，我的上帝，我不知道哇，你是個有趣的人，除了我
i'm not a bucket after all a new stanley you're still here you're not a bucket
畢竟我不是一個新的斯坦利你還在這裡 你不是水桶
either oh this is wonderful news we're not buckets
要么哦，這是個好消息，我們是不是水桶
yes i actually feel much more at ease right now it's delightful to get some
是的，我實際上感覺更自在現在很高興得到一些
clarity on that issue but it doesn't change the fact that we haven't got a
澄清這個問題，但事實並非如此改變我們沒有
game so tell you what uh-huh i'll reset
遊戲所以告訴你什麼，嗯，我會重置
everything and we'll put back all of the buckets okay okay and we'll know that
一切，我們會放回所有的水桶好吧好吧，我們會知道的
it's all a bucket but if you run into anyone else maybe don't mention that who
這都是一個桶，但如果你遇到其他人也許不會提到誰
knows what that information might do to a person all right here we go
知道該信息可能對一個人好吧，我們走
i am losing my mind i can't believe it
我正在失去理智我不敢相信
everything's a bucket every everything's a bucket everything's a
一切都是水桶一切都是一個桶 一切都是一個
[ __ ] it oh man
去他媽的哦，伙計
bro
兄弟
but he took away the bucket do i get it back though if i go back to the same
但他拿走了水桶我明白了嗎雖然如果我回到原來的地方
spot because we're gone all of these co-workers were gone
發現因為我們已經離開了所有這些同事走了
they decided to go to the meeting room give me that pocket he lifted the bucket
他們決定去會議室把那個口袋給我 他舉起水桶
into his arms and a wave of comfort rushed over him in that [ __ ] bucket
投入他的懷抱和一波安慰在那個該死的桶裡衝過他
it's my bucket stanley clutched the bucket tightly to
這是我的桶斯坦利緊緊抓住水桶
his chest this was not the correct way to the meeting room yeah you're damn
他的胸部 這不是正確的方式去會議室 是的 你該死
right it isn't felt the bucket calling to him telling him that the employee
是的，沒有感覺到水桶在呼喚告訴他該僱員
lounge was simply the place to be and here it was had the bucket turned
休息室簡直就是好去處水桶轉過來了
out to be correct was this no you know why i just noticed i just
這是正確的你知道為什麼我剛剛注意到我只是
noticed something i completely forgot to turn off the uh hold on give me a second
注意到我完全忘記的東西關掉呃等一下
oh my god i can't believe it
我的天啊我不敢相信
this whole time i had my my thing was like a little
這段時間我有我的東西有點像
darker than it should have been i am bright again hi manny took the door
比應有的更暗我又亮了 嗨曼尼拿了門
on his left back
在他的左邊背部
sorry i had like a filter on a little filter on non-brighter now
對不起，我有一個過濾器現在對非更亮進行一點過濾
save the bucket don't go to the meeting room go somewhere else find a cargo lift
存桶不去開會房間 去別的地方 找一個貨梯
yes go there go to the cargo lift guys it doesn't it sound does it not or
是的 去那裡 去貨梯伙計們，這聽起來不是嗎？
it sound like miss though come on it's pretty it's pretty close i like that
聽起來像小姐，儘管來吧漂亮，非常接近，我喜歡
good said the bucket now ride the lift all the way to the top there's something
好說桶現在坐電梯一直到頂部有東西
up there i need you to do actually you kind of can kind of feel
在那裡我需要你做實際上你有點能感覺到
but stanley chose not to think about this obvious fact he was firmly
但斯坦利選擇不去想這個明顯的事實，他堅定地
convinced that the bucket had spoken to him and he unthinkingly did whatever the
確信水桶曾與他和他不假思索地做了什麼
[ __ ] it asked oh my god i'm so i'm sorry
他媽的問哦，我的上帝，我很抱歉
i'm so sorry in here said the bucket go into this dark room over here uh-huh
我很抱歉在這裡說水桶走了進入這黑暗的房間
danny once again obeyed blindly go into the dark room over here what
丹尼再次盲目服從進入這裡的黑暗房間什麼
dark room huh there's a dark room this one
暗室 嗯，這裡有暗室一
oh now pick up the phone said the bucket no
哦現在拿起電話說水桶沒有
whoa hold on why did you unplug the phone
哇等等你為什麼拔掉電話
were you trying to resist the bucket's orders stanley i was joking obviously
你是不是想抵制水桶的命令斯坦利，我顯然是在開玩笑
the bucket isn't talking to you and telling you to do things buckets can't
桶不和你說話告訴你做桶不能做的事情
talk it was a joke don't you get the joke it's funny stammy a talking bucket
說這是個玩笑你不明白嗎開玩笑 把說話的水桶塞住很有趣
ah can't you see um oh goodness i must have
啊你看不到哦天哪我一定有
really bungled up the delivery if you actually took me seriously where did i
如果你真的搞砸了實際上把我當回事我在哪裡
mess up the joke should i have paused for longer or
把笑話搞砸了我應該暫停更長時間還是
spoken quicker comedic timing is so difficult i wish i
說得更快喜劇時機太難了，我希望我
were better at it but there isn't exactly an instructional video on comedy
做得更好，但沒有完全是一部關於喜劇的教學視頻
that one can watch to fully oh wait yes there is
那個可以看完整哦，等等，是的有
um it's sitting right here let's take a look what
嗯，它坐在這裡，讓我們試一試看什麼
but but wait no no what what is comedic timing
但是，不，不，什麼是喜劇定時
what is what is comedic timing timing how does it work how long should it last
什麼是喜劇定時定時它是如何工作的 它應該持續多長時間
how can it be used to effectively silence your political enemies and more
如何有效地使用它讓你的政治敵人沉默等等
importantly can it be taught in its entirety within 90 seconds
重要的是它可以在它的90 秒內完成
thankfully the answer to all of these questions is
謝天謝地，所有這些的答案問題是
yes let's dive deeper i'm so confused if
是的讓我們潛得更深，如果我很困惑
you've ever told a kid or made someone laugh in all likelihood you did it while
你曾經告訴過一個孩子或製造過某人很可能你在笑的時候做到了
standing 50 to 80 centimeters from them in a room of no more than 76 degrees
距離他們 50 到 80 厘米在不超過 76 度的房間裡
fahrenheit with one of your arms raised straight upward at a 15 degree angle
舉起一隻手臂的華氏度以 15 度角筆直向上
from your body these are the optimal conditions for
從你的身體這些是最佳條件
good comedic timing to begin the joke huh start by stating
好的喜劇時機開始開玩笑吧，首先說明
and spelling your name next
拼寫你的名字下一個
joke including the specific times at which the recipient of the joke will
笑話，包括具體時間笑話的接受者會
laugh and then spell out your name a second time
笑然後第二次拼出你的名字
with these steps complete it's time to begin the humor
完成這些步驟後，是時候開始幽默
speak the entire joke in no more than 18 seconds and no less than 13 and a half
在不超過 18 分鐘內講完整個笑話秒且不少於13個半
pausing only for bathroom breaks when necessary
僅在浴室休息時暫停必要的
when the joke has concluded it is customary to inform your listener that
當笑話結束時習慣上告訴你的聽眾
the joke is over by declaring in your loudest possible voice
在你的聲明中，這個笑話就結束了最大可能的聲音
i'm dunny with the funny
我很傻有趣的
let's practice screaming i'm danny with the funny now
讓我們一起練習尖叫吧現在的好笑
i'm donny with the funny good
我是唐尼有趣的好
this saying is a perfect example of expectations management which is the
這句話就是一個很好的例子期望管理是
cornerstone of good comedy this is all a joke to you finally it's time to hand
好喜劇的基石和你開玩笑 終於到手了
out surveys collecting hard data from your audience on how rap they were
出調查收集硬數據你的聽眾對他們的說唱程度
throughout the joke is the only way to grow or learn as a comedian
整個笑話是唯一的方法作為喜劇演員成長或學習
an effective survey should be no less than 10 pages long and should include
有效的調查不應該少長度超過 10 頁，應包括
the same question reprinted several times
同一個問題轉載了好幾篇次
just to ensure the survey taker is actually paying attention and not simply
只是為了確保調查員是真正關注而不是簡單
filling in answers at random and that's all there is with these
隨機填寫答案這就是這些
strategies at your disposal you'll have audiences doubled over in latter and
您將擁有的策略後者的觀眾翻了一番，
even triple over and laughter in no time at all
甚至三倍以上，很快就笑了根本
just remember to let them stop laughing at some point you gut-busting little
只記得讓他們停止笑在某些時候你會破壞小腸
scamp after all you've got busting the front
惡棍畢竟你已經破壞了前線
lines of the war to fight the 12-legged invaders who threaten our very existence
打十二條腿的戰爭路線威脅我們生存的入侵者
and very likely die in a hailstorm of bullets and mandibles all of us must be
並且很可能死於一場冰雹子彈和下顎 我們所有人都必須
prepared to give our lives to this noble course just as our children must do
準備把我們的生命獻給這個貴族當然，就像我們的孩子必須做的那樣
after us and their children after them godspeed and made earth reign supreme
在我們和他們的孩子之後神速，使地球至高無上
this feels like an analog horror hey what was that this video is a little
這感覺就像一個模擬恐怖嘿這個視頻有點什麼
outdated isn't it well no matter i think the fundamentals of proper comedic
過時了不是很好嗎不管我怎麼想適當喜劇的基礎
timing are still as relevant today as they were back then so with that in mind
時機在今天仍然與他們當時是這麼想的
i believe the only way forward is for us to return to the two doors and walk
我相信唯一的出路是我們回到兩扇門走
through all of this again so i can try telling my story with more appropriate
再次經歷這一切，所以我可以嘗試用更恰當的方式講述我的故事
comedic delivery come along let's head back uh
喜劇交付來吧讓我們開始吧回來吧
so apparently okay i don't know how comedic timing has to deal with like
所以顯然還好我不知道怎麼做喜劇時機必須處理
fending off the alien invaders but okay
抵禦外星入侵者但沒關係
sure yeah let's let's let's say yeah that will work
當然是的，讓我們說是的那可行
there's aliens i love aliens man
有外星人我愛外星人
oh my god what is happening man like i still don't understand what's going on
哦，天哪，發生了什麼事像我這樣的人還是不明白怎麼回事
in this game like there i don't know how to explain
在這場比賽中就像那裡我不知道如何解釋
what what the [ __ ] is happening what's going on
他媽的發生了什麼這是怎麼回事
i can feel i want my talking bucket back i'm really going to nail the delivery
我能感覺到我想要我的談話桶回來我真的要搞定交貨
you'll be in stitches a talking bucket you'll say how ridiculous how absurd
你會在一個會說話的桶裡縫針你會說多麼荒謬多麼荒謬
what a hilarious concept the king of comedy that's what you'll call me thank
多麼有趣的概念之王喜劇這就是你會叫我謝謝
goodness we have the instructional video otherwise who knows where we'd be right
天哪，我們有教學視頻否則誰知道我們會在哪裡
now well i wouldn't be the king of comedy
現在好吧，我不會成為喜劇之王
that's for sure the bucket spoke to stanley hmm
這是肯定的水桶對斯坦利說
the bucket spoke the bucket spoke
水桶說話了水桶說話了
oh i'll figure it out on the fly no need to go over there
哦，我會馬上解決的，不需要去那裡
um man he does good he does a good miss the
嗯男人，他做得很好，他做得很好，錯過了
voice like i'm jealous
像嫉妒一樣的聲音
okay i kind of miss it you know i think i think i actually just miss him i think
好吧我有點想念你知道我想我想我其實只是想念他 我想
that's why it's going on i think i just miss him do not lie if you're lying
這就是為什麼它會發生我想我只是想念他，如果你在撒謊，不要撒謊
right now stop okay i'll stop lying
現在停下來，好吧，我不再說謊了
[Music]
[音樂]
ah i'm gonna kick this bucket across the room
啊，我要把這個桶踢過房間
no i want so i won't do that you're precious here we go you ready
不，我想要，所以我不會那樣做寶貝，我們準備好了
when stanley and the bucket came to a set of two open doors and the bucket
當斯坦利和水桶來到一套兩個敞開的門和水桶
entered the door on the left yeah
進了門離開是的
left right left
左右剩下
right left right left
正確的左 右 左
right we're going to darkness now
正確的我們現在要去黑暗了
we're back at the phone already no no what's going on there was supposed
我們已經接電話了不不不應該發生什麼
to be several rooms leading up to this there was supposed to be a build up to
是幾個房間通向這裡應該有一個積累
this point a dramatic display of remarkable comedic wit which culminates
這一點戲劇性地展示了非凡的喜劇智慧達到高潮
in this scene with the phone but now the timing's completely off
在這個用手機的場景中，但現在時機完全不對
the joke will never land well not the way it was meant to and it's all my
這個笑話永遠不會成功它的本意是，這都是我的
fault i must have forgotten that the phone room comes immediately after the
錯誤我一定忘記了電話室在
two-door's room what an egregious mistake
兩扇門的房間多麼令人震驚錯誤
i've made a fool of myself i don't know is it was this supposed to be funny i'm
我出醜了我不知道難道這應該很有趣嗎？
nothing i'm not even the lowliest joke telling
沒有什麼我什至不是最卑微的笑話
will i think
將要我認為
i think i need no no we do not need to watch the video again no no no no no no
我想我不需要 不 我們不需要再看視頻不不不不不不
no no no no no i don't want to watch it that will help me improve my
不不不不不我不想看這將幫助我提高我的
no please i don't want to watch the video again here we go oh you ready
不，我不想看視頻又來了，我們走哦，你準備好了
when stanley and the bucket came to a set of two open doors they entered the
當斯坦利和水桶來到他們進入了兩扇敞開的門
door on the left right
左邊的門正確的
we're back at the phone already
我們已經接電話了
oh he doesn't like me here we go you ready
哦，他不喜歡我，我們走吧準備好
when stanley and the bucket came to a set of two open doors they entered the
當斯坦利和水桶來到他們進入了兩扇敞開的門
door on the left bro wait hold on like
左邊的門兄弟等等等等
okay i guess i it doesn't really let me go to the right so i guess i just gotta
好吧，我想我真的不讓我向右走，所以我想我只需要
go to the left you were supposed to go through the door on the right leading
向左走，你應該去通過右邊的門
way to the phone not even look at the instructional video
去電話的路甚至不看教學視頻
i think this is all covered very clearly oh you're such a comedic timing work now
我認為這一切都非常清楚哦，你現在真是個喜劇定時作品
it's done the joke is completely down and over it's all there is never a joke
完結了，笑話完全沒了僅此而已，從來沒有開玩笑
narrator oh my god i'm gonna eat you a community of other joke writers oh my
旁白哦，我的上帝，我要吃掉你一個其他笑話作家社區哦，我的
god bro bro he's making me lose it you're making me
天哪，兄弟，他讓我失去了它你讓我
it's as though all of your other most prized possessions pale in comparison
就好像你所有的其他人一樣珍貴的財產相形見絀
yes let me try that again stanley
是的讓我再試一次，斯坦利
i heard that you are pale with shame over how unabashedly in love with them
聽說你臉色蒼白關於如何毫不掩飾地愛上他們
shame pale
恥辱蒼白
what's another word to describe a bucket stanley this bucket is so metal i think
還有什麼詞可以形容桶斯坦利，我覺得這個桶太金屬了
i saw it playing guitar no
我看到它彈吉他不
no no no no we're getting away from making fun of that i i i
不，不，不，我們正在遠離取笑我我我
guys guys get me out get me out get me out i don't even hear these jokes
伙計們 讓我出去 讓我出去 讓我出去我什至聽不到這些笑話
anymore oh my goodness let me out let me out
哦，我的天哪讓我出去 讓我出去
let me out let me help
讓我出去讓我來幫忙
let me help help me
讓我來幫忙幫我
someone get me out [ __ ] bro oh thank god it's over no it's
有人讓我出去他媽的兄弟哦謝天謝地它結束了不它的
not over we're back at the beginning i'm not going to grab the bucket this time
還沒有結束，我們回到了起點，我是這次不去搶桶
how about that how about that i can't wait to tell this story to my co-workers
那怎麼樣 那我不能等著把這個故事告訴我的同事
stanley thought what story using they'll find it oh won't we all just laugh and
斯坦利想他們會用什麼故事找到它哦，我們不是都笑了
laugh at the time i thought everyone had gone missing
在我以為每個人都有的時候笑失踪了
i'm not grabbing the bucket
我不搶桶
i'm not grabbing the bucket when stanley came to a set of two open
我不搶桶當 stanley 來到一組兩人開場時
doors he entered the door on his left
門他進入了他左邊的門
i'll grab him next time i want to see if uh you know he he does anything
下次我會抓住他，我想看看呃你知道他什麼都做
yet there was not a single person here either
然而這裡沒有一個人任何一個
feeling a wave of disbelief stanley decided to go up to his bosses
感到一陣難以置信 斯坦利決定去找他的老闆
left you guys behind upstairs to his boss's office
把你們拋在後面上樓去他老闆的辦公室
no i want to go downstairs again
不，我想再下樓
oh you found one of them one of the
哦你找到了其中之一
miniature stanley figurines remember no reward for collecting all of these only
微型斯坦利小雕像記得不僅收集所有這些的獎勵
the intrinsic pleasure of a job well done you can't buy that sort of fabulous
工作的內在樂趣做你不能買那種神話般的
stanley god knows that tribe ah
斯坦利 上帝知道那個部落啊
every moment you'll come across one of these beautiful figurines
每時每刻你都會遇到一個這些美麗的小雕像
ah why am i here again stanley just
啊為什麼我又來了，斯坦利只是
couldn't do it he considered the possibility of facing
做不到他考慮了面對的可能性
his boss admitting he had left his post during work hours he might be fired for
他的老闆承認他已離職在工作時間他可能會被解僱
that and in such a way this is the same ending hold on wait i [ __ ] up hold on
以這種方式這是相同的結束 等等 我搞砸了 等等
begin the game again yeah yeah i [ __ ] up i went back to the same law
重新開始遊戲我搞砸了，我回到了同樣的法律
i got that's the same thing maybe i have to grab the bucket stanley
我知道那是一樣的也許我必須抓住桶斯坦利
decided to go to the meeting room perhaps he had simply missed him you're
決定去會議室也許他只是想念他你是
not [ __ ] you you're coming with me over here from the chaos all seemed to melt
別操你，你要跟我過來這裡從混亂中一切似乎都融化了
away as stanley embraced the bucket yeah
斯坦利擁抱水桶時離開是的
stanley clutched the bucket tightened into his chest and entered the door on
斯坦利緊緊抓住水桶進入他的胸膛，然後走進門
his left i kissed the bucket is my bucket
他的左邊我吻了水桶是我的桶
wait what wait what is this
等什麼等等這是什麼
trust the completionist instinct there will be a reward for finding them
相信完成主義者的本能找到他們會有獎勵
all huh
全部呵呵
that's creepy
太嚇人了
the mission status alar oh
任務狀態阿拉哦
a large room lots of boxes somewhere both red and blue nearby a fireplace a
一個大房間 某處有很多盒子壁爐附近的紅色和藍色
private but smelly place for an important person
私人但很臭的地方重要的人
oh is to collect all the collectibles
哦是收集所有的收藏品
stalking yourselves there will be a cleaning of this wall
跟踪自己將清理這面牆
required who are you 666 lol
必填 你是誰666 哈哈
what
什麼
they they really want me to go look for it okay you know what fine fine i will i
他們真的要我去找沒關係，你知道我會怎麼樣
will go look for the collectors coming to a staircase stanley and the bucket
會去尋找來的收藏家到樓梯斯坦利和水桶
walked upstairs to the bosses what if i just take the bucket with me
走到樓上的老闆那裡，如果我把水桶帶在我身邊
downstairs will i change anything
樓下我會改變什麼嗎
but stanley just couldn't do it he considered the possibility of facing
但斯坦利就是做不到他考慮了面對的可能性
his boss admitting he had left his post during work hours he might be fired for
他的老闆承認他已離職在工作時間他可能會被解僱
that and in such a competitive economy why had he taken that risk all because
在這樣一個競爭激烈的經濟中他為什麼要冒這個險都是因為
he believed everyone had vanished his boss would think he was crazy and then
他相信每個人都消失了老闆會認為他瘋了，然後
something occurred to stanley maybe he thought to himself maybe i am
斯坦利發生了什麼事也許他心想也許我是
crazy no it's the same thing down at the bucket in his arms am i crazy he asked
瘋了，不，在下面是一樣的在他懷裡的水桶我瘋了嗎他問
the bucket the bucket returned his gaze but said nothing at all am i crazy
水桶 水桶回了他的目光但什麼也沒說我瘋了嗎
buckingham stanley thought usually the bucket is a source of guidance and
白金漢斯坦利通常認為桶是指導的來源和
wisdom for me in difficult times such as these hey chad am i crazy it felt none
在困難時期為我提供智慧，例如這些嘿，乍得，我瘋了嗎，感覺沒有
of it's familiar am i crazy
熟悉的我瘋了嗎
and that's when stanley realized this isn't my bucket it's just a normal
就在那時，斯坦利意識到這不是我的桶 這只是一個普通的
everyday bucket someone else's bucket perhaps how did i end up with someone
每天桶別人的桶也許我是怎麼和某人在一起的
else's bucket this is all terribly wrong surely no good would
其他人的桶，這都是非常錯誤的肯定沒有好處
who knows what sorts of bizarre hallucinations stanley might experience
誰知道有什麼奇怪的斯坦利可能會經歷的幻覺
without the unfocused grounding presence of his bucket
沒有不集中的接地存在他的桶
indeed now he noticed that the rooms were repeating which was of course very
的確，現在他注意到房間正在重複這當然是非常
odd now he felt himself floating off the
奇怪的現在他覺得自己飄離了
ground oh gracious he exclaimed without my
地面哦，天哪，他在沒有我的情況下驚呼
bucket i've gone truly mad where is it i must find it far off in the distance now
水桶我真的瘋了我在哪裡現在必須在遙遠的地方找到它
he heard it calling to him stanley stanley it's me
他聽到它在呼喚他斯坦利 斯坦利 是我
the bucket could it truly be he rushed forward from
桶難道他真的是從
room to room passing by one bucket after the next none of them were his none of
一個水桶經過一個房間到另一個房間下一個都不是他的
them were his special bucket come to me stanley find me
他們是他的特殊桶來找我斯坦利找到我
he had to return to his old friend it was the only way to truly restore his
他不得不回到他的老朋友那裡是真正恢復他的唯一方法
sanity and then suddenly it froze dead in his tracks
理智然後突然凍死了在他的軌道上
he knew where the voice of the bucket had been coming from
他知道水桶的聲音在哪裡來自
the real bucket was inside of him all along
真正的水桶在他體內沿著
it was incredibly painful really stanley doubled over in agony and blacked out
斯坦利真的非常痛苦痛苦地翻了一番，昏了過去
the real bucket was inside of me of a woman named mariela huh are we really
真正的水桶在我體內名叫瑪麗埃拉的女人，嗯，我們真的嗎？
gonna it's are we gonna really be passing on the
會的我們真的要傳遞
streets again like any other die die rose got dressed picked up her bucket of
街道再次像任何其他死亡一樣死亡玫瑰穿好衣服拿起她的桶
comfort and security and walked to her place of work
舒適和安全，走向她工作的地方
but on this particular day her walk was interrupted by the body of a man who had
但在這一天，她的散步是被一個男人的身體打斷
stumbled through town talking and screaming to himself and then collapsed
跌跌撞撞地通過城鎮談話和對自己尖叫然後倒下
dead on the sidewalk right away she knew what the problem was
她知道馬上死在人行道上問題是什麼
this man had no butt i'm bucketless no buckets
這個人沒有屁股 我沒桶沒有桶
no buckets [Music]
沒有桶[音樂]
all of his actions and how everything is pre-determined
他的所有行為以及一切如何預定的
how cruel the world can be marielle and she hugged her own bucket even
世界有多殘酷，瑪麗艾爾她甚至擁抱了自己的水桶
tighter but of course she had no time for this
更緊但她當然沒有時間
there were a myriad of confusing problems she would soon have to confront
有無數的困惑她很快將不得不面對的問題
at work for which her bucket would provide absolute guidance and total
在工作中，她的水桶會提供絕對指導和總
clarity on everything heck yes she thought to herself my life ticks ass and
一切都清楚，是的，她心想我的生活滴滴答答
she backflipped all the way to work what a [ __ ]
她在上班的路上一直後空翻真是個[ __ ]
flaunting her bucket at a dead body
對著一具屍體炫耀她的水桶
what is with the bucket man what's with all the bucket so why is the bucket so
水桶男怎麼了所有的水桶那麼為什麼水桶如此
important oh my god oh it's right there why is it why are
重要的天啊哦，它就在那裡 為什麼它為什麼
you so close to me now warmth spread through stanley's arms with the bucket
你離我如此之近 現在溫暖蔓延用桶穿過斯坦利的懷抱
in his arms again he was home stanley clutched the bucket tightly to his chest
在他的懷裡，他又回到了家，斯坦利將水桶緊緊攥在胸前
and entered the door on his left
進了他左邊的門
this was not the correct way to the meeting room but stanley had felt the
這不是正確的方法會議室，但 stanley 感覺到
bucket calling to him telling him that the employee lounge was simply the place
水桶打電話給他，告訴他員工休息室就是這個地方
to be and here it was had the bucket turned
成為水桶轉過來了
out to be correct was this better than the meeting room yes danny thought to
正確的是這比會議室是的，丹尼想
himself yes perhaps it truly oh how insightful the bucket turned out to
他自己是的，也許真的是哦桶原來是多麼有見地
be no
是不
never mind wait hold on left we have to go this way what if i go this
沒關係，等一下，我們必須走這條路 如果我走這條路怎麼辦
way left to go back and so the two of them detoured through the maintenance
剩下的路要回去，所以兩個他們繞道維修
section and walked straight ahead to the opposite way what is this
部分，徑直走到相反的方式這是什麼
wait what is this stuff
等等這是什麼東西
uh hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on wait i don't i don't recognize what
呃 保持 保持 保持 保持 保持在等待我不知道我不知道什麼
this is i want to see what goes what we're going
這是我想看看我們要做什麼
towards
向
where am i going oh good stanley i'm glad you found your way here i knew
我要去哪裡哦，斯坦利，我在很高興你在這裡找到了自己的路我知道
you'd find this place eventually oh
你最終會找到這個地方哦
you see your friends and i are concerned for you stan ah we've come together here
你看到你的朋友，我很擔心為了你，斯坦啊，我們走到了一起
my friends about you very much it's this bucket you're carrying around
我的朋友們非常喜歡你這是你隨身攜帶的這個桶
everywhere the bucket isn't even from the original
到處桶甚至不是原來的
stanley parable it's just secret am i having the ones that matter stanley
斯坦利寓言這只是秘密，我是擁有重要的斯坦利
classic characters from the first game like the adventure line and the broom
第一款遊戲中的經典角色像冒險線和掃帚
closet because that's what fans oh my god they're giving me an intervention
壁櫥，因為那是粉絲哦，我的上帝他們在給我干預
their favorite jokes not this bucket that they've never seen before
他們最喜歡的笑話不是這個桶他們以前從未見過的
yes i know i'm the one who gave you the bucket but you're spending too much time
是的，我知道我是給你的人水桶，但你花了太多時間
with it don't you want another story involving the adventure line we could
有了它你不想要另一個故事嗎涉及我們可以的冒險路線
make the adventure line go somewhere new yes yes that's what the fans want let's
讓冒險路線去一個新的地方是的，是的，這就是粉絲想要的，讓我們
do it
做
but but look at that wacky line who knows where
但是但是看看那條奇怪的線誰知道在哪裡
it'll go off to next oh and it played some silly music as well you can't take
它會轉到下一個哦，它播放了一些你不能接受的愚蠢的音樂
my bucket [Music]
我的桶[音樂]
what
什麼
[Music] now this is what the stanley parable is
[音樂]這就是斯坦利的寓言
all about don't you remember all those great jokes from the original dialogue
你不記得所有那些原始對話中的精彩笑話
also stanley is addicted to drugs and hookers
斯坦利也吸毒成癮妓女
whoa
哇
whoa i did not expect that
哇我沒想到的是
it's as classic knowledge it was back then let's do it for the fans stanley
它就像經典知識一樣回來了那麼讓我們為粉絲們做吧 stanley
let's give them more content exactly like this but if we want to do that
讓我們準確地給他們更多的內容像這樣，但如果我們想那樣做
you're going to have to give something up
你將不得不給予一些東西向上
why am i have to give up
為什麼我要放棄
oh my huh give up you're not gonna let me get rid of my
oh my huh 放棄你不會讓我擺脫我的
bucket are you huh yeah i'm making me give her a bucket no
水桶你是嗎是的，我讓我給她一個桶不
i don't i this is my bucket sir that's his name is onion i give him a name and
我不，我這是我的桶，先生，那是他的名字是洋蔥我給他一個名字
everything don't you get it stanley we need to get rid of the bucket
一切你不明白，斯坦利，我們需要擺脫水桶
that's why i'm very proud to introduce a brand new character
這就是為什麼我很自豪地介紹一個全新的角色
this is the bucket destroyer
這是鏟斗破壞者
i think it'll make a wonderful new addition to the rich lore of the stanley
我想它會成為一個很棒的新的除了斯坦利的豐富傳說
parable true it also was not in this but it's such a well flesh i refuse with
寓言真實它也不是在這個但我拒絕吃這麼好的肉
so much personality that to me it already feels as though it's been part
如此個性，對我來說已經感覺好像它是一部分
of the cast all along don't you agree [ __ ] is this can you guess what the
你不同意嗎？他媽的這是你能猜到是什麼
bucket destroyer does surely you don't need me to spell it out
鏟斗毀滅者你肯定不需要我拼出來
for you no no i can't just say that now stanley
對你不不，我現在不能這麼說斯坦利
say goodbye to the bucket and then pop it into the machine when you're ready no
和水桶說再見然後彈出準備好後將其放入機器中
i don't think i will i don't think i will i uh
我想我不會我不認為我會
listen to me it's crucial that you give it the bucket i don't know what the
聽我說，你給予是至關重要的它是桶，我不知道是什麼
bucket destroyer will do if it can't destroy your bucket destroying buckets
如果它不能，bucket destroyer 會做銷毀你的桶 銷毀桶
is all it knows that is its singular personality trait
它所知道的就是它的奇異嗎人格特點
sure i can hear you saying how does a character with only one personality
我當然能聽到你說只有一種性格的角色
trait deserve to join the pantheon of beloved stanley parable characters well
特質值得加入萬神殿心愛的斯坦利寓言人物很好
you see if you were to really explore the bucket destroyer you would see that
你看看你是否真的要探索你會看到的鏟斗驅逐艦
its desire to crush buckets is so densely loaded with complexity and
它壓碎水桶的慾望是如此充滿了複雜性和
nuance that it's really like 10 personality traits what other object in
細微差別，它真的很像 10性格特點什麼其他對象
this game can you even say that about the broom closet certainly not i wonder
這個遊戲你能說嗎掃帚櫃當然不是我想知道的
what sort of bucket destroyer merchandise the fans will be clamoring
什麼樣的鏟斗破壞者粉絲們會叫囂的商品
for after this okay the bucket destroyer is getting
在此之後好的，鏟斗驅逐艦正在
very upset now you'll have to hurry and feed it we can't get back to the classic
現在非常沮喪，你必須快點餵牠我們無法回到經典
stanley parable characters like the adventure line or the bucket destroyer
斯坦利寓言人物，如冒險線或鏟斗驅逐艦
until you've crushed that damn bucket no now the fans are waiting do it the fan
直到你粉碎了那個該死的水桶現在粉絲們正在等待做粉絲
standing no fans what they want it's my bucket no
沒有粉絲他們想要什麼這是我的桶不
[ __ ] you i'm keeping the bucket
去你的我保留桶
i don't care what anyone says wait did i die
我不在乎任何人說什麼等等我做了嗎死
did i die wait what is that
我死了嗎等那是什麼
the bucket destroyer my prized creation you had so much
鏟斗破壞者我珍貴的創作你有這麼多
potential we were going to do such marvelous things with you tell such
有可能我們會這樣做你的奇妙事告訴你
spell binding stories about you all of its squadron now
關於你們所有人的拼寫故事現在它的中隊
goodbye new friend
再見新的朋友
for the moment in time that you were here
在你曾經的那一刻這裡
you were magnificent you're so dramatic
你之前是太棒了，你太戲劇化了
i've known the bucket for longer screw that guy
我認識水桶的時間更長了搞砸那個人
wait hello
等待你好
okay well well i mean he's dead i mean the bucket destroys that what
好吧好吧我的意思是他死了我的意思是水桶摧毀了什麼
is there nowhere and stanley decided that as soon as he
有沒有地方斯坦利決定，只要他
found a new space he felt safe in that he would never leave it again in his
找到了一個他覺得安全的新空間他再也不會把它留在他的
life guys guys
生活伙計們
guys guys guys stanley picked up the bucket and smiled he'd never be alone
伙計們，伙計們，斯坦利拿起了桶和微笑他永遠不會孤單
again not truly alone put the bucket around
又不是真正獨自放桶大約
oh my god he makes it sound like i'm going crazy dude he's like he's playing
哦，我的上帝，他讓我聽起來像瘋了，伙計，他就像在玩
into my brain like i think the bucket is like another person dude stop stop it a
像我認為水桶一樣進入我的大腦像另一個人一樣，停止停止它
narrator you're cr stop it no
敘述者你是cr停止它不
i'm just picking it up because it's pretty cool it's a pretty good looking
我只是把它撿起來，因為它是很酷，很好看
bucket it's a pretty good looking bucket and they clutched the bucket tightly to
水桶 這是一個很好看的水桶他們緊緊抓住水桶
his chest and entered the door on his left
他的胸膛，踏著他的門進了門剩下
help [Music]
幫助[音樂]
i'm in the boss's office this is the executive bathroom oh my god
我在老闆辦公室這是行政浴室哦，我的上帝
another miniature stanley figurine wow there's three you know there really must
另一個微型斯坦利雕像哇有三個你知道真的必須
be a snappier name for these things what about
給這些東西起個更響亮的名字關於
mini stands stanley figs um what about stanlarines yes i think i like that
mini stand stanley figs 嗯怎麼樣stanlarines 是的，我想我喜歡
another stanlerine under your belt i'm gonna go crazy oh my god to be rich
你腰帶下的另一個斯坦勒林我要瘋了，天哪，我要發財了
is it a crime to commit crimes isn't it rich what a life it would be to have to
犯罪是不是犯罪豐富的生活將是怎樣的
pick just one well
只選一個出色地
you know you could just pick your nose and be done with it right
你知道你可以挖你的鼻子做對了
another thing
另一件事
oh
哦
holy [ __ ] hold up
天哪耽誤
wait cannot use the elevator again damn wait
等等 不能再用電梯了 該死等待
oh where's he's gonna take me where are we gonna go
哦，他要帶我去哪裡我們要去哪裡
new adventures
新的冒險
this is a very elevator music it's very elevator music
這是一首非常電梯的音樂這是非常電梯的音樂
um
嗯
[Music]
[音樂]
oh thank you oh wait what
哦謝謝哦等等什麼
what huh
什麼呵呵
can go up
可以上去
wow i got scammed
哇我被騙了
i got [ __ ] scammed that's not real stepping into his manager's office
我被他媽騙了，那不是真的走進他的經理辦公室
stanley was once again stunned to discover not an indication didn't bring
斯坦利再次驚呆了發現不是一個跡像沒有帶來
me anywhere who makes an elevator just for the sake
我在任何地方誰只是為了造電梯
of staying in one spot into an emotional dumpster fire if not for the soothing
停留在一個地方變成情緒化的如果不是為了舒緩，垃圾箱火
presence of the bucket even now in his darkest of hours did the
桶的存在即使現在在他最黑暗的時刻
bucket's warmth and guiding light pierce the dark clouds of confusion and chaos
水桶的溫暖和指引之光穿透混亂和混亂的烏雲
it would be with him always the bucket would
它會永遠和他在一起水桶會
and he knew it will guide me
他知道會指導我
at this point stanley was so absorbed in the tender spiritual connection he
在這一點上，斯坦利全神貫注他溫柔的精神聯繫
shared with the bucket that he didn't notice the keypad behind the button i
與他沒有的桶共享注意按鈕 i 後面的鍵盤
literally see it right here in his bliss of simply being near the bucket did he
從字面上看，就在他的幸福中他只是靠近水桶
have you're making me sound like i am like just
你讓我聽起來像我嗎就像只是
i am obsessed with the bucket you're acting like i i i put it to bed every
我沉迷於你的桶表現得像我我每次都把它放在床上
night and i kiss it and i like feed it dinner and i cuddle the bucket to eight
晚上，我親吻它，我喜歡餵牠晚飯，我把水桶抱到八點
four five see stanley but stanley guessed the correct code by sheer luck
四五見史丹利但史丹利完全靠運氣猜到了正確的代碼
what was it what do you mean
它以前如何你是什​​麼意思
yes this is certainly the most logical explanation
是的，這當然是最合乎邏輯的解釋
oh my god oh my god here's another figurine the name of these little
哦，我的上帝，我的上帝，這是另一個想像這些小東西的名字
stanley figurines and now i'm torn between stan lorene's and figlis what do
斯坦利小雕像，現在我被撕裂了在 stan lorene's 和 figlis 之間做什麼
you think stanley what name better encapsulates the intrinsic sense of
你覺得斯坦利叫什麼名字更好囊括了內在的意義
happiness that you get from seeing a small number in the corner of your
你從看到一個得到的幸福你角落裡的小數字
screen go up i walk as a figure sit on it i'm sure it will come to me
屏幕上去我走作為一個人坐在我相信它會來找我
i feel like i'm getting more deranged you know like how how i'm game wards
我覺得我越來越精神錯亂你知道我是怎麼玩遊戲的
arranged as we go along with this charade of a game
我們一起安排遊戲的遊戲
where are these huh what is this you think this is all some kind of stanley
這些在哪裡啊這是什麼你認為這都是某種斯坦利
parable to you huh huh narrator
比喻給你呵呵敘述者
reassuring that in this darkest moment of uncertainty he would be right
在這最黑暗的時刻保證不確定他是對的
the bucket is here everything will be fine
桶在這裡一切都會好起來的
okay i'm fine i'm okay
好吧，我很好我很好
the bucket got me i know if no one else got me the bucket of god you can walk
桶讓我知道如果沒有其他人給我一桶上帝你可以走路
straight ahead through the large door than red escape
直接穿過大門比紅色逃脫
control facility although this passageway had the word
控制設施雖然這條通道有這個詞
escape written on it the truth was that at the end of this hall stanley and the
逃跑寫在上面，事實是在這個大廳的盡頭，斯坦利和
bucket would both meet a violent death
水桶都會遭遇暴死
i think you're lying you're a liar you are a liar
我認為你在撒謊 你是個騙子你是個騙子
i'm not gonna die the door behind them was not shut
我不會死的他們身後的門沒有關上
stanley and the bucket still had every opportunity to turn around and get back
斯坦利和水桶仍然有轉身回來的機會
on track
在軌道上
at this point stanley and the bucket were knowingly walking forward into a
此時斯坦利和水桶明知故犯地往前走
very painful death for each of them very painful death
他們每個人都非常痛苦地死去痛苦的死亡
what's the very painful death huh what's down here
什麼是非常痛苦的死亡 huh what's在這裡
do i just go back
我要回去嗎
me and you bucket
我和你鬥
huh hey we're fine
呵呵嘿，我們很好
we're perfectly fine the narrator lied oh my god maybe he
我們很好敘述者撒了謊哦，我的上帝，也許他
lied to me because he didn't want me to find this
對我撒謊是因為他不想讓我找到這個
oh no oh no oh no as the machine worked into motion oh yeah in the bucket inch
哦不哦不哦不因為機器工作動起來哦，是的，在桶裡
closer to their demise stanley reflected on how meaningless the bucket's warmth
更接近他們的死亡斯坦利反映關於桶的溫暖是多麼的無意義
and comfort had turned out to be to be sure it puts the mind and the soul at
和舒適原來是肯定它把思想和靈魂放在
ease to embrace the bucket but what use is a sense of ease when you're about to
輕鬆擁抱水桶，但有什麼用是一種輕鬆的感覺，當你即將
be crushed to death uh bucket do something [ __ ] it guys chat do
被壓死uh桶做點什麼他媽的吧伙計們聊天做
something help me help help farewell
有什麼幫助我幫助 幫助 告別
oh farewell stanley cried the narrator as
哦告別斯坦利，敘述者哭著說
stanley and the bucket were led helplessly into the enormous metal jaws
斯坦利和水桶被引導無助地陷入巨大的金屬鉗口
in a single visceral instant the bucket's life came to an end as it
在一個發自內心的瞬間水桶的生命結束了
was crushed violently to death
被粗暴地壓死
mommy
媽媽
mommy it was a shame the death of such a magnificent bucket it's true that all
媽媽，這樣一個人的死真是太可惜了華麗的水桶這是真的
buckets are agent in their own way but this one stood above the rest it was a
水桶以自己的方式代理，但這個站在其他人之上，這是一個
glorious bucket to behold bucket saved me
光榮的水桶看到水桶得救了我
the bucket saved me the bucket welcomes you to the grand
水桶救了我桶歡迎您到盛大
exhibits you are standing at the precipice of
展品你站在懸崖邊
knowledge much like the bucket itself the human mind is frequently empty
知識很像水桶本身人的頭腦經常是空的
within a cavernous void but through the either use of the exhibition in front of
在一個巨大的空隙中，但通過要么利用前面的展覽
you the mind comes full and enriched and substantiated knowledge of the bucket
你的頭腦變得充實而豐富經證實的水桶知識
and it's not history is the only true knowledge we really have you take what
這不是歷史是唯一真實的知識我們真的有你拿什麼
you have learned you're out with you into the world will you accept with an
你已經知道你和你在一起進入這個世界你會接受嗎
open mind what may be challenging about the information this exhibit will you
敞開心扉，什麼可能具有挑戰性本次展覽將為您提供的信息
change the lives of yourself and your loved ones as a result of this exhibit
改變你自己和你的生活親人作為這次展覽的結果
or will you turn a blind eye and continue to live as you were in
還是你會視而不見繼續像以前一樣生活
ignorance and darkness
無知和黑暗
can you see how arrogant it was for stanley to take a bucket like this and
你能看出它有多傲慢嗎斯坦利像這樣拿一個水桶，
to claim it for his own can you see the hubris that blinded him can you see that
為他自己主張，你能看到嗎？讓他失明的狂妄你能看到嗎
my hubris is far more noble than stanley will ever be in his short life
我的狂妄遠比斯坦利高貴將永遠在他短暫的生命中
what happens to the narrator she's she sounds kind of kind of mom mommy as heck
敘述者發生了什麼她就是她聽起來有點像媽媽媽媽
what happened to the other one the stress bucket and analogy worrying
另一個發生了什麼事壓力桶和類比令人擔憂
negative forecasting negative thinking lack of reassurance this is like some
消極預測消極思考缺乏保證，這就像一些
1800s psychology [ __ ] uh
1800年代的心理學狗屎呃
cave drawing while we know that the buckets predate the existence of mankind
雖然我們知道洞穴繪畫水桶早於人類的存在
we do not know how long this cave drawing depicts early man's discovery of
我們不知道這個洞穴有多長繪畫描繪了早期人類的發現
the practical uses of the bucket by which time the bucket had already likely
水桶的實際用途桶已經很可能是什麼時候
been around for several millennia notice in these drawings how the bucket is
已經存在了幾千年的通知在這些圖中，桶是怎樣的
allowing itself to be used having judged humanity to be worthy of its treasures
允許自己被用來判斷人類配得上它的寶藏
no man can own a bucket and certainly not a bucket as dazzling to behold as
沒有人可以擁有一個桶，當然不像水桶那麼耀眼
this one it is man who should kneel before the
這個應該跪在人前
bucket what
桶什麼
the hanging bucket this piece symbolizes the necessary
吊桶這件作品象徵著必要的
relationship between buckets and humanity our clearer grasp of the bucket
桶和桶之間的關係人類我們更清楚地掌握了水桶
may be there is yet more that is always out of reach this distance inevitably is
也許還有更多永遠存在的東西遙不可及這個距離必然是
for our own good
為了我們好
the bucket analogy is actually a thing i i guess i jump in the whole oh
桶類比實際上是我的事情我想我跳進去了哦
oh
哦
is this heaven we can do something we can do together
這是天堂嗎我們可以做一些我們可以一起做的事情
you and i that will right this terrible wrong
你和我會糾正這可怕的錯誤的
let stanley die let him be crushed by the machine no
讓斯坦利死讓他被機器碾壓不
reset the game don't give him another opportunity to run off with another
重置遊戲不要給他另一個和另一個人一起逃跑的機會
beautiful bucket we can save the world's buckets from their treatment as tools
美麗的水桶我們可以拯救世界從他們作為工具處理的桶
and implements if only we let stanley die together the bucket shall take its
只要我們讓 stanley 就可以實現一起死，水桶將帶走它的
place as ruler as leader as commander of a new world a new vision
作為統治者作為領導者作為指揮官新世界新視野
i died
我死了
i i actually died
我真的死了
i [ __ ] gots
我他媽的得到了
the what the hell is happening in this game
這到底是怎麼回事遊戲
ah oh my god
啊我的天啊
yo yo
喲喲
yo i'm so confused i am so lost
喲我很困惑我很迷茫
this is like i feel exhausted you know
這就像我感到筋疲力盡你知道
like i feel unreasonably exhausted
喜歡我感到莫名的筋疲力盡
and i don't know why
我不知道為什麼
do you guys know what i mean like we've only been here for how long
你們知道我的意思嗎就像我們只在這裡多久
two hours and almost 30 minutes and i'm already like
兩個小時將近 30 分鐘，我已經喜歡了
my i've gone through so many emotions like this game like really brought me up
我經歷了很多情緒喜歡這個遊戲就像真的把我養大了
and down to the highest points and the lowest points and everywhere in between
一直到最高點和最低點和介於兩者之間的任何地方
like just going up and down up and down up
喜歡只是上下上下
and down up and down up and down like i'm bouncing on some [ __ ] but no this is
上下 上下 上下 像我在一些公雞上彈跳，但不是這個
entirely different nothing related to that i i just feel like i'm going
完全不同 無關我只是覺得我要走了
through a rollercoaster and it is it is it just doesn't get any it just makes me
通過過山車，就是這樣它只是沒有得到任何它只是讓我
is really like rubbing salt on the wound
是真的很喜歡在傷口上撒鹽
right now it's like exacerbating the injury at this point and i don't know
現在這就像加劇了在這一點上受傷，我不知道
what to do this [ __ ] bucket stanley had never seen the office this brightly
怎麼辦這個他媽的桶斯坦利從未見過如此明亮的辦公室
lit was it a sign of something no he hoped it was he hoped very much that it
點燃是不是有什麼跡象希望是他非常希望
was the good old bucket just standing in the bucket off on another thrilling
那個好舊的水桶只是站在裡面嗎再一次驚險刺激
adventure together stanley clutched the bucket tightly to
一起冒險斯坦利緊緊抓住水桶
his chest and entered the door on his left
他的胸膛，踏著他的門進了門剩下
what if i don't go anywhere huh what if i don't go anywhere what if i
如果我哪兒也不去怎麼辦如果我哪兒也不去怎麼辦
just chill here huh i say [ __ ] it i don't go anything
在這裡冷靜一下吧我說操，我什麼都不去
through any of those doors i just say here it's me and you hey there
通過任何一扇門，我只是說這裡是我和你嘿那裡
hi it's me shoto how you doing today
嗨，我是shoto您今天怎麼樣
ignore the bucket for a second and look at me all right
忽略桶一秒鐘然後看我沒事
yeah [ __ ] the game [ __ ] the doors [ __ ] the [ __ ] the narrator okay
是的 去他媽的遊戲 去他媽的門操他媽的敘述者好吧
just look at me all right
看著我好的
cool go around the same page nice nice nice all right
酷 去同一頁 不錯不錯不錯不錯
so uh what you're doing this weekend
所以呃這個週末你在做什麼
it's thursday tomorrow's friday and it's gonna be saturday and sunday right you
今天是星期四明天星期五星期六和星期天對你
wanna you wanna do something together
想你想一起做點什麼
you wanna go somewhere how about we go somewhere i feel like i wanna go
你想去某個地方我們去怎麼樣我覺得我想去的地方
somewhere i wanna i'll go out
某處我想出去
i'll be somewhere do something i wanna touch grass eat ass
我會在某個地方做我想做的事摸草吃屁股
and go fast
走得快
no no
不不
i wanna i want to go somewhere i'm gonna go somewhere
我想我想去某個地方我要去某個地方
i'll be here with this bucket anymore maybe i do
我會再拿著這個桶在這裡也許我會
maybe i'm lying to myself stanley just stood there doing nothing
也許我在對自己撒謊斯坦利只是站在那裡無所事事
at all he seems to think i have nothing better to do with my time than to sit
他似乎認為我一無所有我的時間比坐著好
around and describe every fascinating little detail of his ability to do
圍繞並描述每一個迷人的他做事能力的小細節
anything this is why stanley and i are on such good terms
這就是為什麼我和斯坦利在這麼好的條件下
oh my god it worked it [ __ ] worked
哦，天哪，它起作用了它他媽的奏效了
all right let's just chill here for a bit
好吧，讓我們在這裡放鬆一下少量
i know he's gonna he's gonna eventually just say something else
我知道他會 他最終會說點別的
he's gonna be easy to say something else and know it know it
他會很容易說別的知道它知道它
what am i drinking i'm drinking a cup of earl grey
我在喝什麼我在喝一杯格雷伯爵茶
with a little bit of uh honey honey and earl grey tea
加一點蜂蜜蜂蜜和伯爵茶
as any of her my throat
就像她的任何一個我的喉嚨
this is nice isn't it we get to just talk to each other and chill
這很好是不是我們只是互相交談並冷靜下來
just me and you not a worry in the world right
只有我和你不是世界上的擔心
we're just chilling in the air it's like we're laying on the couch
我們只是在空氣中冷卻，就像我們躺在沙發上
just vibing don't have to worry about a silly
只是振動不用擔心一個傻
british british now right uh as in his bucket
英國的現在英國人，呃，就像在他的桶裡一樣
agenda
議程
the entire time
整個時間
nope nothing at all nothing at all
不，什麼都沒有什麼都沒有
okay maybe maybe i can't do anything he doesn't seem like he's saying anything
好吧也許我什麼都做不了 他他好像什麼也沒說
right now narrator hello
馬上解說員你好
narrator
敘述者
no okay
不好的
oh my god i think
我的天啊我認為
hmm
唔
there's nothing left over here is there let me think about that real quick
這裡什麼都沒有了讓我考慮一下
i go down there i go down
我去那裡我下去
this was not the correct way to the meeting room but stanley had felt the
這不是正確的方法會議室，但 stanley 感覺到
bucket calling to him telling him that the employee lounge was simply the place
水桶打電話給他，告訴他員工休息室就是這個地方
to be and here it is i know exactly where i
成為在這裡，我確切地知道我在哪裡
want to go again i'm going to jump off i want to jump off the knee and go down to
想再去一次，我要跳下去了想從膝蓋上跳下來
the catwalk again and see if anything changes
再次走秀，看看有沒有什麼變化
left to go back to the meeting room
離開回到會議室
now said the bucket don't go to the meeting
現在說水桶不去開會
room go somewhere else the cargo lift yes good said the bucket now ride the
房間 去別的地方 貨梯是的，很好說，桶現在騎
lift all the way to the top there's something up there i need you to do
一直舉到頂部上面有事我需要你做
stanley did not miss that voice bucket was speaking to
斯坦利沒有想念那個語音桶正在說話
him it should have alarmed him of course because buckets can't talk but stanley
他當然應該驚動他因為水桶不會說話，但斯坦利
chose not to think about this obvious fact he was firmly convinced that the
選擇不去想這個明顯的事實上，他堅信
bucket had spoken to him and he unthinkingly did whatever the bucket
水桶和他說過話，他不假思索地做了什麼
asked is it gonna be the same thing again is
問會不會又是一樣的事情
he gonna make me like be like oh no buckets allowed
他會讓我喜歡哦不允許的桶
no stop [ __ ] up there on the wall you see there's a sign right there it says
不要停止他媽的在牆上你看到那裡有一個標誌，上面寫著
no buckets past this point stanley how could you think it was okay give me the
沒有超過這一點的水桶斯坦利如何你覺得可以嗎 給我
same thing again unless what if the problem is that you actually don't know
同樣的事情，除非如果問題是你實際上不知道
what is a bucket and what i know what's a bucket and what in the bucket you
什麼是水桶，我知道什麼是一個桶，你桶裡有什麼
can't do this to me again
不能再這樣對我
mama mia what could it mean
媽媽咪呀這意味著什麼
stan it is meeting today figurine finders to me wow give me the [ __ ]
斯坦今天開會小雕像發現者給我哇，給我他媽的
bucket where are we going today the bucket asked stanley just smiled
鬥我們今天要去哪裡水桶問斯坦利，只是笑了笑
anywhere they went together would be perfectly fine
他們一起去的任何地方很好
[ __ ] it doesn't talk the bucket does it talk stop
他媽的它不說話桶做它談話停止
oh get out of my head get out of my head get out of my head get out of my head
哦，滾開我的頭，滾開我的頭滾開我的頭 滾開我的頭
oh wait what's this somewhere with both red and blue a large room of boxes lots
哦，等等，這兩者都是什麼地方紅色和藍色的一個大房間的盒子很多
of boxes oh boy oh boy i can't wait
盒子哦男孩哦男孩我等不及了
dude i can't [ __ ] wait we're gonna go all the way back up to the boss room
伙計，我等不及了，我們要走了一路回到boss房間
yeah i'm gonna go here and then the code is two eight four five ariel to the
是的，我要去這裡，然後是代碼是二八四五愛麗兒
yes this is certainly the most logical explanation
是的，這當然是最合乎邏輯的解釋
let me down maybe i am losing it i'm not making up
讓我失望也許我正在失去它我沒有彌補
no no i'm just i'm just i'm just
不不，我只是我只是我只是
spiraling i feel like i'm spiraling my my my brain is a haze right now it's
盤旋我覺得我在盤旋我的我的大腦現在是一片陰霾
full it's clouded it's full of bubbles
滿了 烏云密布 充滿了氣泡
mind control facility all right what's in here huh
精神控制設施好吧，這裡有什麼
what's in here what's the big idea
這裡有什麼 有什麼大創意
on an enormous room packed with television screens
在一個擠滿了電視屏幕
what horrible secret did this place hold stanley and the bucket both wandered to
這個地方藏著什麼可怕的秘密斯坦利和水桶都跑到
themselves
他們自己
stanley and the buckets and the buckets
斯坦利和水桶和水桶
and the buckets the monitors jumped to life and stanley
和水桶監視器跳了起來，斯坦利
nearly dropped the bucket in shock everyone in the office was being
震驚中差點把桶掉下來辦公室裡的每個人都在
videotaped is there a bucket in one of these
錄像其中一個有桶嗎
wait what about the ones that are fired like this and who's the fired ones burst
等等那些被解僱的人呢像這樣，被解僱的是誰？
into cradled it tears
進入抱著它流淚
reassuring it that everything would be fine
向它保證一切都會美好的
i cradled the bucket gently and caressed the bucket i i then firmly pressed my
我輕輕地托著桶，撫摸著然後我用力壓住我的桶
lips onto the metallic surface of his of his ridges his his triple ridges and
嘴唇貼在他的金屬表面上他的山脊 他的三棱脊和
then i grab the wooden handle of the bucket lift it up and put it on top of
然後我抓住了木柄桶把它舉起來放在上面
my like
我喜歡的
was the bucket under the mind control facility's influence as well had the
是精神控制下的水桶設施的影響也有
bucket been told to do things he didn't wish to do
桶被告知做他沒有做的事情想做
what kinds of things does a bucket want to do or not want to do in the first
水桶想要什麼樣的東西做或不想做在第一
place yeah i don't know i don't know i really don't know man
地方是的我不知道我不知道我真的不認識人
don't know anything i don't even i can't even comprehend what you're saying at
我什麼都不知道 我什至不能甚至理解你在說什麼
this point he screamed into the bucket he couldn't accept it his own life in
這一點他尖叫著入桶他無法接受他自己的生活
someone else's control never he squeezed the bucket tighter his one
別人的控制從不他把桶捏得更緊了
friend the entire world bucket at this point he could trust no one except for
全世界的朋友都在這一點他不能相信任何人，除了
the bucket
桶
but here was the proof the heart of the opera being
但這是證據歌劇的核心
eating working all of it monitored and commanded from this very place
吃工作所有這一切都受到監控和從這個地方指揮
and as the cold reality of his past began to sink in we're gonna get out
作為他過去的冰冷現實開始沉入我們要出去
here together bucket don't worry don't worry we're gonna get out of here
在這裡一起鬥別著急別著急擔心我們會離開這裡
we're getting out of here buddy me and you me and the bucket
我們要離開這裡，伙計我和你我和水桶
stanley in the bucket waited in blackness
桶裡的斯坦利等著黑
was it over is it over it's over [Music]
結束了嗎 結束了 結束了嗎[音樂]
yes it's over stanley it's over defeated
是的結束了，斯坦利，結束了
their greatest and darkest enemy freed themselves from the tyrannical grip of
他們最大和最黑暗的敵人被釋放自己從暴虐的手中
the evil mind control machine freedom was now mere moments away
邪惡的心靈控制機器自由現在就在片刻之外
excitedly the two of them began to discuss the kind of life they wanted to
兩人興奮地開始討論他們想要什麼樣的生活
live once they stepped through this massive me in the bucket my kid wanted
一旦他們經歷了這一切我的孩子想要的桶裡的我
to learn to roller skate stanley wanted to sneeze in every country on earth why
學習輪滑 stanley 想要在地球上的每個國家打噴嚏 為什麼
both of them wanted to begin watching a movie any movie but then stop it halfway
他們倆都想開始看電影任何電影，然後中途停止
through and begin watching it in reverse from the end
通過並開始反向觀看從頭到尾
true it was a simple life they envisioned but it was one they'd lived
真的，他們的生活很簡單設想，但這是他們住過的
together with one another to lean on to trust to support
彼此依靠信任支持
hello wait what was happening no why had the door stopped no was stanley in the
你好等待發生了什麼沒有為什麼門停了 沒有斯坦利在
bucket not about to be no no let me out please silence though let me out
桶不會是不不不讓我出去請保持沉默，儘管讓我出去
lingering oh no
揮之不去不好了
the truth hit stanley square in the face this building did not want the bucket to
真相直擊斯坦利廣場這棟樓不想水桶
leave even the facility itself recognized the
離開甚至設施本身也承認
incredible calming presence of the buffet needed the soothing warmth of the
令人難以置信的平靜存在自助餐需要舒緩的溫暖
bucking will go to any lengths not to part with the bucket what but
反抗將不遺餘力與水桶分道揚鑣
stanley can't leave this place not while he has such a precious bucket in his
斯坦利暫時不能離開這個地方他有這麼珍貴的水桶
arms not while this building has anything to say about it
當這座建築有有什麼要說的
stanley realized he would never again leave this very room but at least at
斯坦利意識到他再也不會離開這個房間，但至少在
least he has the bucket to be trapped eternally in darkness isn't really so
至少他有被困的桶永遠在黑暗中並非如此
bad stanley thought to himself as long as i have my bucket with me right i'll
壞斯坦利想了很久因為我有我的水桶，所以我會
be okay won't i stanley goat very soon now
沒事吧斯坦利山羊很快
he was about to find out
他正要知道
wha i'm fine i was about to leave oh
我很好我正要離開哦
wait oh my god wait hello
等待哦，我的上帝，等你好
there's a phone ringing
有電話響了
good morning thank you for contacting the future happiness foundation we are
早上好，感謝您的聯繫我們是未來的幸福基礎
confirming your shipment of 1 327 cardboard boxes to your place of
確認您的 1 件裝運327 個紙箱送到您的位置
work can you verify that this is correct
工作你能驗證這是正確的嗎
excellent your order will arrive shortly thank you again for contacting the
太好了，您的訂單將很快到達再次感謝您聯繫
future happiness foundation
未來幸福基金會
anyways i i guess we're getting carver boxes you
無論如何我想我們要給你買雕刻盒
[ __ ] you little [ __ ] you little [ __ ] you were the one thing that was gonna be
[ __ ]你這個小[ __ ]你這個小[ __ ]你是唯一的一件事
between me and escaping this place you know that you were the one barrier the
在我和逃離這個地方你之間知道你是唯一的障礙
one obstacle that i couldn't surmount to leave this never-ending hell it's all
我無法克服的一個障礙離開這個永無止境的地獄
because of you it's literally all because of you look at your rusty ass
因為你，這就是一切因為你看著你生鏽的屁股
yeah shut the [ __ ] up
是的閉嘴
i'll need you i never needed you
我需要你我從不需要你
a good bucket a strong bucket a humble bucket a committed bucket a bucket of
一個好桶 一個強壯的桶 一個卑微的桶桶 一個已提交的桶 一個桶
culture and distinction
文化與區別
stanley clutched the bucket tightly to his chest and entered the door on his
斯坦利緊緊抓住水桶他的胸膛，踏著他的門進了門
left
剩下
what do i do i don't know where to go guys guys where the [ __ ] do i go now
我該怎麼辦我不知道去哪裡伙計們，我現在要去哪裡
i don't know where to go if i go here let's just go like the same stuff that
如果我去這裡，我不知道該去哪裡讓我們像以前一樣
was before and if i go here oh my god oh my god wait the cardboard wait hold on
以前，如果我去這裡哦，我的上帝哦我的上帝等等紙板等等等等
hold on wait a room of large cardboard boxes
等一等大紙板房間盒子
maybe this was not the correct way to the meeting room but stanley had felt
也許這不是正確的方法會議室，但 stanley 覺得
the bucket calling to him telling him that the employee lounge was simply the
水桶呼喚他告訴他員工休息室簡直就是
place to be and here it was at the bucket maybe you
去的地方它就在桶裡，也許你
know maybe there's more cardboard boxes there now the bucket was wrong
知道也許還有更多的紙板箱現在桶錯了
stanley took the door on his left to go back to the meeting room
斯坦利拿著左邊的門走了回到會議室
now said the bucket don't go to the meeting
現在說水桶不去開會
no go somewhere else no cargo lift yes go there wait what is that cargo lift
不 去別的地方 沒有貨梯 是去那裡等等那個貨梯是什麼
how do i get there whoa wait a second
我如何到達那裡哇等一下
oh my god i'm pogging oh my god
哦，我的上帝，我在搗蛋我的天啊
you're getting close now stanley you've nearly gotten all of the figgler and
你現在越來越近了，斯坦利，你已經幾乎得到了所有的幻想和
marines very soon you'll collect the last one and then the first number will
海軍陸戰隊很快你就會收集最後一個，然後第一個數字將
equal the second number and that will be it
等於第二個數字，那將是它
we'll be different people by then different in the sense that we used to
到那時我們將成為不同的人在我們過去的意義上不同
have none of them and now we have them all you can't go back to when you had no
一個都沒有，現在我們有了當你沒有的時候，你無法回到的一切
figure and marines none of us can okay
人物和海軍陸戰隊我們誰都做不到好的
wait does that mean i can fall from here and not die
等等這是否意味著我可以從這裡掉下來不死
hold on is this is this a safe
堅持，稍等這是保險箱嗎
fall can i fall down here like
落下我可以像這樣跌倒嗎
reliably i don't know hold on let me go over here there's something in the vents
可靠地我不知道等一下讓我走通風口裡有東西
isn't there
不在那裡
hello
你好
hello where the [ __ ] are we
你好，我們到底在哪裡
ah
啊
where is this it doesn't look doesn't look very
這是哪裡它看起來不太
familiar very quiet
熟悉 很安靜
okay this is day number 295
好的這是第 295 天
tate number new person i don't even know i've lost track
泰號新人我什至不知道我迷路了
nothing feels real anymore
沒有什麼感覺真實了
the longer i study this bucket the less you lost me
我研究這個桶的時間越長你失去我的次數越少
anything mike you [ __ ] lost me when you said bucket the sheer
像你他媽的失去我一樣的東西你說水桶
euphoria i feel every time
我感到欣喜若狂每次
i pick it up no matter how many times i've done it
我撿起來不管我做了多少次
it's always the same feeling
總是一樣的感覺
and the emptiness in my chest when i set it down
和我胸中的空虛當我放下它
it doesn't make sense
它沒有說得通
there's no explanation for it still he's australia i haven't figured
沒有解釋還是他是澳大利亞我還沒想好
out why i see the world so differently when this bucket is in my arms
為什麼我對世界的看法如此不同當這個水桶在我懷裡
why everything feels so sorry
為什麼一切都感覺如此對不起
what do i do with this treasure treasure i can
我該怎麼處理這個寶藏我能
i like it i can monetize it what monetize the bucket
我喜歡它我可以通過它賺錢什麼將存儲桶貨幣化
it's unthinkable the amounts of money people will pay for even just an hour
這是不可想像的金額人們甚至會為一個小時付費
with the bucket this that sounds sass it's my golden
用桶這聽起來很粗魯，這是我的黃金
that sounds kind of sus but i have to be careful
這聽起來有點可疑，但我必須是小心
because as soon as this gets out there's going to be a target on my back
因為一旦這齣來了會成為我背上的目標
even now i don't know who might be trying to get
即使現在我也不知道可能是誰試圖得到
what's that who's there
那是什麼誰在那兒
[Music]
[音樂]
you sure this ain't a horror game yo
你確定這不是恐怖遊戲喲
are we gonna pretend like that never gonna happen
我們要假裝永遠會發生
narrator
敘述者
hello all of his co-workers were gone oh what could it mean oh these are all the
你好他所有的同事都走了哦這是什麼意思哦，這些都是
they decided to go to the meeting room oh my god these are all the cardboard
他們決定去會議室哦，天哪，這些都是硬紙板
boxes we ordered hey
我們訂購的盒子嘿
what's up [ __ ] the embrace of an old friend a withered
怎麼了[ __ ]老友的懷抱一個枯萎的人
companionship that stands the test of time stanley clutched the bucket tightly
經得起考驗的陪伴時間斯坦利緊緊地抓著水桶
to his this was not the correct way to the meeting room all in this together
對他來說，這不是正確的方法會議室都在這
[Music]
[音樂]
i'm going to go down to the bottom i want to go to the bottom not the left
我要下到谷底我想去底部而不是左邊
don't go to the meeting room go somewhere else the cargo lift yes go
不要去會議室去其他地方的貨運電梯是的
there i won't die surely i won't die if i jump from this but stanley feared that
那裡我不會死我肯定不會死如果我從這裡跳下來，但斯坦利擔心
anybody walked might lead to the separation of himself and the bucket his
任何人走路都可能導致他和他的桶分離
dearest friend so he threw himself to his death that
最親愛的朋友於是他投身自盡
they might die in one another's arms how deeply touching
他們可能會死在彼此的懷裡多麼感人
all of his co-workers will go what happened to the cardboard boxes
他所有的同事都會去做什麼發生在紙板箱上
stanley decided to go to the meeting room perhaps he had simply missed a memo
斯坦利決定去開會房間也許他只是錯過了一個備忘錄
but it made stanley want to be a better man and a better co-worker in time
但這讓斯坦利想變得更好男人和一個更好的同事及時
perhaps he would become both of those hey babe
也許他會成為這兩者嘿寶貝
you make me you know you you make me i want to be
你讓我知道你讓我我想成為
a better man i won't be better for you babe
一個更好的人我不會對你更好，寶貝
only the best version of myself that can be just for you babe
只有最好的自己只為你，寶貝
what the [ __ ] is that is this what is this what he wants
這他媽是什麼這是什麼這是他想要的
this bucket is making me lose where is somewhere both red and blue
這個水桶讓我迷失在哪裡紅色和藍色的某個地方
somewhere that is both red and blue so does that mean somewhere purple
紅色和藍色的地方，所以這是否意味著紫色的地方
because red and blue equals
因為紅色和藍色等於
red and blue doors oh alright hold on
紅色和藍色的門哦，好吧堅持，稍等
where's the red and blue doors area oh does that mean i have to not take the
紅藍門區在哪裡哦這是否意味著我不必採取
bucket because remember when we got to the red
桶因為記得當我們到達紅色時
door in the blue door area we we didn't have the bucket with us so does that
藍色門區的門，我們沒有把桶放在我們身邊
mean i can't take the bucket with me to get
意思是我不能帶著桶去拿
to that area when he was like
到那個區域的時候他喜歡
all of his co-workers were gone what could it mean
他所有的同事都走了是不是意味著
danny decided to go to the meeting room perhaps he had simply missed a memo
丹尼決定去會議室也許他只是錯過了一份備忘錄
yeah let's try it we're not bringing the bucket this time sorry guys when stanley
是的，讓我們試試吧，我們不帶這一次，當斯坦利時，對不起伙計們
came to a set of two open doors this was not the correct way to the meeting room
來到一組兩扇敞開的門，這是不是去會議室的正確方式
and stanley knew it perfectly well now how do i get to the door in the right
斯坦利現在非常清楚我怎麼到右邊的門
door
門
what did i do last night here it was the lounge
我昨晚在這裡做了什麼休息室
but eager to get back to business stanley took the first open door on his
但渴望恢復業務斯坦利打開他的第一扇門
left no sir no i didn't i'll not do that stanley was so bad at
不離開，先生，不，我沒有我不會做斯坦利那麼糟糕的事
following directions it's incredible he wasn't fired years ago
按照指示，他太不可思議了幾年前沒有被解僱
wait if i go down hold on hold on if what if i if i go to the vents
等我下去如果我去通風口怎麼辦
and i don't have the bucket does it change
我沒有水桶它會改變嗎
like if i go to that room inside the vents but i don't have the bucket
就像我去裡面的那個房間通風口，但我沒有水桶
wouldn't that be different hold on
那會不會不一樣堅持，稍等
stanley had now gotten himself so far off the beaten path that it seemed the
斯坦利現在已經做到了這麼遠在人跡罕至的地方，它似乎
office had begun just so far off the beaten path that it seemed the office
辦公室剛剛開始人跡罕至的地方，這似乎是辦公室
had begun just so far off the beaten path that it seemed the office had begun
剛剛開始離人遠去辦公室似乎已經開始的道路
you didn't think i was actually just a recording did you what a silly and trite
你沒想到我其實只是一個錄音你是多麼愚蠢和陳詞濫調
explanation that would be all the back and forth between you and me all the
說明一切都會過去的在你我之間來回
absurd adventures we've been through and it all turns out i'm just a tape
我們經歷過的荒謬冒險和原來我只是一盤磁帶
recording it was all justin stanley's head
錄音都是賈斯汀·斯坦利的頭
i bet that's the kind of twist you think is revelatory i bet each and every time
我敢打賭這就是你想的那種扭曲很有啟發性，我每次都打賭
you watch a movie where it turns out all to be in the main character's
你看了一部電影，結果證明一切成為主角
imagination you must absolutely bolt off the couch in pure shock at the
想像力，你必須徹底放棄沙發上完全震驚
phenomenal and intricate storytelling it must be so simple to be you
驚人而復雜的故事講述做你一定很簡單
life being an unending waterfall of surprises you're assuming a lot of
生命是一個永無止境的瀑布你假設很多驚喜
things about them how much more exciting you must find the world than the rest of
關於他們的事情有多令人興奮你必須比其他人找到世界
us do ah
我們做啊
now i've become sad look what you've done to me this is all your fault
現在我變得悲傷看看你有什麼對我做了這都是你的錯
he's sad oh and he just kicked me out okay well damn that's all i get
他很傷心哦，他只是把我踢出去了好吧，該死的，這就是我得到的一切
wait someone's calling again hello hi
等待有人再次打來你好你好
i'm i'm stuck here i'm done i just wanted to leave you a message to let you
我被困在這裡我已經完成了我只是想給你留言讓你
know there's a few things i need you to pick up on your way home from work today
知道有幾件事我需要你做今天下班回家的路上接你
we need milk cereal dish soap spaghetti get a thing of sugar
我們需要牛奶麥片洗潔精意大利面吃點糖
some bread and coffee beans whichever ones you like i'll give you a call if
一些麵包和咖啡豆你喜歡的我給你打電話
there's anything i forgot thanks sweetie see you tonight
有什麼我忘了謝謝親愛的今晚見
was that my wife or was that like number 434 oh okay
那是我的妻子嗎或者是像數字 434 哦，好吧
so i had to get milk cereal dish soap a thing of
所以我不得不買牛奶麥片洗潔精的東西
spaghetti some sugar and and my favorite coffee beans is that what she said
意大利面 一些糖和我最喜歡的咖啡豆就是她說的
did i remember all the time i came to a set of two open doors this was not the
我是否一直記得我來到一個兩扇敞開的門，這不是
correct way to the meeting room and staff this is not the correct way to
去會議室的正確方式和工作人員這不是正確的方法
stop by the employee lounge first whose wife is that right now i don't know i
先停在員工休息室妻子是不是現在我不知道我
guess it's my wife now it was okay my wife now well to get back to business
猜這是我的妻子現在沒關係我的妻子現在可以恢復工作了
ncr the first open door on his left maybe i'm the wife
ncr 左邊第一扇打開的門也許我是妻子
stanley was so bad by the way it's incredible
順便說一句，斯坦利太糟糕了太不可思議了
my wife
我的妻子
look stanley i think perhaps we've gotten off on the wrong foot here i'm
看斯坦利，我想也許我們已經我走錯了路
not your enemy really i'm not okay if i go over there that's the blue and red
不是你的敵人真的我不好去那邊那是藍色和紅色的
door stuff right difficult but the fact is that the story has been about nothing
門的東西很難，但事實是不是這個故事什麼都沒有
but you all this time if i do i jump off to go to the doors or do i go over there
但你一直都在，如果我這樣做，我會跳下去門口還是我去那裡
someone you've forgotten about jump down do i jump down to go to the doors stop
你已經忘記的人跳下我要跳下去去門站嗎
trying to make every decision really
試圖做出每一個決定真的
i was in the middle of something do you have zero consideration for others are
我在做某事你呢對他人零考慮是
you that convinced that i want something bad to happen to you why i don't know
你確信我想要一些東西壞事發生在你身上 為什麼我不知道
how to convince you of this but i really do want to help you to show you
如何讓你相信這一點，但我真的確實想幫助你向你展示
something beautiful look let me prove it let me prove that i'm on your side give
漂亮的東西讓我證明一下讓我證明我站在你這邊
me a chance
我有機會
save at this moment stanley this is a real accomplishment this oh my god
保存此刻 stanley 這是一個真正的成就，我的天啊
something just for the sake of we [ __ ] did it where so many people
只是為了我們他媽的在這麼多人那裡做的
expect to be rewarded for the most trivial achievements
期望得到最多的回報微不足道的成就
you've insisted that a job well done is its own reward do i not get a reward
你堅持認為做得好的工作是它自己的獎勵我沒有得到獎勵嗎
i'll tell you that i'm proud of you for collecting them all but that would be
我會告訴你，我為你感到驕傲收集它們，但那將是
like a reward and we can't have that so instead i'll just say it's done we're
就像獎勵一樣，我們不能這樣相反，我會說它已經完成了，我們是
all done here and now we can go to whatever the hell you were doing before
一切都在這裡完成，現在我們可以去不管你以前在做什麼
you hunted for food wait i got scammed i didn't get a reward that's it
你找食物等我被騙了我沒有得到獎勵，僅此而已
there's no reward oh my god now listen carefully this is important
沒有獎勵哦，我的上帝，現在聽著小心，這很重要
stanley walked through the red door
斯坦利穿過紅門
perhaps you misunderstood stanley walked through the red door i still don't think
也許你誤解了斯坦利走穿過紅門我還是不覺得
we're communicating properly stanley all right fine go ahead stanley you want to
我們溝通正常 stanley all好吧，去吧，斯坦利，你想要
know so badly what's out there you want to find out what okay now i can go back
非常清楚你想要什麼找出什麼好，現在我可以回去了
to the beginning of the game ah
到遊戲開始啊
are you do i really get nothing out of that
你是嗎？我真的一無所獲那
oh sorry but i have to put a pause on things it's just it's those figurines
哦，對不起，但我得暫停一下只是那些小雕像
what is this those figures oh my god that scared me since you have
這是什麼數字哦，我的上帝，因為你有
every last one wasn't it just the most intrinsically fulfilling moment of your
每一個都不是最你的內在充實的時刻
entire life didn't it fill you to the brim with inner richness
整個人生難道沒有讓你充滿充滿內在的豐富
yes i know we're supposed to be telling a story but won't you please indulge me
是的，我知道我們應該告訴一個故事，但你能不能放縱我
with one more trip back to the memory zone
再一次回到記憶中區
i would love nothing more than to revisit the figurines
我只想重溫小雕像
just one more time oh my god this man is
就再一次哦，我的上帝，這個人是
oh you gotta make me lose my mind man okay fine we'll go back we'll go back if
哦，你得讓我失去理智，伙計好吧好吧我們會回去如果我們會回去
that makes you so happy we instantly found the collectibles we
這讓你很開心我們立即找到了我們的收藏品
literally found them like within the hour you're acting like i found them
從字面上發現它們就像在小時你表現得就像我找到了他們
back in 2010.
回到2010年。
okay ah
好的啊
here's where it all began the first collectible back then we had
一切從這裡開始那時我們擁有的第一個收藏品
no idea of how many of them we'd find sure it's at six right there on the
不知道我們會找到多少確定它在六點就在那兒
screen but how could we know for certain we were so innocent
屏幕，但我們怎麼能確定我們是如此無辜
we'll never be like that again stanley
我們再也不會那樣了 斯坦利
wait where is this
等等這是哪裡
where is this i hear something creepy wait and here was a second stan marine
這是哪裡，我聽到了一些令人毛骨悚然的東西等等，這是第二艘 stan Marine
i'll be honest back then i had no faith in you to find any of them let alone six
我會誠實的，那時我沒有信仰在你身上找到其中任何一個，更不用說六個了
but you continue to surprise me in all sorts of mundane unremarkable ways
但你繼續讓我感到驚訝各種平凡無奇的方式
okay let's do a little quiz huh which of these rooms was the room you found your
好吧，讓我們做個小測驗，呵呵這些房間是你找到的房間
third mini stand can you remember
第三個迷你架你還記得嗎
i think we found it in the bathroom i'm pretty sure that's where we found it
我想我們是在浴室裡找到的我很確定那是我們找到它的地方
right hey that's exactly right it was here in
正確的嘿，這是完全正確的，它就在這裡
the boss's bathroom it was the third one you picked it up and then after that you
老闆的浴室是第三間你把它撿起來然後你
had three of them i didn't pick up the first one by accident it was so crystal
有三個我沒有拿起第一個是偶然的，它是如此晶瑩剔透
clear in your memory but i shouldn't be surprised after all science tells us
在你的記憶中清晰，但我不應該在所有科學告訴我們之後感到驚訝
that it's impossible to forget your third time doing anything
不可能忘記你的第三次做任何事
it's impossible to forget my third time doing anything
不可能忘記我的第三次做任何事情
let's see what came next oh yes we found a fig in this pink room
讓我們看看接下來會發生什麼哦，是的，我們在這個粉紅色的房間裡發現了一個無花果
oh well i can't actually say i remember being in this room we were never here
哦，我實際上不能說我記得在這個房間裡，我們從未在這裡
before the memory zone so it must have happened
在內存區之前，所以它必須有發生了
why
為什麼
this was the fifth ministan and this one was really something special it was in
這是第五個部長和這個真的很特別
the warehouse i remember it so clearly in fact because this one is particularly
倉庫我記得很清楚其實因為這個特別
special to me i made a little video to commemorate the occasion enjoy you made
對我來說很特別，我製作了一個小視頻紀念你享受的場合
a video
一段錄像
[Music]
[音樂]
i i hate this game of so much what is this
我非常討厭這個遊戲這是什麼
2005 edits style oh my god bro
2005 年編輯風格哦，我的上帝，兄弟
this is so dumb this is so dumb
這太愚蠢了這太愚蠢了
[Music]
[音樂]
best boy
最好的男孩
takes you back doesn't it i spent a lot of time making that video but it was
帶你回去不是我花了很多錢製作那個視頻的時間，但它是
eight minutes i wouldn't have spent on anything else
我不會花八分鐘還要別的嗎
and now where am i going
現在我要去哪裡
what the [ __ ] even what's that i don't know
什麼他媽的甚至什麼我不知道知道
what even was that and then right then we came to the last collectible yeah the
那是什麼，然後就在那時我們來到了最後一個收藏品是的
final figurine right here by the red and blue doors this memory is the most
最後的雕像就在紅色和藍門這段記憶最
distinct and clear in my mind perhaps because it was the one that happened
也許在我腦海中清晰而清晰因為那是發生的一件事
more recently than all the others you're you're a funny guy
比你最近的所有其他人你是個有趣的人
you know that works all i know is that this is the moment where you picked up a
你知道這行得通我所知道的是這是你拿起一個
fig and i thought to myself yes that's all of them they're all collected it was
無花果，我心想，是的他們都被收集起來了
a moment unlike any other except for the other moments picking up
與眾不同的時刻除了其他時刻回升
figurines which it was exactly like
一模一樣的小雕像
oh wait they're both to the same area
哦，等等，他們都在同一個地區
you are in the present and then
你在當下接著
there was no more because we've caught up to the present moment nothing left to
沒有了，因為我們抓到了到現在為止什麼都沒有
do would move onward into the future goodbye memory zone
做會走向未來再見記憶區
um no no no i'm not done i'm not ready to
嗯不不不，我還沒做完，我還沒準備好
move on stop the loading screen isn't there some way we can stay here keep
繼續停止加載屏幕不是我們可以留在這裡
enjoying these figurines let's just go backwards no we'll do the memory zone
享受這些小雕像讓我們走吧向後不，我們會做記憶區
again from the opposite direction see how that feels
再次從相反的方向看感覺如何
i'm scared i don't want to go back i don't want to go back
我害怕我不想回去我不想回去
what is this man doing to me
這個人在對我做什麼
all the illusion of choice yes sir okay yes the room with the red
所有選擇的錯覺是的，先生，好的，是的，紅色的房間
and blue doors i remember this i must say of all the figurines we
和藍色的門，我記得這個我必須說我們所有的小雕像
looked at in our initial tour of the memory zone this one he's making me do
在我們最初的遊覽中看過記憶區這是他讓我做的
it again clear in my mind oh my god get me out
它再次清晰在我的腦海中哦，我的上帝，讓我出去
you better not play another video don't you remember the video we watched
你最好不要播放另一個視頻你不記得我們看過的視頻嗎
yes love that video
是的喜歡那個視頻
you you showed it to me like one second ago
你像一秒鐘一樣向我展示了它前
what the [ __ ] what the [ __ ] is happening you don't
什麼鬼他媽的發生了什麼你沒有
remember the pink room stanley still no memory of this one yeah this one's weird
記得粉紅色的房間 stanley 還是沒有記得這個是的，這個很奇怪
though a solid room i don't think we got it from the pink room did we get it from
雖然我認為我們沒有一個堅固的房間它是從粉紅色的房間裡得到的
the pink room i don't remember i really don't remember
粉紅色的房間 我不記得了 我真的不記得
these really were a treat to hunt down you know if there had been any kind of
這些真的是一種追捕的享受你知道是否有任何一種
reward for finding all of these it really would have muted the intrinsic
找到所有這些的獎勵真的會削弱內在的
joy of collecting them i'm very glad we resisted the temptation next one
收集它們的樂趣我很高興我們抵制下一個誘惑
is definitely a horror game i am
絕對是恐怖遊戲我是
living hell
活的地獄
right now this was our second fig don't you
馬上這是我們的第二個無花果，不是嗎？
remember yes i remember i remember it because this is like the third time
記得 是的 我記得 我記得因為這就像第三次
why does anyone ever choose to leave it keep going
為什麼有人會選擇離開它繼續
oh wait hold on wait let me grab it oops sorry okay i grabbed it 16 16.
哦等等等等讓我抓住它哎呀對不起，好吧，我抓住了它 16 16。
wow we missed this place this is it the very first one we found in the exhibit
哇，我們錯過了這個地方，這就是它我們在展覽中發現的第一個
where i introduced you to the figurines oh i want more memories stanley i want
我向你介紹小雕像的地方哦，我想要更多的回憶斯坦利，我想要
to keep going [ __ ] you i want out before this
繼續去他媽的你我想出去之前這個
i want out get me out of here
我想出去帶我離開這裡
oh what is this collectible oh yeah this is back where in the beginning
哦，這是什麼收藏品哦，是的，這是回到了最初的地方
yeah get me out get me out give me i gotta escape i got you out here the
是的 讓我出去 讓我出去 給我我我得逃跑我把你弄出去了
terrible new content that we were originally sold on oh man i gotta leave
可怕的新內容，我們是原來賣的哦，伙計，我要走了
i gotta leave the time does we need to get out
我得離開我們需要的時間出去
oh yes the two doors oh god [ __ ] that a classic memory
哦，是的，兩扇門哦，天哪，那是一段經典的記憶
this one
這個
what's wrong with him and before everything else there was
他究竟怎麼了在其他一切之前
your office
你的辦公室
yeah is there anything else was there something that came before your office
是的 還有其他的嗎你辦公室前的東西
there's something i feel i can remember i can remember i can remember
有些事情我覺得我記得我記得 我記得
what do you remember yes i'm remembering something now
你記得什麼是的，我記得現在的東西
i remember before this whole story got started back then i was
我記得在整個故事發生之前那時我就開始了
i was different i used to make big decisions i was
我不一樣我過去常常做出重大決定
passionate i was skeptical i weighed each decision with profound
充滿激情的我持懷疑態度我稱重每一個決定都深刻
thoughtfulness and then somewhere along the way i stopped making decisions
體貼，然後在某個地方我停止做決定的方式
i became lazy and i came up with well came up with a character named stanley
我變得懶惰，我想出了很好想出了一個名叫斯坦利的角色
to do my thinking for me he would make the decisions he would decide which way
為我做我的想法，他會讓他將決定哪種方式的決定
to go i would cheer him on as he collected
去當他收集時，我會為他加油
figurines for no reason why did i invent stanley
無緣無故我發明的小雕像斯坦利
was i lonely yes perhaps that's it perhaps i needed to imagine i had
我孤獨嗎 是的 也許就是這樣也許我需要想像我有
companionship and stanley really did make for a wonderful companion even if
陪伴和斯坦利真的做到了做一個美妙的伴侶，即使
he was a fiction but i suppose it's grown old i
他是虛構的但我想它已經變老了
i want to think for myself again i want to go back to how it used to be
我想再為自己考慮我想回到過去的樣子
yes i can be on my own again i can do it i'll be stronger this time i'll take
是的，我可以再次獨自一人，我可以做到這次我會更堅強，我會接受
care of myself i don't need stanley anymore oh but he truly was so much fun
照顧好自己我不需要斯坦利哦，但他真的很有趣
to play with you know what
和玩你知道嗎
since we're in the memory zone how about one more good memory let's go back just
因為我們在記憶區怎麼樣又是一段美好的回憶讓我們回去吧
once and give stanley one more run of the office and then i'll retire him for
一次，再給斯坦利一次辦公室，然後我會讓他退休
good i did enjoy telling his story so very much okay
很好，我很喜歡講他的故事，所以非常好
here we go this is the story of a man named stanley
開始了這是一個叫斯坦利的人的故事
the end is never the end i think i think that's the end though wait hold on is
結束永遠不是結束 我想我想這就是結束，雖然等待堅持是
that actually the end or is it is like okay how about we do it one more time
那實際上是結束還是它就像好吧，我們再做一次怎麼樣
and he just it's just like a loop again we do literally everything again i don't
他只是又像一個循環我們從字面上再次做一切我不
know or that is i think that's it right
知道或者那是我認為這是正確的
maybe one more one more
也許還有一個多一個
all of his co-workers were gone what could it mean
他所有的同事都走了是不是意味著
you missed some endings
你錯過了一些結局
not everyone is so lucky to have a bucket but stanley is a very it's a loop
不是每個人都這麼幸運擁有一個桶，但斯坦利是一個非常它的循環
guys guys it's a loop i'm pretty sure it's a loop and it's just like oh how
伙計們，這是一個循環，我很確定這是一個循環，就像哦，如何
about we do it one more time and then they're gonna bring me again through
關於我們再做一次然後他們會讓我再次通過
everything yeah
一切是的
okay okay
好的好的
look it's never ending this game never ends it just goes on forever okay
看它永遠不會結束這個遊戲永遠不會結束，它會永遠持續下去，好吧
ah
啊
i am i have been put through
我是我已經通過
a lot of mental torment from this game
很多心理這場比賽的折磨
was it fun yes it was but
好玩嗎 是的但
did it break me yes it did it broke me somehow it broke me
它打破了我是的它打破了我不知怎的，它打破了我
i i i can never
一世我永遠不能
look at a bucket the same way again dude
再以同樣的方式看水桶老兄
i can never look at a bucket the same [ __ ] way again without thinking about
我永遠無法以同樣的方式看待水桶再次他媽的不假思索
the tractor i'm gonna look at a tractor and be like is this a bucket
拖拉機 我要看看拖拉機就像這是一個桶
like you know how much damage that is that's a lot of damage
就像你知道那是多大的傷害這是很大的傷害
that's a lot of damage my guy
這是很大的傷害我的傢伙
ah okay i'm gonna drink some water give me a
啊好吧我要喝點水給我一個
second
第二
i'm done i'm done that's it
我受夠了我已經完成了
we are done with the stanley parable there is no more there is no more
我們完成了斯坦利的比喻沒有了 沒有了
stanley there is no parable why it is only shoto there is only shotgun now
斯坦利沒有比喻為什麼會這樣只有shoto現在只有shot彈槍
okay there is only shoto only shotpo only
好的只有shoto只有shotpo只有
shoto okay
還好
only shot though oh
雖然只開槍哦
my goodness bro what a [ __ ] game
我的天啊兄弟什麼他媽的遊戲
i i'm not okay i'm not okay i need to i feel like
我不好我不好，我需要我感覺
here's what i'm gonna do here's what i'm gonna do to help myself i'm gonna go
這就是我要做的事情 這就是我要做的事情我要去幫助自己
take a shower i'm gonna sit in the shower
洗個澡，我要坐在淋浴
listen to uh i don't know listen to some keshie just sit in there for like 10
聽 呃 我不知道 聽一些keshie 只是坐在那裡 10
minutes maybe like open my mouth and like you
分鐘也許喜歡張開嘴喜歡你
know let the let the shower water like spray against my tongue but i'm not
知道讓淋浴水喜歡噴在我的舌頭上，但我不是
actually gonna drink the shower water i'm just gonna like let it like you know
實際上會喝淋浴水我只想讓你知道
impact my tongue because it feels kind of funny when it does that i like it and
影響我的舌頭，因為它感覺很親切有趣的是我喜歡它
and after that i'll get out of the shower right
然後我會離開正確淋浴
i'm gonna go out actually touch some grass
我要出去實際觸摸一些草
right go to the gym come back be a little responsible and then i'm
去健身房回來吧有點負責，然後我
gonna play video games i'm just gonna play whatever video game i want maybe i
我會玩電子遊戲玩我想要的任何視頻遊戲也許我
want to go pew pew maybe i won't play league of legends maybe i want to play
想去 pew pew 也許我不會玩英雄聯盟也許我想玩
final fantasy i don't know i'll play something but
最終幻想我不知道我會玩但是
i want to touch some grass because
我想摸一些草因為
i i gotta i don't know this is this game makes me
我要我不知道這是這個遊戲讓我
feel like i need to to get out of the room i don't know
感覺我需要離開不知道的房間
it's just like it makes me feel like this existential crisis like i need to
就像它讓我覺得這種生存危機就像我需要的那樣
escape now i don't want to be in inside my room at the moment i gotta like run
現在逃跑我不想在裡面我現在的房間我得喜歡跑步
outside okay and just and just like breathe in the air maybe pet some dogs
外面還好，公正，就像呼吸空氣也許撫摸一些狗
maybe i'll go to the park and pet some more dogs dude i saw a husky and a shiva
也許我會去公園養寵物更多的狗，伙計，我看到了一隻哈士奇和一隻濕婆
the other day i had to pet both of them that was pog as hell i love those dogs i
前幾天我不得不撫摸他們兩個那真是太棒了，我愛那些狗，我
wanna see them again the game entirely multiple times
想再見到他們遊戲完全多次
i don't know i really don't know my name's not jim my
我不知道我真的不知道我的名字不是吉姆我的
name is not jim anyways i'm gonna quit to the main menu
反正名字不是吉姆我要退出主菜單
okay ah
好的啊
thank you everybody for coming by today though it means a lot that
謝謝大家今天過來雖然這意味著很多
you were here to relive through that experience with me even though like it
你來這裡是為了重溫那個和我一起體驗，即使喜歡
was it was suffering you got to see me like break a little bit
你要見我是不是很痛苦像休息一下
to get to the epilogue you have to reboot the game entirely multiple times
要到達尾聲，你必須完全重啟遊戲多次
oh my god really reboot the game entirely multiple times
哦，我的上帝，真的完全重啟遊戲多次
holy [ __ ] also satsui thank you for the thousand
天哪也satsui謝謝你的一千個
bits you keeping for the 300 3 000 bits and then i'm leaving for the donald as
您為 300 3 000 位保留的位然後我要去唐納德
well um
出色地嗯
and uh priscilla priscilla thank you for the tier one thank you for the bits uh
嗯，普里西拉，普里西拉，謝謝你第一層謝謝你的位呃
thank you for the tier one uh chloe thank you for the gift sob andrea thank
謝謝你的第一層呃克洛伊謝謝你的禮物抽泣安德里亞謝謝
you for the bits oats thank you for the bits too
你的燕麥片謝謝你位也
thank you for the [ __ ]
謝謝你的[ __ ]
breath some fresh air have some sweet f the bucket
呼吸一些新鮮空氣有一些甜蜜的f桶
f the bucket do you are you trying to sell me you want me to [ __ ] the bucket
f桶你是你想賣給我你想讓我操桶
or are you saying hey yeah [ __ ] that bucket no one cares about that bucket
或者你是說嘿，是的，他媽的桶 沒人關心那個桶
because it comes off in two different ways i don't know
因為它以兩種不同的方式脫落我不知道的方式
uh and i'll let me see who else who else
呃我會讓我看看還有誰還有誰
who else jess thank you for the five gifted subs and umi-san thank you for
還有誰傑西謝謝你的五個有天賦的潛艇和 umi-san 謝謝你
the five uh it's your own gift subs as well and some kiwi thank you for the
五個呃這是你自己的禮物替代品好吧，還有一些獼猴桃，謝謝你
zono and rinwin thank you for the doll now
zono 和 rinwin 謝謝你的娃娃現在
and uh
和呃
really thank you for the download too and uh see thank you for the uh five
也非常感謝您的下載嗯，謝謝你的五個
gift subs still and emil angelo thank you for the attendance you want to give
禮物潛艇仍然和埃米爾安吉洛謝謝你想出席
subs dale thank you so much
潛艇戴爾非常感謝你
wow i know there's more endings
哇我知道還有更多的結局
i know there's more endings but i will probably approach those endings again
我知道還有更多的結局，但我會的可能會再次接近那些結局
when i feel like it or just because like you know i'll be like sure why not i'll
當我喜歡它或只是因為喜歡你知道我會肯定為什麼不我會
go check these out since there's a lot of them right i know there's a lot of
去看看這些，因為有很多他們是對的，我知道有很多
them but reasonably i feel like it's gonna
他們但合理地我覺得它會
take me a while to like you know explore each and every single one of them they
花點時間像你一樣探索他們每一個人
just take me a bit but i'm going to go look for someone to
帶我一點但我要去找人
raid thank you guys for coming by today tomorrow
突襲謝謝你們今天來明天
tomorrow we're playing fatal frame i really was thinking about playing
明天我們要玩致命一局我真的在考慮玩
fiddle frame today instead but i just felt like we've had so much horror
今天取而代之的是小提琴框架，但我只是感覺就像我們經歷了太多的恐怖
content back to back i don't think i want to just like drown myself in too
內容背靠背我不認為我也想淹死自己
much spooks i gotta like give myself a break and man this was a break all right
我很想給自己一個休息，伙計，這是一個休息，好吧
ah this was quite the [ __ ] first it broke me as a break it broke me
啊，這真是他媽的第一次打破了我作為一個休息它打破了我
it did its job so um yeah i'm ready for fatal frame tomorrow
它完成了它的工作，嗯是的，我準備好迎接明天的致命一擊了
i heard a lot of good things about fatal frame a lot of you guys liked it
我聽到了很多關於致命的好消息框架你們很多人都喜歡
everyone a lot of people recommended it so let me try it out and see how it goes
很多人都推薦了所以讓我試試看效果如何
i'm scared though i know it's hard i know it's really spooky
我很害怕雖然我知道這很難我知道這真的很恐怖
so um i'll see you tomorrow for that and uh thank you for coming by okay
所以我明天見呃謝謝你過來好
if you guys haven't joined the discord already uh it's discord.json
如果你們還沒有加入discord已經是discord.json了
um i usually post announcements there about
嗯我通常在那裡發布關於
when i go live and subscribers also get like access to additional content so hey
當我上線時，訂閱者也會得到喜歡訪問其他內容，所以嘿
i might post something there sometime soon so you guys can like take a sneak
我可能會在某個時候在那裡發布一些東西很快，你們就可以偷偷摸摸
peek at what's been going on also uh be sure to follow me on twitter
看看發生了什麼也一定要在推特上關注我
and subscribe on youtube i posted a new video on youtube recently so check that
並在 youtube 上訂閱我發布了一個新的最近在 youtube 上的視頻，所以檢查一下
out okay
好的
all right have a good night guys i'm gonna look for somebody to raid but i'll
好吧，晚安，伙計們，我是會找人突襲，但我會
play a quick ad in the meantime so brb give me a second
同時播放快速廣告，所以 brb你稍等一會兒
what a [ __ ] game though oh my god what a [ __ ] game dude i would rather
多麼他媽的遊戲啊，我的天啊我寧願玩什麼他媽的遊戲
like um i i don't know instead of like the
喜歡嗯我不知道而不是喜歡
the bucket i think it's just the bucket that's getting to me something about the
桶 我認為它只是桶這讓我對
[ __ ] bucket
他媽的桶
jesus i like the the moment i started to snap
耶穌我喜歡我開始抓拍的那一刻
was when the game introduced the bucket like that was the turning point that was
是遊戲引入水桶的時候就像那是轉折點
the moment i snapped
我拍的那一刻
god damn okay let's see who's live right now
該死的好吧，讓我們看看現在誰在直播
oh yeah i'm gonna go hard at the gym today i really all wanted to i really
哦，是的，我要在健身房努力今天我真的很想我真的
want to uh i don't know since i didn't go yesterday i'm gonna make up for it
想呃我不知道，因為我沒有昨天去我會彌補的
today and uh do a little bit more it's because like my
今天和呃多做一點這是因為像我的
my upper my upper shoulders were a little bit sore for some odd reason so i
我的上我的上肩是由於某種奇怪的原因有點疼，所以我
didn't wanna like overdo it right and like you know hurt myself it's good to
不想喜歡過度正確和就像你知道傷害自己一樣，這很好
take breast days when you can we're gonna go and read
盡可能採取乳房日我們要去讀
uh
呃
a canadian youtuber and um i think she does a lot of variety
一個加拿大youtuber和嗯我認為她有很多變化
content as well and um very cute as a fun little voice i think
內容以及嗯我認為作為一個有趣的小聲音非常可愛
you guys would like her model she's very sweet as well so share some love
你們會喜歡她的模特，她很也很甜蜜，所以分享一些愛
okay let's see
好吧，讓我們看看
i think this is right
我認為這是對的
take care guys have a good night i love you
保重 伙計們 晚安 我愛你
[Music] sleep well okay i'll see you tomorrow
[音樂]睡個好覺，明天見
[Music]
[音樂]